schmxtzz: ayeee
schmxtzz: we live
archer723: Yo bro, good to seeeee you!
oakmrk: PogChamp LIVE
fuseteaseftali: hewy george
Toastie1: late stream PogChamp
masters8: yeee boi
meteorlake: hey george
awesomeo113: Yee yee
ankitc: yeeet
meteorlake: geo the living icon
benchai18: What Jorge
glitch3dout: Hello
schmxtzz: 30 days streaming everyday Pogchamp
jay_al97: good morinng
roystang: is this an ice chewing stream
benchai18: Pawgchamp
Jehhred: What gives George, I thought there wasn't going to be a stream today?!?!?!
wisamalrawi: first timer
logi6000: ayy a nother stream
imAidenr: @georgehotz hey man hows it going?
vrv_exe: Hah. Wasn’t expecting this. Perfect timing.
aiex42: wassup bro
benchai18: George. Subscriber for 4 months. Whatup son. Why do I like u so much
urhentom: how's everyone back home George?
OrlinTheMage: hey hottie!
benchai18: The moment the stream has 200-300 he’s gonna turn it up to 11
hexicity1: yo George, apart from being interested in it, how do you keep interested/focused on something you're working on, on the side? I seem to lose focus/motivation on things very quickly
rawrxp: hello
itsxaos: <3
deva73: yo
benchai18: He gets especially obnoxious (in the best way) as the stream goes on
logi6000: how's everyones day
grenaderaven: did you see stephen wolframs corona stream? he did a lot of data analysis using mathematica
TheLastMrX: shame im lazy otherwise i would comment now :(
coolmacjr: coolmacjr subscribed with Twitch Prime.
cankunwang: Have you checked this paper? A SARS-CoV-2-Human Protein-Protein Interaction Map Reveals Drug Targets and Potential Drug-Repurposing
amo77777: hey🙂
benchai18: George’s fav sweater
not_Awful: thank you geo
Jaynevs: !gamble 100
logi6000: who does comma ai archive
benchai18: Ugh. There goes my evening.
lawric_: LUL
TheLastMrX: LUL
guapcollector: lern teh hacking
urhentom: he is an idiot
amo77777: 🚀
mirceau: He back.. My man is on a role!!
urhentom: we love to waste time with you
doctorgenus: i love u geohot keep tinkering
archer723: BAN him, Lol
doctorgenus: its tinkering
mirceau: Shit talking
logi6000: they are thinking of the bs Hollywood hacking
champ900: is comma paying you to do these streams
schmxtzz: finding exploits
cankunwang: trying finding 'meaning' for everything
guapcollector: hacking is collecting certs wym
roystang: hacking is infiltration the online mainframe and getting money
mirceau: And getting shit done
GabeDoesNotTalk: We’re hacking the Wirus!
benchai18: Don’t “you guys” us. That’s one retard... most of us ain’t that bad
Nefariousbtw: hacking is actually observing right?
slimetimewalks: Favorite snack ?
Jehhred: The point is to waste time!!!!!
popposbubbolo: rofl
Penguino138: Groceries are in the same place as yesterday hehe
l1ght5p33d: hack for win
Nefariousbtw: I think hes confusing hacking with cracking
OrlinTheMage: I love you!
omar3141: NP hard: hard to solve, easy to verify!
grenaderaven: in his defence you didnt hack your local university photo directory and create a competitive tinder like app...thats hAcKinG
mirceau: Hacking = critical thinking and considering your targets world view.
DecayingSkullz: Hi George
urhentom: why incognito?
doctorgenus: its like edison and the light bulb
byLeandroid: "hacking is just being able to think with an open mind" 😍
hexicity1: George if you were someone just at the basics of CS, what languages would you learn first and what steps would you take, with the hindsight and knowledge you have now?
logi6000: hacking is like math. you can tell if you've got the right answer and you can see how far off you are
hitsIikeagirl: hacking seems to be an applied art, like trading.
guapcollector: that good zine formatting
georgehotz: http://www.phrack.org/issues/7/3.html
RODNEYDIESEL: thanks boss man
zennydmt: hi do you use docker at all?
roystang: this stream got deep real quick
LocoLuka: is this data science?
logi6000: @roystang just as it should be
meteorlake: geo, i liked ur sxsw talk..
TheLastMrX: hacking is just about not being normal and dont do what ppl say to do... be yourself
archer723: I prefer shit talking than doing stuff, hacking will be less entertaining for sure. So any chance we can get rapping today instead?
AlwaysTilted_: a society that values you for SKILLS not affiliations
mirceau: it’s 04:05 a.m. here.
logi6000: @meteorlake the simulation one?
meteorlake: simulation theory is definitely interesting
yanhaoli: What’s up geo hogs
guapcollector: duckduckgo bro
itsxaos: reddit is absolute trash
swftdev: Geo being back is the silver lining of the plague >.<
mirceau: true
benchai18: This is By far the most serious I’ve ever seen George on Twitch
thuganalyst: Beautiful
logi6000: sim theory is one of my fav theories
neiliss: You are going back to my early days with that brings back memories, might reread them and some 2600 while I’m at it
DecayingSkullz: ooooffff
l1ght5p33d: Ecosia is alright sometimes but Capitalism rules all
champ900: George are you afraid for humanity
slArkBig: and there is r/China
glitch3dout: Dude reddit search sucks
7Locrian7: isn't that just based off the description of those subreddits?
128p_: r/memes is not completely crap.
glitch3dout: Why would you use reddit search
7Locrian7: just seems like an overly simplistic search
guapcollector: seems like its just based on frequency of mentions
cutza: their algorithms seem to be optimized for attention, not relevance
highxsnow_: maybe they filter by where most ppl post shit about corona like corona memes
swftdev: everyone know reddit search is a meme, should have started on google.
Penguino138: Reddit sends out spammy articles to my email all the time, so annoying
imafungi53: memes is how society deals with tragedy
mirceau: We trashed Google / Twitter / Reddit / Youtube results ! Look at youtube trending once.. !
benchai18: Isn’t that indicative of how large groups of people are kinda.... dumb? Or simple? The algorithm is just adapting to accommodate the behavior of the masses no???
cankunwang: Maybe their algorithm based on what ppl likely goes to after searching covid-19
archer723: All I want is you stream everyday no matter whatever you want to stream LoL
l1ght5p33d: reddit does have probably the leetest mod algorithm of all
kornez: @georgehotz maybe try to escape dash LUL
SparksCx: low members?
guapcollector: sort for recent communities
nozpheratu: It's being hidden maybe?
bankzed: the search results are returned by frequency and by number of views
mirceau: The results of Google is like: The kings mirrors his people.
sp3ed_xx: have you listened to eminem godzilla song?
benchai18: But human subjective meaning isn’t discerned by the algorithm isn’t it?
itsxaos: agree
mirceau: True
meteorlake: Healthy people with no underlying conditions are in the hospital for 10 days. You live but its a nasty virus either way. Whats really sad is whats happening to every bodies grandparents, stay safe ppl
logi6000: could this be what could be new in a decentralized internet?
Retromankind: Agree
SparksCx: there
SparksCx: I SAW IT
mashafique: COVID19 is a meme LUL
benchai18: Fair enough
pz3300: What’s happenin George?
solitarynative: searching on reddit is usually trash
nozpheratu: Is google a better search engine for finding reddits then reddit itself?
Plurmorant: china_flu best subreddit Kreygasm
LocoLuka: the internet is made to make it easier for new ppl and ppl that dont use the internet frequently
cankunwang: True. I can only receive good information by following professors in twitter
OlympusDev: SCROLL UP
Santiago_LHC: It's valuing popularity over some higher criteria of relevance
xa1ry: try "covid19" (in quotes) or something?
hexicity1: George if you were someone just at the basics of CS, what languages would you learn first and what steps would you take, with the hindsight and knowledge you have now?
benchai18: I just imagined it’s predictive. The algorithm knows what most people do. Most people are not power users
mirceau: I deleted my Reddit 4 months ago due to this shit !
bankzed: completely agree, the internet is far from the academic endeavor it was once
Digital_donger: covid19 is a bad meme
128p_: ^
nitthewiz: Tru
SparksCx: lol
kornez: truuue, its trash
hitsIikeagirl: 100
fantadmin: add ``` site:reddit.com`
Santiago_LHC: lol
Lathendros: @georgehotz what do u have against business insider
zennydmt: do u read scidaily?
highxsnow_: same
l1ght5p33d: The search results are super dynamic, can change instantly
guinness84: respect
guapcollector: duckduckgo does better
LaheyFPS: truueee
cankunwang: Can I block website from google?
itsxaos: https://duckduckgo.com/?t=ffab&q=covid 19 positive reddit&ia=web
nozpheratu: try this "covid 19 positie site:reddit.com"
itsxaos: ddg finds it sorta :)
Santiago_LHC: I want all my search results to be the bill gates blog
Plurmorant: wow
imafungi53: whats wrong with business insider
itsxaos: :D
Penguino138: Always use duckduck go
pz3300: First page of google is a shit show
Plurmorant: its not bought
hexicity1: PogChamp duckduckgo
barkazzaz: cause google still wants to prioritize based on mentions
nozpheratu: You can search google w/ a site: prefix
edu4594: google sucks
mohammed1996mizab: Pog
bankzed: yeah duckduckgo is much better
Penguino138: You can easily change your phone and computer to default to DuckDuckGo
ahahahaitslit: when did this stream start?
cutza: pay the moneys
benchai18: Most people are subscribed to covid, funny, memes, and The Bachelor. If these algorithms learn by patterns of use, and most users are not powerusers (or they’re simple people), don’t u think the algorithm will adapt accordingly ?
Santiago_LHC: @nozpheratu That's not the point
meteorlake: What's your take on COVID-19 @georgehotz
ackxhpaez: at least with bing you can get points you can use for free burritos
itsxaos: hey what do you think of this urbit thing? seems kinda goofy to me
l1ght5p33d: allocate half meta data stream always
slArkBig: It's because these companies hire mediocre software engineers
logi6000: ight time to go make millions of George's idea
ph4tal_: what'd I just run into
RODNEYDIESEL: okay can you give me funding
wholesome_pepe: we can call it altavista?
glitch3dout: Google is good at some stuff. DDG is good at some stuff
zennydmt: why do you think Google is a failed company?
nitthewiz: Agreed
guapcollector: nah it's because of monetisation not lack of skill
mirceau: Really difficult
glitch3dout: Comeback of Yahoo
zennydmt: Why dont you like Google?
ryboii1: why is google a failed organization?
pz3300: I don’t trust duck duck go. When you type in bitchu.... it doesn’t even predict bitchute. Suspect
AlwaysTilted_: in what way would you differentiate this search engine from google's?
cankunwang: He said not to work in Google
omar3141: lol wat
solitarynative: vc funded crypto is almost always trash
marzmike: Google will buy you out of you're successful
nozpheratu: Santiago_LHC but it is, no search sngine will ever give you exactly what you need unless you tailor your query a bit, really we just need more tooling to narrow down our searches
l1ght5p33d: another Linux !
itsxaos: it seems like they are being deliberately obtuse about what they do
l1ght5p33d: moarrr linuxxxx
champ900: it sounds like you dislike Google because they're mainstream
doctorgenus: i just scheduled an interview with google. should i withdraw and start my own company?
ryboii1: why is google a failed organization?
logi6000: @doctorgenus this highly depends on your situation
solitarynative: a crypto is only as good as the underlying protocol - doesn't matter how many features you build on top
omar3141: b/c they haven't innovated in like 10 years
hexicity1: how do i start to become as smart as you George
barkazzaz: @georgehotz what are we doing today? ever tried getting into NLP?
l1ght5p33d: what is this
zennydmt: why not work for Google if you are talented?
l1ght5p33d: syntax trees?
Plurmorant: LUL
nozpheratu: doctorgenus You can build you own web crawler easily to act as a search enginge, good luck affording the infrastructure as a startup lol
logi6000: @doctorgenus so what's your startup?
omar3141: @zennydmt b/c that's where you go die
meteorlake: Google is a shitty company
Plurmorant: google's success rate is weak
guapcollector: blind lmao
bankzed: interesting is one way of putting it, he excused nationalism and genocide...
itsxaos: have you looked at their programming language? absolutely insane
thecoder15: @georgehotz teambling is a dumpster fire
elephantpandas: monkaW
zennydmt: I dont like money
zennydmt: I like to learn
elephantpandas: danX FBBlock TheIlluminati
omar3141: but it isn't b/c it's RSUs on publicly traded stock
guapcollector: leetcode harder
WiseSwift: I'm not a whore
slArkBig: money is fake? but my money is tight
zennydmt: what company is best for learning?
ph4tal_: when are you going on Joe rogan
AlwaysTilted_: work at google and write a backdoor in something Kappa
omar3141: if anything the money is less fake than it is at any private company
brittonx2: Cheer100
zennydmt: can an introvert start his own company?
mirceau: true.. the culture
itsxaos: @ph4tal_ hes said its not a good idea because its too big
omar3141: "any fool can learn from his own experience"
champ900: can you explain what is teamblind
astrailz: George "Start your own company" hotz
mirceau: Start up, yes!
hexicity1: how do you keep interested/focused on something you're working on, on the side? I seem to lose focus/motivation on things very quickly
wholesome_pepe: best way to learn is in research writing journals
elephantpandas: justke10Virus
SpaceGhost8: virus memes FeelsGoodMan
mirceau: True
l1ght5p33d: Winggssss
Penguino138: Coffee or yerba mate definitely required tonight
popposbubbolo: That's also the most expensive way to learn
Juankinator: best way to learn is to watch vox videos Kappa
mirceau: My man is back !!!!!
masters8: Correct!
ankitc: how to be better programmer
ahahahaitslit: codons n shit
itsxaos: RNA
barkazzaz: why does Geo say because bea-coss?
ackxhpaez: Are we on to COVID-21 already?
slArkBig: how much does your rent cost
WiseSwift: Hardware Hack Kreygasm
CompestLive: Hello!
cellophane11578: are we going to reverse engineer the covid strains?
mirceau: @slarkbig we don’t talk about money here, it’s rude to ask.
Santiago_LHC: amino acids
xmalware60: big rent
itsxaos: @georgehotz is the markdown public?
martaway: Isnt this lockdown unconstitutional
pz3300: Why you need supplements George, you can afford to eat great?
Jehhred: Isn't vitamin C good for cold?
martaway: You cant arrest ppl that havent done crime...
dzid26: This video explains nicely why zinc can work https://youtu.be/U7F1cnWup9M?t=102
Roundlay: Zinc lozenges seem to be effective https://academic.oup.com/jac/article/20/6/893/692279
Scydra_: @georgehotz and chat, whats the best way to ship out your PC interstate( CA to OREGON)
BernardoFire: "coronavirus party" kkkk
Scydra_: monitor, CPU
cellophane11578: zinc and garlic cannot boost immunity i heard, only balance it out so it doesnt worsen
Roundlay: (Not covid)
martaway: I wish streamers would stop normalizing illegal house arrest
pz3300: Seafood and lamb chops are good for zinc
mirceau: This year is different, because I got a Vitamine D shot from my GE to boost my immune!
theonlymonkas: yoyoyoyyo hello geo!
l1ght5p33d: Similarity measured in infection rate? depends on the Spike to penetrate membrane probably
SolarBerry: another thing to look into is vitamin D, it has been shown to reduce chest infections and the severity
mirceau: The past years I didn’t get a Vit D shot from my GP, and i was getting flu from left to right.
pz3300: Dry your mushrooms in the sun. This increases vit D ten fold and you can store them dry through the winter
martaway: Doent zinc need vitamin k
martaway: How do u increase vitamin D...
Ayyyy420Lmao: dont think the vit d form found in mushrooms is bioactive in humans
pz3300: Sun
cellophane11578: sunlight/supplements
IceStationZebraAssociates: Bro even if you can find the right antibody to make the vaccine, do you know how freaking hard it is to synthesize it?
martaway: Sunlight doesnt create vitamin D
martaway: Your skin does
jimmyadaro: Sup boy
IceStationZebraAssociates: it would be unfeasible to make it in mass quantities
pz3300: It’s the same vitamin d produced on your skin
ahahahaitslit: i don't think zinc itself is an ion?
dzid26: chloroquine
Santiago_LHC: @IceStationZebraAssociates I think he is well, aware.
benchai18: @chat guys, what’s on the left in the terminal? Did he write all that or did he download it but just commenting on it????????
ahahahaitslit: lmao
TheZarkxs: the most disgusting thing about this corona thing, is that it has been in other peoples bodies CrreamAwk
theonlymonkas: it think it is
itsxaos: so the virus itself is RNA and RdRP duplicates RNA?
theonlymonkas: it has some charge
Ayyyy420Lmao: i recall it has an exatra hydroxy or methyl in some place
11plus4thinking: salmon15Hmm go on
hexicity1: how do you keep interested/focused on something you're working on? I seem to lose focus/motivation on things very quickly
ahahahaitslit: but you can only become an ion after gaining or losing electrons no?
pz3300: Uv hits the chemical on your skin and synthesis
ahahahaitslit: pretty rusty on this so idk
Santiago_LHC: @benchai18 https://github.com/geohot/corona
martaway: Yeah but it doesnt work that way on mushrooms
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 I think those are notes
theonlymonkas: positive ions
thecoder15: work on stuff that truly interests you @hexicity1
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz why not use Google scholar?
braininavatt: "keen"
mashafique: @ahahahaitslit yeah an ion is just a charged molecule or atom basically
benchai18: @santiago_lhc @jimmyadaro Thank u!
squiggly_nibba: He's an idiot
TheZarkxs: hey look its orange man
hexicity1: @thecoder15 i feel like what i'm working on, does interest me, or atleast, i long to be interested in it
omar3141: lol chloroquine can't cure stupidity
ahahahaitslit: ah ok
ahahahaitslit: tru
doctorgenus: they use Chloroquine to clean aquarium
martaway: I like how some ppl heard some random chemical and immediately ran to the fish store to down aquarium cleaner
nremind: LUL
mweldo: yep
pz3300: @Marta way google it dude
SpaceGhost8: LUL
mirceau: My dad did his PhD on Chloroquine for Malaria/HIV
TheZarkxs: wut
Vindalis: LUL
guapcollector: Sad story
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
leftyytwo: journalism is a legit field 4Head
coolmacjr: hes the goat fr
11plus4thinking: ??? WHAT
squiggly_nibba: It's a parasite remover for fish
itsxaos: welp bad call there
nozpheratu: kek
memphisFPS: LUL
grey_street: wtf
Vindalis: hahahaha
theonlymonkas: LUL
ackxhpaez: Yeah I'm guessing that fish tank cleaner isn't exactly the same chemical
Santiago_LHC: So... less fishtank cleaner then?
peter35_: journos at it again..
Ayyyy420Lmao: reading cnn lmao
l1ght5p33d: lmfaorofl
Vindalis: fake news CNN
cankunwang: Sad
jimmyadaro: Koi fish??
Coolio1232: why do u prefer to use a mac than windows?
doctorgenus: I think the dosage he took was too high
martaway: Then the media was like “SEE? It desnt work!”
roystang: cnn is trash
entangledbeing: Woah... tonic water x10
benchai18: Whoa. Fucking journo twats
theonlymonkas: so the pill in itself isnt dangerous?
mirceau: @georgehotz Look at Chloroquine as used in countering Malaria and HIV
itsxaos: "The corporate media is the enemy of the people"
Nussinov: never a good idea to self medicate
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: monkaW
ankitc: @hexicity1 i feel the same
theonlymonkas: or its kind of a reaction?
pz3300: People been sun dry mushrooms for millennia. It’s the same chemical that’s on your skin
DrewHintz: what if covid-19 is the way that the simulation admins are reducing our compute costs?
squiggly_nibba: It can also cause blindness
LocoLuka: would this classify as bioinformatics?
superduperepic: @georgehotz what was for dinner?
360Plato: he had a cup
Nussinov: Google Forsythia I heard that helped for a pandemic once Kappa
Santiago_LHC: "I'm not a doctor" is how I start all my sentences this year.
Vindalis: whats in fish tank cleaner? LUL
doctorgenus: he couldn't get a prescription lol
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Will you do some Q&A today as well?
leftyytwo: what kinda drugs to you take
nremind: if it doesn't kill koi, then he must've drank a lot of it
Rydberggg: every dugs has side effect
xmalware60: Pr Raoult
martaway: Then the media blames it on trump that someone drank fish cleaner
hexicity1: @ankitc any luck dealing with it? I really wish i could sit there and work on stuff for hours
KNG_ftw: That's the news we got in Spain too. Someone killed for following Trumps recommendations... So sad the state of journalism
thrashtazs: hes an imbecile
highxsnow_: flakka
TheZarkxs: isntreal
jimmyadaro: isreal
benchai18: So did they mention trump just for drama?? Like why did those cunts mention him
jimmyadaro: lmao
mirceau: Look at Chloroquine as used in countering Malaria and HIV
logi6000: the media is just fucked up
xmalware60: proofs of hydroxycloroquine effects are not clearly identified for the new coronavirus
RODNEYDIESEL: yo bro i got a fart. you got discord? i want you to hear it
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Will you do some Q&A today as well?
Rydberggg: the french is raoult didier
doctorgenus: seems like doctors are guessing
fantadmin: @georgehotz whats the difference between chloroquine and hydroxychloroquine ?
martaway: They keep trying to link chloroquine to trump when other countries started using it WEEKS before trump mentioned it
mirceau: My dad did his PhD on Chloroquine for Malaria
martaway: Its like the media wants to keep this pandemic going
128p_: @RODNEYDIESEL I hacked your pc and heard it, bro it's hella lame.
meteorlake: deep state
pz3300: It’s a virus FFS. Drink plenty fluid and go to bed for a couple days
squiggly_nibba: There's studies sshowing that it works that's why he. mentioned it
Ayyyy420Lmao: vitamin d from mushroms is d2 and not d3 which is the one produced in yhour skin, theres doubts about its biological activity in animals
shivoshifter: @georgehotz are u really believing in coronavirus ? the stats show that a normal flu is way more deadly
cogforkd: hello George!
dunehazard: @georgehotz https://twitter.com/yaletung day by day (1-16) account of symptoms from a doctor in spain
itsxaos: @hexicity1 i struggle with this too. i think its like any other skill: you have to practice it
masters8: "inhibitor"
itsxaos: just try and try again
360Plato: so thats stops the replication right
cogforkd: long time no see
logi6000: @shivoshifter no it's not
dr_set: !uptime
jimmyadaro: Hell yeah, oral
imafungi53: youre talking about harvoni
BubbatheVTOG: BubbatheVTOG subscribed with Twitch Prime.
128p_: looks like a hard to swallow pill
newlastaccount: covid-19 first human transmition found https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L2c9q6zVp-I
martaway: Pz3300 just cause its virus doesnt mean anything. HIV is just a virus. Rabies is just a virus
jimmyadaro: @128p_ lmaaoooo
mashafique: @fantadmin the only difference hta i can see from the moleuclar strucutre is the OH
thrashtazs: did you get a minor in biology?
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Will you do some Q&A today as well?
11plus4thinking: @newlastaccount thats fucking disgusting wtf
ankitc: @hexicity1 i try to reorganize my self and work on something. I lack focus
guapcollector: doesn't lysine do this kind of thing too
IceStationZebraAssociates: yo the virus has RNA which codes to make it's own transcriptase. that's called viral transcriptase
squiggly_nibba: @newlastaccount nah that is cooked
jimmyadaro: @thrashtazs He's good at googling
mashafique: @fantadmin it has the hydroxy group
11plus4thinking: @newlastaccount is that a fucking cat??
crispyvideo: G
shivoshifter: @logi6000 https://www.cdc.gov/flu/about/burden/preliminary-in-season-estimates.htm
RODNEYDIESEL: thrashtazs i got a masters
Vindalis: @georgehotz Hawaii 5-0 star Daniel Dae Kim had this "He explained that his doctor gave him a "drug cocktail", consisted of the antiviral medicine TamiFlu, the antibiotic Azithromycin, a Glycopyrrolate inhaler, and the anti-malarial drug Hydroxychloroquine"
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Will you do some Q&A today as well?
fantadmin: hence the hydroxy but i wonder why it it has similar/diffrent effects @mashafique
masters8: Some are toxic. They get incorporated into human DNA/RNA
martaway: Thats alot of freaking drugs, he musta been on his death bed or something
crispyvideo: Why is every nerd (programmer / rich car maker et) now a biologist all of a sudden?
TheZarkxs: dna sucks, rna for life
jimmyadaro: I just noticed he's using Chromium
RODNEYDIESEL: georgehotz add some pizza grease to the list
jimmyadaro: @crispyvideo We're curious af
Nussinov: @crispyvideo curious
bloodstrive: wait isnt this pt4
entangledbeing: Lol
crispyvideo: Maybe listen to someone who actually knows something? )
mashafique: @fantadmin Functional groups make a difference in how molecules work and how they interact
jimmyadaro: Yes it is
l1ght5p33d: This is high school bio stuff. were on quarantine what else to do
doctorgenus: what are your thoughts on blood transfusion? the people who already recovered has antibodies in their blood
martaway: Why would they give him an antibiotic for a virus?
thecoder15: @georgehotz also has shown to have good effects on patients with MERS resveratrol
Ayyyy420Lmao: dude you can see the purine analog in the molecule wtf
PiroFloydian: adenosine is the sleep chemical I believe
jimmyadaro: @martaway Wtf who did that?
DatGuyToby: the anti biotic has anti inflamatory properties
martaway: Idk somene said they gave azithromycin
jimmyadaro: Wtf LUL
bloodstrive: blood transfisuion sounds interesting
crispyvideo: You’ll read. “Person takes geohot advice and takes xyz” lol
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Will you do some Q&A today as well?
hordead: what is the goal of this project?
sinceretear: what is he building
sinceretear: !project
crispyvideo: Waste time?
jimmyadaro: Rever-engineering coronavirus?
bloodstrive: its just to learn
jimmyadaro: reverse*
128p_: ^
martaway: Play the protein folding game
128p_: I guess that's the idea
doctorgenus: during the spanish flu, blood transfusion was used and 50% of critical patients recovered. Maybe give it to them before they become critical
Mint2bSpiced: zinc can be absorbed by the stomach and intestines and then move to your bloodstream, where it can deactivate some viruses, but new virus production occurs inside each cell in the cytoplasm, and little zinc normally passes through the cellular membrane. Chloroquine and other quinine compounds "punch holes" in the cellular membrane and allow Zn ions to flood through. Once inside the cytoplasm Zn halts viral replication.
pz3300: How can it be up in the air if d-2 is bioavailable or not. How hard is this shit?
cankunwang: I only know doctors from wuhan said Remdesivir is very very useful
jimmyadaro: Spanish flu kll a lot of people lmao
128p_: Btw, does anyone know what is this cool font @georgehotz is using on vim?
iteeo: hi
theonlymonkas: github
jimmyadaro: @128p_ Any sans-serif will do it I think
Ayyyy420Lmao: how strong is the evidence for that zinc theory? sometimes they just throw this around because they can texplain the observed effects and just put together whatever
nammedit: just joined the stream, what is he trying to do?
TheZarkxs: more than 400k infected and 20k dead, the majority elder people. this virus is a joke lads, lets discuss about GoT ending
itsxaos: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ionophore
jimmyadaro: serif*
jimmyadaro: i meant
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Will you do some Q&A today as well?
Mint2bSpiced: Zinc has no effect on the cells without ionization (specifically zinc entering the cell to blocking an RNA that's needed by the virus to replicate).
crispyvideo: Imagine Elon musk did a live stream like this? His dumb ass would break the internet
Nussinov: LUL
Mariosavitch: hello mr hotz
Ayyyy420Lmao: oyve
highxsnow_: lol
Rydberggg: he wants to code what ?
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LULW
pz3300: Funny how Iran is getting it bad but it’s two noisy neighbours are not?
Ayyyy420Lmao: oyvey
guinness84: lmao
jimmyadaro: @crispyvideo At least Twitch lol
meteorlake: LOL
thecoder15: @crispyvideo i doubt that
cankunwang: lol
hordead: LUL
wholesome_pepe: KKomrade
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: WUT
jimmyadaro: wtf who is dat
opus_000: can Elon code ?
bloodstrive: have we figured out of china is giving us all their numbers since thy apperently have 'controlled' it.
TheZarkxs: doctor and rasputin
DecayingSkullz: There should be a way to filter out certain google website genres
jimmyadaro: @opus_000 Sure
wholesome_pepe: LUL
crispyvideo: His followers are worse then covid9
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Will you do some Q&A today as well?
theonlymonkas: Remdesivir
128p_: @jimmyadaro thanks
crispyvideo: The Elon cult is strong
jimmyadaro: @128p_ Np
crispyvideo: And yes he can code
thecoder15: @bloodstrive I don't even think even china knows their own number, they were welding people into apartment buildings
FurikuriYugi: you are awesome!!
pz3300: He dances like a mechanical boiler timer
Nussinov: @crispyvideo are you okay man? LUL
dunehazard: @georgehotz https://twitter.com/yaletung day by day (1-16) account of symptoms from a doctor in spain
Mariosavitch: hello mr hotz
martaway: The warm weather will clear this virus up, my prediction
grenaderaven: which text editor do u use
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Will you do some Q&A today as well?
martaway: Global warming will stop Corona
l1ght5p33d: we want Zinc sims on the GPUs
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: TheIlluminati
theonlymonkas: @martaway NO
bankzed: he uses vim
imafungi53: are u a part time pharmacist geo
DecayingSkullz: @grenaderaven he uses Vim
wholesome_pepe: what is moderna working on? anyone patent troll them yet?
pz3300: No more bat wing soup
theonlymonkas: LUL
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz vietnam
doctorgenus: @georgehotz can I breakdance on your floor?
martaway: We arent seeing exponential spread as predicted. It seems to be winding down
logi6000: @doctorgenus wtf
itsxaos: well chinas history gives reason to doubt them but its certainly plausible
pz3300: Ramping up in spain
nremind: china and korea value personal sacrifice for the public good, the USA... doesn't
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Will you do some Q&A today as well?
martaway: Spain has cold weather rn
thecoder15: @georgehotz zinc, resveratrol, and melatonin have been used in tandem against other sars with good results
almonte550: yey!
Ayyyy420Lmao: parenthesis in multiplication/division lmao
pz3300: It’s because of all that check kissing in italy
almonte550: I was waiting for this!
Krakken_TM: Also note that these numbers also biased on the severe cases.
logi6000: George when did you say we should be at 1 mil yesterday
mirceau: Singapore is now regretting its strong counter measurements.. As they see other countries are giving up on their counter measures to this virus.
cellophane11578: spoiler alert guys,the dead ones will turn into zombies
l1ght5p33d: It's to biased to reporting policy right now
syzo__: yo yo yoo
jimmyadaro: @martaway De qué parte de España eres?
Santiago_LHC: @jimmyadaro Stop spamming the question. He might, he might not.
xmalware60: If the quarantine stops, cases are coming again so ..
entangledbeing: How do testing numbers play into whether the data is trustworthy or not?
jimmyadaro: @Santiago_LHC idgaf
mirceau: The Spanish Flue was how much.. 500K
doctorgenus: @logi6000 in two weeks right?
128p_: @cellophane11578 I had a nightmare this happened, thanks for more nightmare fuel
logi6000: wasn't it 2 weeks
mikenachos: 2 weeks
Plurmorant: 1 mill in a week
DecayingSkullz: you said two weeks for a mil, four weeks for 100 mil from now
logi6000: @doctorgenus what I thought too
ooMariaoo: !uptime
zennydmt: isNYC bad
m00chan: when does lockdown end?
ziggyzergling: Nice layman explanation of the Chloroquine & Zinc paper George just showed: https://youtu.be/U7F1cnWup9M?t=104
almonte550: Before this month ends we will hit a million
martaway: Warm weather is the best immune system boost
almonte550: Mark my words!
nomorequity: George, do you have biology/chemistry background?
128p_: Realistic @almonte550
doctorgenus: @logi6000 in 4 weeks, 100mil
cellophane11578: @128p_ its probably the twd and zombieland u watched =p
TheZarkxs: lets go spain, you can get those 100k infected!
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Will you do some Q&A today as well?
Mariosavitch: this will go away like all of the yearly flus and everyone will forget about it
martaway: If we get warm weather soon (ty global warming) this virus will be history
Plurmorant: let's bet PogChamp
tsAllySparkles: ooh more coronavirus streams
imafungi53: is the impact on the economy worth saving boomers
theonlymonkas: PogChamp
tsAllySparkles: check out keplar.gl
logi6000: @doctorgenus that's when we start getting out a bug out bags ready
Mariosavitch: yes it will
theonlymonkas: V3
mirceau: How much does the incubation play a role in the speed of the enforcement loop?
Ayyyy420Lmao: augur works on browser now? it had some awful executable in the beginig
mirceau: True
tsAllySparkles: spelled that wrong lol https://kepler.gl/
wholesome_pepe: not all ACE2's are the same. there may be polymorphisms involved
jimmyadaro: @mirceau Not much if you're isolated
doctorgenus: @logi6000 that's when @georgehotz says we need the M16s
TheZarkxs: LUL
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz Vietnam is fighting it well
7Locrian7: monkaS
Krakken_TM: facts
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Will you do some Q&A today as well?
brittonx2: definitely
Mariosavitch: 2-weeks of food.. for government collapse..
Fantasma56: monkaS
SpaceGhost8: like 2 weeks of food will help in that case
logi6000: George can't remember did you get to ride on that jetski like Jay z yet
cankunwang: buy guns ?
mirceau: lol
Krakken_TM: but wouldnt help you
Krakken_TM: lmao
dzid26: 0.1% is like 0%
pz3300: Fear of fear mongering
dr_set: Who made that site? Are they scared of percentages?
l1ght5p33d: China is fineee
Krakken_TM: guns n food production
thrashtazs: weapons just cause more of a problem
jimmyadaro: @dzid26 No, it's not
360Plato: one handgun
TheZarkxs: what if we shoot corona? i mean the infected, just like north korea
128p_: Political leaders are showing their real selves on this one...
Plurmorant: guns and a garden are all you need
nozpheratu: Famous last words
mirceau: I hate guns
martaway: Well people have been claiming exponential spread for weeks, we arent seeing it
mikenachos: dzid26 you need a math lesson bud
dunehazard: @georgehotz https://twitter.com/yaletung day by day (1-16) account of symptoms from a doctor in spain
guapcollector: buy bow and arrow
yungdeli_: off topic is fun
l1ght5p33d: look at T=0
hordead: so no partying for the rest of the year?
doctorgenus: I bought tasers, the prices has been going up exponentially
pz3300: Help you steal food
FurikuriYugi: "Come on let's get down with the sickness"
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz Vietnam
mirceau: The Mind is the best Gun
Mariosavitch: bit connnectttttttt
SpaceGhost8: total societal collapse LUL
logi6000: remember the Jay z on jetski
tsAllySparkles: any news on HKG ? there's lots waiting for a harness
ahahahaitslit: listen to the portal eric weinstein
Jewishrambo: I'm worried BibleThump
martaway: Even italy is not exponential spread
thecoder15: @martaway what do the graphs look like to you...?linear
mirceau: Nooooooo
Ayyyy420Lmao: do you cunnypost on /tv/?
jimmyadaro: LUL
LaviBF: Look up the Israeli engineer that tracks infectious diseases
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Will you do some Q&A today as well?
newlastaccount: covid-19 first human transmission found https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L2c9q6zVp-I
Jewishrambo: in worried BibleThump and I'm in Canada
mirceau: no politics or media
tsAllySparkles: ah you good
crispyvideo: If you have no gun and food? And the guy or girl with the gun wants the food? You’re SOL
Hawklite: how long do you think social distancing should be in effect?
crispyvideo: Ergo guns win
ScrubLifeChoseMe: nah smart move
jimmyadaro: <3
imafungi53: is the impact on the economy worth saving the boomers
theonlymonkas: its going to ramp up
PiroFloydian: they're doing good job fighting covid @georgehotz Vietnam is
cutza: what's with the toilet paper shortages?
TheZarkxs: vietnam, 1963, a young charlie sheen confronts a vietcong patrol squad while high on drugs
CompestLive: *No food*
LaviBF: He says once 50% of population is infected Ro drops below 1
Mariosavitch: nothing
Jewishrambo: getting the pneumonia
jimmyadaro: Do you own legal guns??
Krakken_TM: upcoming depression
martaway: Charlie sheen must be scared af
cellophane11578: omg dont click that link above
SparksCx: i am not
guinness84: my dick size
gadean: collapse
dorkmo: worried about my momma
Ayyyy420Lmao: charlie sheen wont get it he has tiger blood
logi6000: Tom hanks
Nussinov: I'm worried that my grandparents will die
ahahahaitslit: healthcare system being overtaxed
meteorlake: my grandparents
Penguino138: Worries about a second resurgence after quarantine
cellophane11578: its not a rick roll but ffs
Pedroso: Economy
roystang: another great depression
s0rrz: that i got fired and i dont know what im gonna do when the lockdown ends
tsAllySparkles: tons of people losing housing
rstk1: economy collapsing
Mariosavitch: dollar collapse and we cant import any food
m00chan: 90% sure I already had the corona
Plurmorant: the end of capitalism PogChamp
Ayyyy420Lmao: im woried I can't tell the bottom of the bear market
bloodstrive: im scard my rolling papers wont be enought for my poop
Hawklite: i'm worried social distancing rules will be prematurely lifted and we won't actually flatten the curve
meteorlake: its a nasty virus either way
martaway: Tom hanks had body aches for a few days, hes fine
nremind: i'm worried that dumbasses will purposefully infect everyone
itsxaos: im worried my elderly relatives will get it
KrauserW: grandma
l1ght5p33d: Too many different linux distros
peter35_: my mom getting sick
pz3300: In the U.K. there giving the police power to arrest people who they suspect have corona
CompestLive: worried about no foods
imafungi53: is the impact on the economy worth saving the boomers
swftdev: I'm worried about the breakdown of our next election >.>
logi6000: Bitcoin price. old people
jimmyadaro: @Plurmorant No way
champ900: I'm worried about the heinekenvirus
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz Vietnam is fighting the virus well
mirceau: WORRIED ABOUT MY GEO
snorting_milk: sup guys!
opus_000: job
Krakken_TM: upcoming depression.
ahahahaitslit: healthcare system getting fucked up
almonte550: I'm worried that we can get reinfected after being infected once
doctorgenus: worry that grandmas are being sacrificed for the dow jones
leftyytwo: i'm worried about lp[l[lpp[lp[lp[[pl
Mariosavitch: im worried about hotz
Penguino138: Worried about when I can smoke my weeds again
gadean: remember Katrina?
fantadmin: worried about restaurants stop delivering
ScrubLifeChoseMe: jesus
chronicle19511951: 134 cases of corona here in Viet Nam
ar2zee: to laid off
cutza: economic collapse
mikenachos: the real threat are the ignorant
martaway: Everyone worried about boomers now
raystriker98: checkout India's shit show by their PM
360Plato: cheap real estate and lower social securiuty costs
dzid26: Social separation for next few years....
jimmyadaro: I'm not worried at all, f*** this planet
mirceau: Worried about my EGO **
tsAllySparkles: all the blue collar jobs are gone lol this is just gonna make the rich richer
theonlymonkas: its going to ramp up after the quarantine
pz3300: Worried about my weed supply
brittonx2: yep!
cellophane11578: ^
Jewishrambo: the high hospitalization rate scares me
TheZarkxs: be honest, are you natty or you taking roids?
logi6000: @pz3300 everyone right now
Br4nnon: Unless it mutates we build immunity?
ahh_me: My roommate doesnt have enough money to pay his rent so now we have to deal with that
edu4594: not worry
memphisFPS: everyone does @pz3300
DecayingSkullz: Would you step on Stewart Little for 18 billion dollars?
edu4594: now worried
edu4594: not worried
icekrieg: will we ever be able to run homebrew on coronavirus firmware?
bankzed: COVID-19 doesn't mutate as fast as the rhinovirus
logi6000: @decayingskullz no
pz3300: I’m smokin solid dude TF
jimmyadaro: @ahh_me F*** that guy
wholesome_pepe: natural selection is scary
SpaceGhost8: you're good until the fall 4Head
theonlymonkas: @DecayingSkullz NO
leftyytwo: have u seen any of the stuff stephen wolfram is streaming
ImJ4Gu4R: where we at
ahahahaitslit: i saw a bit
gabo_sk: LuvPeekR LuvPeekR LuvPeekR
guinness84: worried san diego will shut down the weed dispensaries
benchai18: Desperate people looting and stealing.
martaway: This thing has literally gone viral
TheZarkxs: rhinovirus sounds like a spiderman enemy boss
tsAllySparkles: i was thinking of mapping the virus not based off confirmed cases but rather confirmed deaths per capita
peter35_: worried about the reports of reduced lung function and possible reproductive harm afer recovery
entangledbeing: Not enough ventilators and hospital beds
mirceau: So Incubation of 14 dats
Mint2bSpiced: Seems like it's standard of care we need to improve, but new drugs may not help patients who have advanced symptoms; and, obviously, does not prevent infection. Therefore it may not stop us from imposing the preventative measures (quarantine, travel restrictions, the like) which are causing all the economic catastrophe. Still, seems like it would push a bit of a positive spin on things rather than allowing the economic free-fall we've witnessed.
mirceau: days*
jimmyadaro: Are AIDs more dangerous than COVID??
Jewishrambo: apparently its 1/3rd of hospitalizations require intubation while the others just need oxygen... like wtf
itsxaos: @georgehotz the wikipedia link was on the right side at the first google
dorkmo: uni1 unicornvirus
mikenachos: 7200-8500 bases
C0deCane: some other news article today or yesterday talking about Hanta virus killing some dude in China
Krakken_TM: @jimmyadaro yeah bro
Krakken_TM: lmao
benchai18: I don’t wanna have to grab the shotgun. Fuck that. I don’t wanna put holes in my walls
jimmyadaro: @Krakken_TM U sure?
kuzan8: @georgehotz did u listen about hantavirus in CHina?
ahahahaitslit: the main issues are the economy which is already fucked, as well as the healthcare system being overwhelmed
Krakken_TM: and aids is the fina lstage desease
Krakken_TM: hiv is the virus
icekrieg: when are you releasing corona jailbreak?
thrashtazs: I'm worried about not having sex for a long period of time
theonlymonkas: so for you the quarantine needs to extend until we find a cure?
jimmyadaro: Is HIV more dangerous than COVID??
martaway: Hanta virus.. now u know MSM is getting desperate when they try and mix in a completely unrelated virus
Nussinov: not necessarily complicated. wheat has like 30x as long of a dna sequence to human and is much less complicated
peter35_: worried about the reports of reduced lung function and possible reproductive harm after recovery
ackxhpaez: @thrashtazs you get used to it
tsAllySparkles: @jimmyadaro AIDS is definitely more dangerous but HIV probably isn't simply because it's hard to spread it
bloodstrive: lol
Ayyyy420Lmao: having sex? LUL
jimmyadaro: lmao
jimmyadaro: LUL
Mariosavitch: i can make that happen
TheZarkxs: chad covid vs virgin aids
Penguino138: @georgehotz worries about lasting lung damage even for young people after getting COVID?
bloodstrive: imagine having sex and going to hell LOL
Pedroso: Sex? what is it?
logi6000: @pedroso same
theonlymonkas: LUL
boarderdude4120: whatever happened to that havard biochem professor that was accused of spying for china?
C0deCane: I am worried about what this does to you years from now
jimmyadaro: @Pedroso Some pokemon?
leftyytwo: have u seen any of the stuff stephen wolfram is streaming
joeyskitkat: Hows everybody back home?
martaway: The young ppl that vape 20 hrs a day care about lung function?
pz3300: Dead
Mariosavitch: the dollar is going to collapse
gadean: I'm not scared about the virus but the implications to our economy
l1ght5p33d: duh 90% recovery at worst
Krakken_TM: im actually worried about the virus mutating
itsxaos: fucking DUH dude most people will beat this in a week
thecoder15: @Mariosavitch yup
jimmyadaro: Sup @C0deCane
entangledbeing: Not enough ventilator
esence: long-lasting damage the boogaloo
Ayyyy420Lmao: i only vape bho i care about my lungs
DecayingSkullz: I think it's only for people with underlying health conditions
pz3300: 1/3 of the population has hiv george
Plurmorant: goodbye lungs FeelsGoodMan
cutza: what about internet shutdowns?
Pedroso: @jimmyadaro NICE
martaway: Well, vapings bad for lungs
Ayyyy420Lmao: 99% of the population has latent herpes
Jewishrambo: it's the pneumonia that causes the damage. perhaps research into viral pneumonia
C0deCane: @jimmyadaro not much man hbu
logi6000: @ayyyy420lmao c02 carts da bamb
kwirny: AIDS is far more deadlier, but better treadable
tsAllySparkles: lol 1/3rd, what a ridiculously false statistic
tsAllySparkles: maybe 1/3rd of the population of west africa
jimmyadaro: @C0deCane Everything fine man
gadean: 1/3 has hiv? you sure about that?
Krakken_TM: @kwirny aids isnt treatable
theonlymonkas: the quarantine needs to extend?
jimmyadaro: @Krakken_TM Are u sure?
Mint2bSpiced: Here is what the lungs look like when you are infected and have Pneumonia... https://doi.org/10.1148/radiol.2020200257
Nussinov: I love seeing tables in medical papers Kappa
vicmoney69: @Krakken_TM its treatable its not curable
Krakken_TM: as long as you take the meds its " treatable"
cjbprime: Why prefer COVID to HIV? Seems like HIV has zero mortality risk for you, this has non-zero mortality and maybe 3% chance of putting you in an ICU.
Krakken_TM: so its not rly treatable
doctorgenus: kinda dry no pictures
meteorlake: Even without underlying conditions you will feel like shit... ive heard of healthy people being in there for 10 days thinking they were going to die.
l1ght5p33d: Blood transfusion Bone marrow transplant ::can:: cure HIV
logi6000: George if you got HIV what would you do?
jimmyadaro: @Krakken_TM https://www.bbc.com/news/health-51804454
entangledbeing: Worried about trump telling people to stop quarantining
TheZarkxs: more people die to mosquitos than to corona, joke of a virus #virgincorona #chadmosquito
Krakken_TM: @vicmoney69 oh yeah my bad not a native speaker
pz3300: @tsallysparkles tell that to Dr Peter duesberg. Virologist. How many times you been published in Nature?
martaway: HIV does not have zero mortality risk... and treatment has side effects
jimmyadaro: @TheZarkxs Do you mean dengue?
11plus4thinking: @logi6000 he would just reverse engineer it duh
kwirny: youre right HIV is
Mariosavitch: mental disease travels faster and its more deadlier than corona
bankzed: well, gonna sleep. If things gets worse, you're welcome to stay at my bunker, got food and water for years Kappa
logi6000: @11plus4thinking what is was thinking
ImJ4Gu4R: ImJ4Gu4R subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 1 month streak!
Jewishrambo: 0
128p_: In 2019 we had 700 deaths with Dengue in Brazil and then Corona joins in for a crossover episode... If you guys want to the play the game in hard mode, come to Brazil.
Jewishrambo: a lesion is a deformity I thought
thrashtazs: yeah trump lifting ban on people quarantining is a real threat
nremind: i'm hoping the government resets the healthcare, pharma, and insurance industries through this pandemic
boarderdude4120: whatever happened to that havard biochem professor that was accused of spying for china?
jimmyadaro: Like… 5%?
cankunwang: the only way of fighting the plague is honesty - Camus
Mariosavitch: @thrashtazs no its not. stop fear mongering
jmv_chin: pro googler
doctorgenus: nodules sound like npm modules
pz3300: Yeah, thought so
doctorgenus: lol
TheZarkxs: imagine mike tyson punching your lung
joshperri: Worried about mass hysteria when our gov fails to be effective and people start eating each other.
martaway: He hasnt even lifted it, he just said it would be reevaluated
Jewishrambo: lesion is an anatomical deformity
Mariosavitch: like u?
Mariosavitch: ooo
jimmyadaro: LUL
Nussinov: oooo
128p_: oooooo
mashafique: gottem LUL
jimmyadaro: ooo
jimmyadaro: pro move
128p_: F bro..
jimmyadaro: meth
128p_: oh crap, I just realized we're dissing a mod
jimmyadaro: hell yeah
C0deCane: @georgehotz I heard something today that some Italian doctor claiming that he thinks they had the virus there in November or something. Suggesting that the virus originated in Italy ... I wonder if the Chinese threatened to cut off aid LUL
Krakken_TM: atmosphere gettin clear now
Mint2bSpiced: here you go: https://doi.org/10.1148/radiol.2020200843 here are the long term affects
Eternallightning: That’s a steroid
pz3300: @logi6000 act surprised when his girlfriend tells him?
jimmyadaro: https://www.bbc.com/news/health-51804454
TheZarkxs: this stream can be described as a bunch of words i dont understand, and a good looking kitchen on the background
martaway: Steroids hurts the immune system
theonlymonkas: but does all of this have a positive climate impact?
Mariosavitch: just run a t-remd simulation with genesis
pz3300: All drugs do
Krakken_TM: @theonlymonkas yeah
jimmyadaro: Meth is good
Nussinov: @TheZarkxs it's fun to do your own research while watching
ackxhpaez: Steroids are what doctors give when they have no idea
thrashtazs: @theonlymonkas yes
Krakken_TM: and people are startingg noticing it
logi6000: @pz3300 lmao. this is prob the funniest shit I've seen all day. I needed this. thanks
martaway: No, steroids literally do it, as their primary purpose
pz3300: 👍
s0rrz: there was a pneumonia outbreak in november @C0deCane
ImJ4Gu4R: Meth as covid19 cure? geo found it?
TheZarkxs: why you not taking roids bro?
egb3: Helllo :)
Krakken_TM: there are numerous claims on atmosphere gettin clear now with the cars and airplanes goin temporarily extinct
C0deCane: @georgehotz look into Hantavirus to me it seemed very similar but apparently its only contagious in Africa
imafungi53: did you just look up hypertension lmao
Ayyyy420Lmao: @pz3300 all drugs do what?
jimmyadaro: @ImJ4Gu4R y not
Nussinov: @TheZarkxs find a word you dont understand? look it up and go down the rabbit hole. this guy is used to reading papers, but you could even benefit from reading wikipedia articles
Mariosavitch: i dont
Hawklite: lmao
opus_000: reverse engineer cows from farting methane
faraday_lenz: not me :)
128p_: @TheZarkxs Watching George is a constant battle to keep up, even when he's coding something you're supposed to understand. Don't feel bad :D
esence: im chugging ice-cream rn
C0deCane: @s0rrz he said specially pneumonia like but tested neg for it
SolarBerry: "56% of Travis County COVID-19 patients are younger than 40, HSEM says" monkaS
itsxaos: also women WAY overrepresented
izikatoshka: no infection bacteria game this night? @georgehotz
itsxaos: this study doesnt seem great
entangledbeing: Everyone has diabetes?
pz3300: Africa must be like, thank fook it’s not us for a change
leftyytwo: not enough colorful pictures
jimmyadaro: https://www.bbc.com/news/health-51804454
Mariosavitch: have you looked at T-REMD simulations with genesis? @georgehotz
itsxaos: small sample size
Eternallightning: SARS was much deadlier
Jewishrambo: this study is good..
Eternallightning: But didn’t spread as fast
pz3300: Take no notice george
Nuroki: statistics on 80 different people is at least questionable
logi6000: @pz3300 but when it does hit. it will hit harder then the second sun hit japan
esence: it's a bad study because the authors were not diverse enough
Nussinov: Published in the journal of 🅱️ O N E research
ImJ4Gu4R: Yea, sars hit ya hard
jimmyadaro: @esence lmao
Jewishrambo: look at the doctors names sometimes you can see them again and again trust for them etc
pz3300: Lol
jimmyadaro: https://www.bbc.com/news/health-51804454
Jewishrambo: gain*
egb3: egb3 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
DecayingSkullz: TheIlluminati
TheZarkxs: im just going to believe what orange man says, hes the president, he must know what the f is going on
Mariosavitch: have you looked at T-REMD simulations with genesis? @georgehotz
nremind: basically over 50% had long term effects?
Nussinov: @Jewishrambo hate to say it but my PhD supervisor (a nobel laureate) told me to be more skeptical of articles written by 100% chinese authors LUL racist I know but still
Penguino138: @georgehotz so there are long term effects on the lungs or no?
whyZaya: @Jewishrambo That's not a great practice. Someone can do good research once and bad research later.
s0rrz: longtime smokers will probably be fucked
itsxaos: very hard to say much when theres so few people no?
jimmyadaro: Genesis? Isn't that a console?
Br4nnon: we're testing for antibodies in 'recovered' patients
jimmyadaro: LUL
martaway: Longtime smokers suddenly care about lung function?
Eternallightning: Yeah sega genesis
logi6000: @jimmyadaro S AYYYYY GAHHHH
s0rrz: i mean about dying
almonte550: Because it's expensive?
nremind: I thought it said 21% had some effect and 34% had another effect
entangledbeing: How many strains?
pz3300: I’ve been smoking since 5 years old. My lungs are amazing!
jimmyadaro: Dying sound good
C0deCane: @martaway hell yeah dude how else we gonna keep smokin Kappa
TheZarkxs: damn once i get my treatment for corona im going to look like jeff seid
jimmyadaro: @C0deCane LUL
doctorgenus: yup they are all guesses at this point
l1ght5p33d: evolve or find a cure
jimmyadaro: wtf
Mariosavitch: jeez lol
SpaceGhost8: zombies monkaS
itsxaos: well maybe they are saying there is no data
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: monkaW
jimmyadaro: psychosis??
faraday_lenz: monkaS
Ayyyy420Lmao: why would u use an inmunosupresant ot treat an infection
theonlymonkas: NotLikeThis
SolarBerry: sars 2 is not to be underestimated
Eternallightning: monkaW crazy patient
C0deCane: LUL sars related psychosis LUL literally the state everyone in the globe is in right now
jimmyadaro: https://www.bbc.com/news/health-51804454
TheZarkxs: @martaway stop lungphobia right there, tobacco has the same rights as you do
Mariosavitch: no
Ayyyy420Lmao: no
Lizardan: Yes
Nussinov: god no
wholesome_pepe: because the the symptoms kill people
jmv_chin: medical programmer Kappa
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Scam
Ayyyy420Lmao: just read a book
almonte550: Are we using steroids again?
s0rrz: are we getting sars 3 next year?
kwirny: Possible
theonlymonkas: lul
pz3300: George, the people in my street are having a corona party. Do you think I should go now?
jimmyadaro: @almonte550 Now is meth
logi6000: @s0rrz 3rd gen?
Eternallightning: Yeah go into 200k debt
Mariosavitch: git tag sars-v3
brittonx2: the steroids will f with your mind
faraday_lenz: learned medicine on the streets
polishtoe: Prolly, rn they're prescribing Azithromycin for 'rona pt's
C0deCane: sars v3 will be much more friendly
pz3300: Synthetic blow sucks
jimmyadaro: @Mariosavitch LUL
almonte550: @jimmyadaro f** yeah!
jmv_chin: like the killer bees incident
l1ght5p33d: I already made sars 3. with python 4
guapcollector: steroids will enlarge your organs
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: every two years we get a new one
esence: just toss that bat out in the market
TheZarkxs: imagine spending billions on a vaccine, and the virus suddenly mutates and its worth nothing. hahahaha
TsarSec: Kappa
theonlymonkas: only if we survive this one
jimmyadaro: @guapcollector All of them? Hmmm
benchai18: I love how much he’s touching his mouth while talking about fatal diseases lol
jimmyadaro: https://www.bbc.com/news/health-51804454
Nussinov: I heard bobby gates say that pandemic is the most likely thing to decimate humanity in the next 50 yerss
TsarSec: not if you keep defunding healthcare LUL
Eternallightning: Seems like complacency dips below threshold every 10 yers
pz3300: Who needs sterile tech?
K177: its the first one that hit us hard in the modern world
mirceau: Do you really think so?
K177: last one was the spanish flu that had a huge global impact
entangledbeing: Other ways to prevent pandemics?
itsxaos: thats what a doctor on JRE said
jimmyadaro: Test that shit with f**** prisoners
phyde79: what are the odds a tsunami hits west coast us
benchai18: @itsxaos Correct
Jewishrambo: they sequence the genome in January... it's been known for awhile
Eternallightning: Yeah small molecules are much harder
pz3300: Pedophiles
s0rrz: dont leave home @entangledbeing
thrashtazs: @jimmyadaro go to hell
jimmyadaro: @pz3300 Hell yeah
TheZarkxs: test it with people who like vegetables
genieyou1: Look my Twitter genieyou
Nussinov: @jimmyadaro yep, go to hell
jimmyadaro: @thrashtazs Ladies first
TsarSec: bruh @jimmyadaro
pz3300: Maximum dose
faraday_lenz: h1n1
Mariosavitch: i think i had it
mirceau: Simple Vaccs Strategy: counter filth with filth.
Nussinov: I got swine flu
esence: Chinese virus is at 20k
nozpheratu: that was only 11 years ago
K177: lmao
4zimut: lvl 1
benchai18: Making it is fairly simple. Human testing is iffy. We have more regulations than most countries. Makes us “safer” but way slower to react. Far less agile than, say, China
TheZarkxs: nuttin
logi6000: now George with all your research on vaccine. how do I convince my antivaxx friend to understand that they are not bad
tsAllySparkles: are you ever going to revive your rap career
K177: yup nothing compared to this
SolarBerry: swine flu was much less severe morbidity
Mariosavitch: i had it
bankzed: my buddy had swine flu, he said it was the worst sickness he ever had
itsxaos: thats in the margin of error lol
jimmyadaro: Any human being > Pedophiles
polishtoe: avian flu was 60% fatality right?
Jewishrambo: coronavirus is much deadlier . it's more consolidated to the lungs
C0deCane: When Trump stops holding rallys its time to seriously find somewhere safe LUL
Ayyyy420Lmao: again man with the parenthesis wtf
TsarSec: i assume youve seen the bill gates vid that predicts this from 2014 @georgehotz
Br4nnon: imagine 800m infected with coven-19
Penguino138: @georgehotz doesn't the page say 150k fatalities?
Nussinov: @bankzed it was fucking awful for me. projectile vomitting for days lying in bed as a healthy young adult
jimmyadaro: Any human being
K177: LUL
wholesome_pepe: im reading moderna patents right now, seems hard af
mirceau: In India, in some village, they got group of people and they were asked to drink cow piss. to help increase their immune
genieyou1: I’m a hacker, passionate about medicine you’re going to call me crazy, but I think that 50 drops of grapefruit seed extract, and 20 drops of propolis and an infusion of cypress per day can neutralize the CoranaVirus. I suggest the researchers look into it.
theonlymonkas: 18,907 deaths by coronavirus
gill_bates_macrosoft: @polishto problem is how fast coved-19 infects
ahahahaitslit: what are corona's numbers so far?
benchai18: @mirceau Chill bro. I was in that village
almonte550: So dying with that flu is like winning the lottery of bad luck?
jimmyadaro: LUL
gill_bates_macrosoft: hospitals in my city just closed down today, patient care infrastructure in my country about to get rekt fam
pz3300: Spanish flu 30 million
Jewishrambo: coronavirus might top Spanish flu then
ahahahaitslit: spanish flu still the goat
imafungi53: bill gates owns the patent for cornavirus
ImJ4Gu4R: @mirceau PogChamp
mirceau: @benchai18 lol I was serious
zennydmt: what sparks your creativity
C0deCane: to bad our infrastructure is shit and we dont have enough supplies we would'nt even have flinched at choosing herd immunity
zennydmt: how do you become creative
Mariosavitch: nothing
ImJ4Gu4R: @georgehotz more stream after this pls..i will sub more
mirceau: Strategy = Counter Filth with Filth
jimmyadaro: We need more drugs
doctorgenus: @genieyou1 : based on what?
benchai18: @mirceau Me too dude. I have utters now
ImJ4Gu4R: this stream is a cure
Eternallightning: Drugs are expensive and take a long time
pz3300: In the 80s the surgeon general in the us said aids was caused by smoking weed!
TheZarkxs: smallpox kileld 300 million people in the 20th century, corona is a joke
esence: I think Italy are misreporting numbers. One got shot, burned, hanged, drown, stabbed. Cause of death: hanged.
AbdoFarwan: More people die from diabetes 😹
Mint2bSpiced: Doctors prescribed steroids because they thought it would help with inflammation but with COVID-19 the inflammation is from Cytokine release syndrome (CRS)
martaway: Is it true if u leave ur home u can be arrested
Nussinov: so youre saying that your confidence in the number increases as more cases are said to have been confirmed? seems reasonable
dzid26: 0.45-1.2 million died this year from influenza, which is kinda crazy
mirceau: I bought a Leopold topre this week. It types like really nice
pz3300: Cancer has a 100% kill ratio
TsarSec: just let the free market handle it LUL
C0deCane: typical gov agency
logi6000: @pz3300 not always
Eternallightning: They fucked up the primers LUL
Ayyyy420Lmao: @pz3300 i get cancer 1000 times a day on the internetz and still hasnt killed me
pz3300: If you last 5 years they say they cured you
benchai18: @mirceau that’s crazy though. But also not surprising. In Salem, they used to have a suspected witch pee on a loaf of bread and feed it to a dog to see if the dog spazzed out. Given that Indians revere cows, it’s not that strange
itsxaos: whats a PCR assay
Plurmorant: yup
TheZarkxs: USA USA USA!
genieyou1: you are going to call me crazy, but I think that 50 drops of grapefruit seed extract, and 20 drops of propolis and an infusion of cypress per day can neutralize the CoranaVirus. I suggest the researchers look into it.
mirceau: Ugh.. I just think we have such a vague and distant and meta idea of what so many things are. For instance consider what amour actual concept is of Cancer or the Flu or the Financial System..
eksdee_1_2_3: may I have some coochie?
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: MURICA NUMBA 1
SolarBerry: assuming china's fake numbers yes
peter35_: exceptional monkaS
Eternallightning: @itsxaos DNA/RNA replication
Nussinov: @itsxaos its a way to check for the genetic material in the sample. its something they teach undergrads
l1ght5p33d: One fuck up doesn't mean everythings fucked up all the time
miiiiiiim: doesnt china just have quietly higher stats than theyre letting on
jimmyadaro: https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1242519973903376384
itsxaos: oh theyre talking about the tests?
phyde79: Tsunami warning for Hawaii and possibly California. You guys see this?
nremind: we have people on extended spring break partying
pz3300: China has 5x what you do
C0deCane: @georgehotz do you think some countries will seek punishment for China?
guapcollector: seems like the US is about to go back to work too
theonlymonkas: so the solution is? more quarantine?
martaway: X doubt
nozpheratu: Why wasn't it called the Asian Flu?
pz3300: Bat wing soup
theonlymonkas: bat flu
jimmyadaro: @theonlymonkas So far, yes
mirceau: My dad’s jewish PhD supervisor took my dads Research results, moved to the USA and patented them.
martaway: We dont havev nearly the density Italy does
miiiiiiim: @theonlymonkas until theres enough PPE for civilians
Mariosavitch: ywn
Mariosavitch: yawn
jimmyadaro: https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1242519973903376384
TheZarkxs: who cares, usa usa usa!
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Trueeeeeee
SolarBerry: @mirceau lol
C0deCane: @guapcollector they won't the governors probably wont let that happen even if trump says its ok
Ayyyy420Lmao: @mirceau woa woa cool it with the antisemitic remarks Kappa
TsarSec: capitalism
Eternallightning: Science research is full of snakes @mirceau
isensualism: KEKW
mirceau: Lol My mom’s side was Jewish, I have a free pass
rstk1: LMAO
isensualism: turn on KEKW BOOMER @georgehotz
C4TFive: 2032 baby
thecoder15: @georgehotz you actually trust a bunch of clowns to get a big bad virus under control lol
cankunwang: conspiracy is stupid
Penguino138: Hotz 2032 lets gooo
l1ght5p33d: open source everything fuck the government
mirceau: @eternallightning true
Ayyyy420Lmao: @mirceau if your mom is jewish you are jewish too
miiiiiiim: @l1ght5p33d want a lollipop?
guapcollector: every state should secede lol
Mariosavitch: Corporate Socialism
logi6000: I think George could start his own party
TheZarkxs: ancaps rise up
Hawklite: do a political conversation with destiny
logi6000: open source party
julien9877: prediction: US #1 cases in 3 days
murkythunder: destiny is an idiot
Ayyyy420Lmao: u read hans herman hoppe george?
isensualism: talk to @destiny @georgehotz
pz3300: Destiny is a coke fiend
martaway: Density is too big for his britches
mashafique: George please take your groceries off the floor. The five second rule has long passed monkaS
thecoder15: they should all go the way of Ceaușescu @georgehotz
itsxaos: destiny is a joke
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: @Hawklite LUL
TsarSec: destiny is a neolib dumbas
jimmyadaro: Coke, hell yeah
gabo_sk: destiny is a videogame
SlaterUSA: but we all agree the libertarians should be the first to be fed to the guillotines, right?
thrashtazs: rationality is the only separation we have from animals, yet we cant
mirceau: rationality is an inefficient way to go about life
murkythunder: destiny is legit a redditor who cant pass college who reads headlines and debates people
cellophane11578: destiny IS a video game Kappa
jimmyadaro: @SlaterUSA wtf
guapcollector: you're using your guillotine wrong slater
gill_bates_macrosoft: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
iGalactic: Jebaitedd me by saying you weren’t streaming tonight 🥴
pz3300: Yeah but destiny uses to enhance his debating
SpaceGhost8: oh yeah, the spike in florida
mirceau: The right process doesn’t mean the right output
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Florida
martaway: Density just takes what other people have done and takes the next step. He didnt do the work himself so he takes no responsibilty for it
SlaterUSA: libertarians, quickly followed by conservatives
roystang: the test i got in FL takes 1 week to get results
TheZarkxs: @SlaterUSA nice bait right there
miiiiiiim: two weeks before we get to watch christians go and celebrate easter like the death cult they are
julien9877: cdc. gov link in there
mirceau: @mashafique lol good one
Eternallightning: Reverse transcriptase is buggy
SlaterUSA: @TheZarkxs :D
SlaterUSA: okok
Itsmeek0: It seems to take about two weeks for people to recover from it. So if everyone that is infected becomes quarantined... perhaps it can kind of go away in two weeks ish?
jimmyadaro: @SlaterUSA Like… Kill the people who builds that country?
C0deCane: @georgehotz if the death tolls continue to skyrocket all over the world can we assume that China is lying?
martaway: Well yeah all enzymes are buggy thats why we have cancer
pz3300: Destiny has an incest fetish
braininavatt: I love it that george googles like my grandma Kappa
mirceau: Reversed Transcription is Dank
jimmyadaro: @SlaterUSA I mean, leftists are doing nothing
jimmyadaro: to improve the country
jimmyadaro: LUL
miiiiiiim: why does anyone listen to destiny
Eternallightning: 5Head
murkythunder: putting a pedo with a league addiction who cant pass college who left his son for an egirl on the same level as hotz is a joke
SlaterUSA: @jimmyadaro and everyone else is just fucking it up :D
11plus4thinking: LUL
Mint2bSpiced: here you go https://www.fda.gov/media/134922/download
almonte550: The thing with that test is that the accuracy is like 60-70%
jmv_chin: that vim Kreygasm
jimmyadaro: SeemsGood
pz3300: Lazy pricks
mirceau: Leopold vs HHKB
tsAllySparkles: did you hit 1m2019.com
dingus74: loool
braininavatt: Kappa
aaaakshat: SeemsGood
Itsmeek0: @braininavatt how do you google?...
Santiago_LHC: Buy me two
pz3300: Brown switches are nice george
mirceau: 😂
11plus4thinking: PRESS IT FeelsGoodMan
cellophane11578: lol
TheZarkxs: how do i buy coronavirus
Eternallightning: What protein does E gene make? @georgehotz
11plus4thinking: LUL
jimmyadaro: LUL
mirceau: you can sell anything online.
almonte550: Antibodies testing will do better accuracy
TsarSec: LUL
theonlymonkas: LUL
cellophane11578: english text, nah bruh just copy and paste a jpeg
doctorgenus: does CTFs make you smarter?
dingus74: Bruh
Nussinov: Pepega
cankunwang: lol
mashafique: LUL
Kemisdan: LUL
Jewishrambo: is uber eats safe during this time does it live on food or something
alameda13: LUL
dingus74: jackoo1Derp
gabo_sk: monkaS
martaway: Antibodies testing is not more accurate. People who have recovered will still have antibodies
theonlymonkas: PogChamp
thecoder15: @Jewishrambo throw the whole thing in the microwave to kill it off@
jimmyadaro: LUL
tsAllySparkles: most tests go up your nose like flu tests
pz3300: Antibodies are good.
tsAllySparkles: not sure about the lab analysis though
cankunwang: so liberal
pz3300: Once you have antibodies it’s job done
SlaterUSA: aw, thanks chinese! so nice!
mirceau: PEOPLE BUY ANYTHING - My grandad ordered a ‘barbecue starter kit’ and he got a box of matches.
timi13462: how many tabs do you have open daily
jimmyadaro: @mirceau LUL
tsAllySparkles: the cartridge is fed into an ePlex machine, where the sample undergoes around 20 different chemical reactions to test for the virus.
gill_bates_macrosoft: @mirceau LUL LUL LUL LUL
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
dingus74: LMFAO
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: TRUEEEEEW
SparksCx: lul
Itsmeek0: lollll
dingus74: LUL
Itsmeek0: nice example
K177: lmao
Itsmeek0: comedy gold
64pillars: but it works
itsxaos: and then they lie about what they will do in the future
martaway: Antibody testing is cheaper and faster but not more accurate
pz3300: Did you google that sparkle. Or ya scared?
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: WOKE USA COMPANIES LULW
Santiago_LHC: Hey, I donated Balloons man
SparksCx: good one georgey
bytebacon: "How does the internet know when I was born, a generation formed by internet porn"
cankunwang: goooood
TheZarkxs: im a clown and do it for free, 24 hours a day 7 days a week
ImJ4Gu4R: lol yea damn balloons donation
Itsmeek0: #balloongiftersattacked
almonte550: @martaway for what I read there are two types of antibodies, one that appear when it's the first time with the virus and one that appears when your body gets infected again
11plus4thinking: HEY dont underestimate a good balloon
Santiago_LHC: The balloons are no joke, man. Donate balloons if you can #balloons
iGalactic: peepoClown
jimmyadaro: wtf
entangledbeing: Shootin straight
pz3300: You love it georgehotz
mirceau: @georgehotz I worked in Kuala Lumpur for 1 year. My Chinese boss was boasting everyday that they are better and more sophisticated than the Malays and the Indians.
lebop: what is he doing today?
martaway: Not sure about that, the first antibodies would still wor
jimmyadaro: @lebop Cure COVID
SlaterUSA: they just do it for the lulz
mirceau: Loved Kuala Lumpur so much.. those were some good times
benchai18: @slaterusa Lol
pz3300: They do it for the sales
Ayyyy420Lmao: hookers lul
Mint2bSpiced: click me ---->>>> https://www.fda.gov/media/134922/download they have a flow chart for how the test works
Sky_Light_37: Kappa
brofessorbob: Bar girls?
Br4nnon: don't they all
Santiago_LHC: #capitalism
sunole: 400,000 new people have joined Folding@Home’s fight against COVID-19 The quest to thwart the virus has strong help from distributed computing. Jon Fingas Jon Fingas, 03.23.20 The Folding@Home community has turned its attention toward the fight against COVID-19, and it now has massive computational power at its disposal as a result. The distributed comp
jimmyadaro: Capitalism is everything that's fine on tis world
Fosade: what up george
Ensthor: #capitalism
theonlymonkas: SeemsGood
zennydmt: are u ever going to get married
thecoder15: @georgehotz my man malaysian girls are fun -
weedlord666: I mean i guess but those large companies are extracting wealth via the exploitation of the surrounding population and environment, often for extreme gain
mirceau: @georgehotz True,
ImJ4Gu4R: Nah, come Kuala Lumpur? lets hangout geo
pz3300: Do they suck dick?
joeyskitkat: hows everyone back home George?
jimmyadaro: @weedlord666 Do you work for pennies?
mirceau: I felt so free at KL
whyZaya: Geohot goes on so many dates. Is he even a real programmer?
dingus74: woahhh
zwisch: #sequenceTheWorld
itsxaos: Theranos 2 PogChamp
thecoder15: @georgehotz check this out
Santiago_LHC: Man.... that's how Jurassic Park started.
theonlymonkas: LUL
Sky_Light_37: monkaS
jmv_chin: what you drinkin
logi6000: offtopic: I loved your song sufficiently advanced democracy is indistinguishable from trolling
bytebacon: Yo, yo I didn't always have skills, But you chilled out with the time that you killed, I was online and on my damn grind, Beggin' the question, What'd you do with your time? Figured it out in my Aunt's basement, Video games and no damn patience, Tech skills and determination, Crossed with the rage and frustration
braininavatt: #NotAScamTheranos
jimmyadaro: Yeah, f*** blood
dingus74: Harvesting Dna
Itsmeek0: Give us your best baritone voice George
jmv_chin: yum
Itsmeek0: CNN interview
thecoder15: @georgehotz check this out https://nanoporetech.com/products/minion
Eternallightning: It was never a scam Kappa
ImJ4Gu4R: Come KL bro
pz3300: Death penalty for an oz of weed. No thanks Kawala lumpher
Ayyyy420Lmao: whats the point of sequencing everything tho
guapcollector: high on coffee
benchai18: WHATS MY MOTHA FUCKIN NAME. R. U. L. E.
Santiago_LHC: Doctor Ian Malcolm warned about the abuse of DNA sequencing
brofessorbob: Did you ever hang with Elizabeth holmes when you were in the bay?
64pillars: xqcM Theranos 🤝 Facebook
imafungi53: do you cut your own hair rn
theonlymonkas: no tea?
SpaceGhost8: how do I invest
mirceau: Ice Tea
entangledbeing: Intellia
PiroFloydian: how we doing boiz
entangledbeing: Invitae
zeeeman: you haven't moved your bags from yesterday
ImJ4Gu4R: Thats nice geo
logi6000: apartment tour
wholesome_pepe: they do that tho. all those genome projects
joeyskitkat: are they whole food bags?
jimmyadaro: I said it yesterday; eat raw garlic, onions and drink some tea mf
itsxaos: its "book a sales call" much LUL
Br4nnon: oh sht lol
brofessorbob: Did you ever hang with Elizabeth Holmes during your time in the bay?
KnollBoss: @georgehotz uve introduced me to my favorite tech quote of all time from holmes. Great announcement video
itsxaos: go back up the table had prices
SpaceGhost8: check on amazon
nremind: it said $1000
murkythunder: no price = $565464565476
zeeeman: CH
cankunwang: oxford
64pillars: scroll up lol
nozpheratu: If they don't tell you the price, it's too expensive for me
jimmyadaro: No price = expensive af
jimmyadaro: I said it yesterday; eat raw garlic, onions and drink some tea mf
KnollBoss: talk to sales
guapcollector: they probably sell in volume
jmv_chin: find out more LUL
almonte550: Talk to sales hahahahahaha
grenaderaven: lol
thuganalyst: Iran is rejecting humanitarian aid even though their death toll is 2000 growin fast
jmv_chin: who designed this website
murkythunder: live sales call Poh
KnollBoss: book a sales call
SpaceGhost8: Book a sales call LUL
nozpheratu: talk to sales = > 5000
entangledbeing: Invitae / intellia
julien9877: just 4Head
C0deCane: LUL we have this product its just impossible to buy
Ayyyy420Lmao: 1000bucks reagents
Santiago_LHC: CALL
jimmyadaro: @thuganalyst Who's help?
ooMariaoo: oh
SparksCx: sales call
pz3300: When they don’t say the price you know it’s gunna cost brewsters
iGalactic: Pog
SpaceGhost8: oh, that's not bad
benchai18: @thuganalyst Good. Fuck em
theonlymonkas: only $1000
almonte550: Talk to sales => your left eye
moncefmd: if you sequence everything you are trespassing the privacy of your ancesters as well as your kids
zwisch: PogChamp
jimmyadaro: I said it yesterday; eat raw garlic, onions and drink some tea mf
jmv_chin: impulse purchases live on stream; high-quality
leftyytwo: scam,,
C0deCane: Just the starter pack? at least get the advanced version LUL
nremind: but what is the practical use?
mirceau: @georgehotz you were in the Golden Triangle of KL. between KLCC, Bukit Bintang and Raja Chulan
SpaceGhost8: have to sign up for their SAAS product with basic
Ayyyy420Lmao: not doing a genome on that if thats what ur thinking
logi6000: George over here looking for the scam lmao
SparksCx: BUY ON STREAM PogChamp
Eternallightning: Is there continuous costs for reagents
itsxaos: you need special cartridges
Vespus: Doesn't include DLC
Santiago_LHC: A month later. George clones himself
almonte550: You need to sell your left eye to purchase it
Itsmeek0: Scam is... it only analyzes jizz
Itsmeek0: lol
murkythunder: dna sequencing as a service
KnollBoss: it costs half of your sexual lifetime
anotherkidnamedaustin: how long have y been on?
pz3300: You will be targeted by drop shippers too fuck george
itsxaos: https://store.nanoporetech.com/eu/flowcells.html/
benchai18: What is that? Gene sequencing? Dna?
sk84uhlivin: It seems there's supplementary packages, a lot of them...
guapcollector: price is monthly
theonlymonkas: let's find out! buy it!
jimmyadaro: I said it yesterday; eat raw garlic, onions and drink some tea mf
ImJ4Gu4R: Can we do this tool open source geo?
anotherkidnamedaustin: day 4 same hoodie?
thuganalyst: @jimmyadaro doctors without borders
brofessorbob: First you need to isolate the organism before you sequence
TheZarkxs: cybervirus
PiroFloydian: no i just have a good immune system i dont get sick
wholesome_pepe: is it one time use??
DecayingSkullz: But it
DecayingSkullz: Buy it
miiiiiiim: @georgehotz do you still have your tonsils
Ayyyy420Lmao: you're not getting enough reads with that shit
Br4nnon: green tea & honey
pz3300: George is turning into Howard hughes
ImJ4Gu4R: I want to see this as open source, lets break it.
jimmyadaro: @thuganalyst Who??
thuganalyst: Those planes Iran shot down really shook my city
brofessorbob: Go to the Dr.
SparksCx: what...maybe just go to the doctor
cankunwang: can you do whole genome sequencing in this?
SlaterUSA: scam is, when u get the product there's just a bunch of soldered metal bits from a broken clothes iron inside
jmv_chin: click the glowing Find OUt More buitton
logi6000: George boutta reverse engineer his self made virus
SpaceGhost8: yeah, buy one and open source it
METH_HEAD_MIKE: home chlamydia test PogChamp
ooMariaoo: true is it one time use
itsxaos: @georgehotz i think you need to buy these consumables https://store.nanoporetech.com/eu/flowcells/spoton-flow-cell-mk-i-r9-4.html
Ayyyy420Lmao: @cankunwang nope, maybe with a lot of runs you could
benchai18: My balls hurt. I’d like to sequence that nut
mirceau: Ask Theranos’s CEO Elizabeth Holmes
jimmyadaro: EAT F**** GARLIC GEORGE, IS NOT THAT HARD
Br4nnon: how does it work
Itsmeek0: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rXfS4wJoVLQ
almonte550: REAL real-time
theonlymonkas: what tea do you drink?
Itsmeek0: this is a video on the dfevice
almonte550: So real
anotherkidnamedaustin: dna extraction is easy peasy
bytebacon: @georgehotz can you just rap before every stream? it's 🔥
benchai18: How does it work and why do u know how to use it @georgehotz
murkythunder: imagine spending 20 years of your life and millions of dollars to make some ingenious tool, and some idiot buys it, reproduces it in a 3d printer, and open sources it
SparksCx: REAL Real-time PogChamp
jimmyadaro: Raw onions
DecayingSkullz: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rXfS4wJoVLQ
Ayyyy420Lmao: yeah george the tech of this is crazy, a weird patented membrane and electrodes measuring the conductance
pz3300: Camel tongue virus I bet it is g
ImJ4Gu4R: Buy and break it geo
zwisch: any length DNA/RNA
mirceau: How is this not a scam like Theranos
Mariosavitch: 10k LUL
thuganalyst: @jimmyadaro https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Médecins_Sans_Frontières
Itsmeek0: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rXfS4wJoVLQ
chillguy269: holy christ
Kemisdan: 10k wtf
anotherkidnamedaustin: @murkythunder imagine waiting 18years of ur life and voting for donald
jimmyadaro: @thuganalyst Oh, those bastards…
Mariosavitch: little?
Eternallightning: DNA purification is kinds expensive pretty sure
anotherkidnamedaustin: so this scam is the price]
theonlymonkas: LUL little
SpaceGhost8: it's always the printer cartridges
Ayyyy420Lmao: yeah but so much better than previous tech, the reads are crazy long
PiroFloydian: this seems like Theranos tbh
cellophane11578: lets create the 5th element dna, the one that bruce willis was protecting in that movie
cellophane11578: Kappa
360Plato: ahh microfluidics
Mariosavitch: once
almonte550: once
Mariosavitch: twice
Nuroki: 6 times it says
Br4nnon: is it expensive to make yourself? granted you knew how to
jimmyadaro: 100 Gb??
Nuroki: 6 reactions
theonlymonkas: you need that too to make it work
ooMariaoo: 6
Mint2bSpiced: the problem with chip based product is the bioaccumulation overtime leading to chip replacement
Itsmeek0: maybe thats why it says talk to sales
jmv_chin: :)
Itsmeek0: so they can explain
mirceau: Ok boys, i am off to sleep it is like 5:13 AM here. #StayStrong BisexualPride
theonlymonkas: LUL just buy it
SparksCx: wait really?
jimmyadaro: @mirceau Kisses
guapcollector: looks like a vape lol
brofessorbob: 30Gbs
itsxaos: i think its not complete per run
SpaceGhost8: giblets of data
wholesome_pepe: you need reagents too or they come with the kit?
jimmyadaro: I said it yesterday; eat raw garlic, onions and drink some tea mf
doctorgenus: call them up and trade them an EON for a MinION
dingus74: Lol
C0deCane: @georgehotz research it on a different site LUL
pz3300: Shop around george TF
Mariosavitch: if u wanna die
tsAllySparkles: what are you gonna throw away in exchange for this device? didn't you throw away a waffle iron on stream?
Waldoqq: YES
ImJ4Gu4R: buy and break it
Br4nnon: lol that'd be hilarious
cellophane11578: thats what i wanna do
ooMariaoo: ouu
theonlymonkas: yes
jimmyadaro: Raw onions mf
anotherkidnamedaustin: @mirceau u made it this far why leave
SparksCx: geebes
itsxaos: i think you need to sample each thing multiple times
botbotboot: you need 10k to all this
murkythunder: Kreygasm gibi
meteorlake: TheIlluminati
pz3300: NSA in the chat
Ayyyy420Lmao: dont jerk off on stream pls
TheZarkxs: god i hate asmr
Santiago_LHC: ASMR
Mariosavitch: danHmm
jimmyadaro: @Ayyyy420Lmao That would be epic
11plus4thinking: isn't she a pornstar???
KnollBoss: goddamn she ugly
CompestLive: lol
syzo__: why
cellophane11578: i want to create drones that flash UV at random peoples faces too
jimmyadaro: LUL
logi6000: yeah like that one guy said trade a eon for a minion
theonlymonkas: Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm Kreygasm
11plus4thinking: isn't she a pornstar??? isn't she a pornstar??? isn't she a pornstar???
Nussinov: very relaxing
julien9877: Kappa
Santiago_LHC: #tingles
itsxaos: whats the S stand for again
murkythunder: girlfriend puts you to sleep Kreygasm
ackxhpaez: creepy
wholesome_pepe: scammazed LUL
Mariosavitch: your face says sexual
K177: Kappa
roystang: its not sexual i just get a boner
miiiiiiim: um ok dude
imafungi53: geo getting a half chubb
iGalactic: WutFace
SparksCx: WutFace
NagyOut: why does she have 2 different colour hairs?
almonte550: Are we going to see people eating again?
dingus74: jackoo1Weird jackoo1Weird jackoo1Weird
C4TFive: Woah there bud, you need to be on Just Chatting for this
360Plato: yes mass produce this shit with microfluidic circuits btw IM rock hard IM sorruy
pz3300: Suck my balls
anotherkidnamedaustin: id get corona to hear her fart asmr
Penguino138: The only ASMR I like are you coding streams please stop
TsarSec: wtf is this
SpaceGhost8: charge some rich valley tech bros for expedited testing
brofessorbob: Do you ASMR regularly
Santiago_LHC: I want to give her money
meteorlake: lol what a turn of events
rahfuls: are u into tapping or what homie
TheZarkxs: turn it off or i burn your kitchen
TheLastMrX: WutFace
l1ght5p33d: I havn't had sex in like 3 years
TsarSec: why are we listening to ads
Nussinov: its sexual for losers who never talked to a girl in real life before LUL
Ayyyy420Lmao: how much money do u have donated to her???
jeffery_fan: I think ASMR IS banned on twitch? @georgehotz
cankunwang: pronhub skip ads
ImJ4Gu4R: NotLikeThis
SolarBerry: remember iDoser lol
ooMariaoo: lol
SparksCx: #ad
Mariosavitch: ASMR ad
anotherkidnamedaustin: i like her farts for asmr
Br4nnon: *deeply inhales* LUL
TsarSec: lmfao i remember that @SolarBerry
iGalactic: Listen to rain instead SeemsGood
nremind: wow those guys are simps
dudvdx: he's about 2 streams away from crispr
Nussinov: youtube comments are ultimate cringe LUL
guapcollector: asmr simps are the worst of all
jimmyadaro: Ads are getting smarter
SpaceGhost8: this isn't even good asmr
benchai18: @georgehotz my shaft disagrees with u
pz3300: It’s like she’s whispering in my ears “ you want me to suck your dick”
ackxhpaez: You could just listen to NPR
izikatoshka: ASMR Kreygasm
TheLastMrX: that was creepy
almonte550: If she starts eating I swear to god
Mint2bSpiced: you still nee a thermo cycler https://youtu.be/iS1pz3IhJvU?t=173
h_may_chess: the sibilants
iGalactic: Simps WutFace
codelumberjack: any crowdsourced reviews for these devices?
Mint2bSpiced: *need
jimmyadaro: @pz3300 Cherry Crush does that
h_may_chess: ssss zzzz thhhh
theonlymonkas: buy the minion
anotherkidnamedaustin: SCAM
HexaField: Simps galore
murkythunder: "asMr iSnT SeXuAl" meanwhile no dude asmr artists with million views
doctorgenus: buy it buy it!
Bloodswordz88: hail brethren
joeyskitkat: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rXfS4wJoVLQ
brofessorbob: starter pack flow cells are dope!
ooMariaoo: loll
SpaceGhost8: exactly
doctorgenus: it's like the giraffe for the EON
tsAllySparkles: yeah you can reset the DRM chips
theonlymonkas: minion minion minion minion
tsAllySparkles: on printers
360Plato: microflidic programming is so good
jimmyadaro: Onions, George
C0deCane: check out the reviews LUL
DecayingSkullz: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rXfS4wJoVLQ
zwisch: nanopore sequencing is apparently legit
cellophane11578: whats a flowcell? i know theres stems
Itsmeek0: GEORGE
pz3300: With the hot breath in your ear?
Itsmeek0: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rXfS4wJoVLQ
HexaField: can we get a TLDR of the last 3 streams?
murkythunder: when you make a proprietary tool and hotz starts looking at it monkaS
syzo__: the ADD is real
MrTriharder: @georgehotz @chat good morning from India admiralF1 admiralF2
brofessorbob: check amazon for reviews
tsAllySparkles: don't get auto-reset chips but you can def reset the DRM chips to say that the ink is full
Mint2bSpiced: you will still need a thermo cycler to prep the device https://youtu.be/iS1pz3IhJvU?t=173
cankunwang: minions movie review
SpaceGhost8: check amazon reviews
jimmyadaro: @HexaField Check his GitHub account
ooMariaoo: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rXfS4wJoVLQ this vid lol
HexaField: true, thanks
theonlymonkas: buy some minions
benchai18: DRM on a cartridge????
jimmyadaro: @HexaField https://github.com/geohot/corona
benchai18: What?
jimmyadaro: There u go
doctorgenus: I wouldn't be surprise if their next product is GRU
Nussinov: @Mint2bSpiced the camera man focuses on her tits the whole time LUL fucking creep
tsAllySparkles: for inkjet printers mostly @benchai18
Ayyyy420Lmao: man theres a protein pumping the dna through a pore in a membrane and electrodes measure the conductance and through this they know what base is passing through
brofessorbob: ligands
Br4nnon: @georgehotz watch that vid in chat
jimmyadaro: @Ayyyy420Lmao Can I put my dick in there?
Ayyyy420Lmao: @sure if it's only 1nm wide :^DDD
pz3300: Are you ever gunna get back to me on that @tsallysparkles,or not?
logi6000: wait a minute. George can't be a programmer. he's gone on a date!
omar3141: signing off.. late on the east coast. have a good night all
omar3141: and keep hacking away
AresRai: @jimmyadaro nano dick detected
jimmyadaro: @Ayyyy420Lmao Hmmm
botbotboot: it works on small scale electricity
benchai18: @tsallysparkles DRM on an inkjet printer? Am I getting wooosh’d rn?
DecayingSkullz: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rXfS4wJoVLQ
logi6000: @omar3141 I'm on east coast too
Nussinov: there are a few different strategies
brofessorbob: Any bros from San Diego?
tsAllySparkles: @pz3300 what?
jimmyadaro: @AresRai Do you prefer bigger dicks?
logi6000: @brofessorbob George it
logi6000: is
thecoder15: @brofessorbob yeah but i leave tomorrow
wholesome_pepe: nanoporetech.com/how-it-works
tsAllySparkles: yeah DRM
thecoder15: @brofessorbob you go to the hackathon?
tsAllySparkles: like
AresRai: @jimmyadaro gachiHYPER ofc
zwisch: you can sequence your entire genome for $100 in China
pz3300: Dr Peter duesberg sucks I’m that hiv is a harmless virus carried by 1/3 of the population
Nussinov: zwisch it must be cheaper
tsAllySparkles: you can only buy cartridges made by the original manufacturer of most lower-end printers
pz3300: Says
Bloodswordz88: it all leads back to China?
tsAllySparkles: but you can hack the drm chips
jimmyadaro: @AresRai Sorry, i didnt mean to waste your time LUL
Ayyyy420Lmao: i got mine sequenced for 400 eur in europe
brofessorbob: @thecoder15 nah, I'm from here.
tsAllySparkles: 23andme $200
tsAllySparkles: that plus promethease (genetic analysis tool)
doctorgenus: damnnn @georgehotz does this much research before buying? Wonder if people do that before they buy the EON as well
tsAllySparkles: it's pretty cool
joeyskitkat: yes watch this video about MinION https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rXfS4wJoVLQ
HexaField: 23andeveryonetheysellyourdatato
MrTriharder: New virus found in China monkaS infects people who eat rodents monkaGIGA
tsAllySparkles: https://in4.us/Gb <-- my genes
brofessorbob: @thecoder15 How was the hackathon. Who was hosting?
jimmyadaro: https://github.com/geohot/corona
pz3300: 23and me is bullshit
tsAllySparkles: yeah they do]
botbotboot: it doesn't always work
tsAllySparkles: just a set
HexaField: imagine doxing your own dna
thecoder15: commaAI hosted it lol @brofessorbob
tsAllySparkles: not everything but the data they get is pretty decent
jimmyadaro: @pz3300 No is not, i've worked with them
tsAllySparkles: much better than what's on their website
ahahahaitslit: lmfaoooo
Ayyyy420Lmao: why would u kill cereal?
jimmyadaro: LUL
Kemisdan: LUL
4zimut: 300 IQ
Mariosavitch: only a serial killer would think about that
imafungi53: hahaah
PiroFloydian: also then they literally own your DNA
ackxhpaez: that's thinking ahead
astrailz: LUL
jmv_chin: big brain
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Trueeeee
vicmoney69: monkaS
imafungi53: genius
jmv_chin: big brain play
mburke005: ya fair
cellophane11578: cereal is inferior to ricecakes
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: 5Head
pjayys77: yup my reasoning too.. wait..
jimmyadaro: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
cellophane11578: duh
pz3300: @jimmyandro. They work on a 50% accuracy rate
theonlymonkas: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
SolarBerry: implying the CIA doesn't already have your DNA
Mariosavitch: 10/10 Serial Killer
brofessorbob: w00t!
Itsmeek0: have you been finger printed by the police?
jmv_chin: can u open ur freezer
jmv_chin: xd
brofessorbob: I have
codelumberjack: what do you think about taking DNA sample from citizens at birth?
zeus13i: @georgehotz - when will this reverse engineering be done? :) days? weeks?
benchai18: I ain’t giving any of those fcking agencies my dna. They can come get it outta my mouth like any respectable woman
KnollBoss: looking at an approved paper in Nature. Is this an ad?
nozpheratu: Couldn't a serial killer easily frame other people by putting their DNA on their victims?
Itsmeek0: my finger prints are in the system as well ;(
Nussinov: illumina is the coolest
jimmyadaro: @zeus13i Months, he said that yesterday
pz3300: I could guess your lineage as accurately as 23andme by looking at you
logi6000: if George becomes a serial killer and someone finds out. they are just going to blackmail him for eons
entangledbeing: Finally
entangledbeing: Illumina
murkythunder: tfw u get paid more than the ppl who make this tool putting buttons on sites
cankunwang: nanopore focus on 3rd gene sequencing, long reads sequencing
benchai18: @pz3300 SAME!!! That’s why the attorneys never choose me at jury duty. Cuz they know I can do that too just by looking at people
MrTriharder: @logi6000 I’d blackmail for stocks and bitcoins
guapcollector: turn that kitchen to a clean room
imafungi53: your fridge door is slightly open!
Nussinov: yuuup
Sky_Light_37: again LUL
swftdev: right?
jimmyadaro: Wow
theonlymonkas: lol
brofessorbob: Fake Lab Again???
joeyskitkat: yeah
jimmyadaro: ResidentSleeper
logi6000: @mrtriharder true
iGalactic: The lab is fake? 🥺
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Again??? LULW
Nussinov: I still think you need a small amount of amplification, no?
swftdev: lul not again, last time it was a whole ordeal.
nomad119: Why do all of these biotech companies require 6 or 7 clicks to buy something jeez
zeus13i: @jimmyadaro - thanks! so comma is on hold?
jimmyadaro: @iGalactic Which one?
almonte550: Let's build another fake lab!
brofessorbob: Geo have you been to Hong Kong?
theonlymonkas: just buy it already ResidentSleeper
Itsmeek0: THE SIDE DOOR IS OPENING
KnollBoss: list shkreli's jail cell as the lab u work from
Itsmeek0: lol
jimmyadaro: @zeus13i Idk, he may have some other people working on that
tsAllySparkles: 4 degrees C would be above freezing lol
ahahahaitslit: is skhreli still in jail?
Itsmeek0: ^ yes
fukurowlz: @Nazhika
jimmyadaro: @zeus13i Keep in mind is 21:23 SF Time
jmv_chin: trolled
Ayyyy420Lmao: ahahahhaa
Kemisdan: LUL
ahahahaitslit: damn
DefinitlyNotXanbot: KEKW
faraday_lenz: LUL
jmv_chin: Xd
Sky_Light_37: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rXfS4wJoVLQ
C0deCane: LUL
cjbprime: lol
vicmoney69: LUL
DecayingSkullz: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rXfS4wJoVLQ
knilecrack: :D
Zameso: LUL
AresRai: LUL
DefinitlyNotXanbot: LUL
Incurs0: LUL
Nussinov: guarenteed geohotz will forget his ice buckets when doing his first experiments
opus_000: lul
brofessorbob: This guy fucks
ackxhpaez: I thought we live in a simulation
SpaceGhost8: lmao
Mariosavitch: ITS REALY
jimmyadaro: LUL
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
PiroFloydian: LUL
astrailz: LUL
aMANT3: KEKW
Penguino138: NOOOO
Mariosavitch: ITS REAL
logi6000: lol
aaaakshat: LUL
AresRai: Future is here
Nussinov: LUL
NagyOut: LUL
TheZarkxs: just watch joe rogan
C4TFive: THIS IS THE FUTURE
guapcollector: all those asmr recs
outlier2: LUL
Nussinov: FUTURE IS NOW
NagyOut: thats a rick roll right there
vicmoney69: put it between brackets
theonlymonkas: LUL
b0ngwizard420: LUL LUL LUL
MrDrSpace: FUTURE
iGalactic: LUL
theonlymonkas: buy some minions
brofessorbob: HeyGuys HeyGuys
Flipc01n: Lol
vicmoney69: put it between quotes to get it case sensitive*
aMANT3: unboxing
nozpheratu: That wasn't slowly
brofessorbob: StinkyCheese
guapcollector: slowly at 2x
braininavatt: george's into asmr Kappa
C4TFive: @Mint2bSpiced you were in 2120 with that link LUL
itsxaos: http://nextgenseek.com/2018/01/illumina-launches-iseq-100-for-20k-at-jpm-2018/
fukurowlz: @Nazhika
nomad119: RGB lets go
SpaceGhost8: just plug it in via usb
nomad119: it has to be good
jimmyadaro: LUL
pz3300: George’s search history is exotic to say the least
itsxaos: so the illumina thing runs you 20k looks like
cjbprime: it's got flashing lights I guess it must be legit
benchai18: I’m stupid
Mint2bSpiced: @C4TFive LUL good to see you
mburke005: Kreygasm
TheZarkxs: nice boobs
brofessorbob: boob
Nussinov: Kreygasm
Ayyyy420Lmao: im gonna cooom
guapcollector: why no rgb on the minION
theonlymonkas: Kreygasm
Nussinov: there are machines for that
faraday_lenz: we dont need to hear
murkythunder: my bio lab was a virtual lab on secondlife state uni is shit
SlaterUSA: george likes to pet the pies
NagyOut: side boob i s always good boob
nomad119: Those pipettes do all of the work
jimmyadaro: Kreygasm
brofessorbob: Hire hot lab chick to pipet for you.
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Kreygasm
highxsnow_: james charles
Nussinov: they have machines for that: theyre called undergrads Kappa
Zameso: pipetting is super relaxing
pz3300: Pip -et George TF
Lizardan: Relax you all. pornhub premium is 100% free
SpaceGhost8: we bout to build a full on lab
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: COOMER
benchai18: @pz3300 Lmao
o______________________k: bio community aren't good at video quality loool
nomad119: just use sous vide
cankunwang: fking graduate students
TheZarkxs: Kreygasm
PiroFloydian: Church & college in 1 Kappa
logi6000: at this point just set up a lab. in your new church of course
brofessorbob: ebay thermocycler
itsxaos: george there is a youtube channel that does this sort of stuff on the cheap, its called the thought emporium
Bloodswordz88: Georgehotz will become peter parker
ackxhpaez: nice puppies
botbotboot: there are
Nussinov: there is
cankunwang: coronaman
botbotboot: robots ones
zeus13i: those machines exist but they are wildly expensive
Br4nnon: it's like manually grinding coffee
kellyIake: there’s used lab equipment websites with transparent pricing like labdepotinc.com
bytebacon: @itsxaos thought emporium is really cool
murkythunder: get a thermo cycler on alibaba for 50% of ebay Pog
Mariosavitch: lol
SpaceGhost8: PogChamp
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
jimmyadaro: LUL
Mariosavitch: comma.bio
AresRai: PogChamp
botbotboot: you should
SpaceGhost8: DO IT
Nussinov: LUL
AresRai: BIO AI
fukurowlz: Pog
julien9877: tax writeoff Pog
Ayyyy420Lmao: just rename to coronaAI
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
SpaceGhost8: open source bio PogChamp
pjayys77: yes
Santiago_LHC: CommaDNA
theonlymonkas: JUST DO IT
joshperri: Call it coma ai
logi6000: @mariosavitch beatmetoit
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogChamp
ak0ya_: DO IT!
thecoder15: ghost virus for the masses @georgehotz
pz3300: George
botbotboot: i already bought it
ak0ya_: so much fun
TheZarkxs: put some socks on ffs
AresRai: HYPERS LET DO IT
Br4nnon: bio.comma.ai Kreygasm
guapcollector: enter.ai
Mariosavitch: no
ackxhpaez: Half of chat is going to try to buy that domain
jimmyadaro: We're alone boys, let's snort some coke mffffff
MrTriharder: PogChamp yes
sunole: 400,000 new people have joined Folding@Home’s fight against COVID-19 The quest to thwart the virus has strong help from distributed computing. Jon Fingas Jon Fingas, 03.23.20 The Folding@Home community has turned its attention toward the fight against COVID-19, and it now has massive computational power at its disposal as a result. The distributed comp
almonte550: fake lab on the way
iGalactic: Lol
Santiago_LHC: COKE
o______________________k: comma.bio
Lizardan: I'll go buy it and will sell it back to him Kappa
theonlymonkas: hands
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PJSugar PJSugar
jimmyadaro: PogChamp
codelumberjack: lol
mineyful: loud ass flush
whyZaya: I bought it. Kappa
Nussinov: biomma
benchai18: @santiago_lhc Shhhhhh
wholesome_pepe: if u scale up im sure ge life science has some tech for pipetting
zwisch: CommaBio: Taking driver monitoring to the extreme
AresRai: strong flush
fukurowlz: wash your hands
jimmyadaro: LUL
aMANT3: FLUSHHHH
4zimut: damn squatters
Joshh185: Is he okay
iGalactic: Don’t forget to not wash your hands
ahahahaitslit: adderall shot
theonlymonkas: HANDS
fukurowlz: nice job
elephantpandas: super glue them onto a back massager
OlympusDev: It's $74.88/yr if you want to buy it lol
mineyful: THAT WASN"T LONG ENOUGH TO WASH
pjayys77: mm 20 seconds?
dzid26: Hydroxychloroquine Dashcam
jimmyadaro: WASH YOUR HANDS
Lizardan: comma.bio is available PogChamp
Santiago_LHC: Those were NOT 20 seconds!
theonlymonkas: SwiftRage 20 sec!
whyZaya: HE ONLY WASHED HIS HANDS FOR FOUR SECONDS.
zeus13i: @georgehotz I would work at your bio division ... PS: outsourcing some of this might be useful? eg. https://www.cloudlab.us
PiroFloydian: coma ai or corona ai?
inciMage: new epidemic called Hantavirus from china
superduperepic: superduperepic subscribed at Tier 1.
Santiago_LHC: TWENTY
doctorgenus: bio division for comma.ai, clone people to drive cars for you
lefse: i dont have corona virus, i dont need to was my hands SMOrc
benchai18: And now he’s gonna put his fingers in his mouth ‼️
jimmyadaro: WASH YOUR HANDS!
Mariosavitch: looks can be deceiving
jimmyadaro: gosh george
TheZarkxs: ez science ez life
fukurowlz: a poor hand's wash and you pretend to open commabio?
jimmyadaro: that's fck upd
fukurowlz: Kappa
Nussinov: concepts are easy but getting things to work is hard Kappa
aMANT3: YOU NOT GONNA EAT THAT
logi6000: what is backspace exactly.
jimmyadaro: WASH YOUR HANDS
pjayys77: yea.. really easy
Sky_Light_37: imagine having a bio divison named comma, not good man, not good
jimmyadaro: WASH YOUR HANDS!!!!!!
HexaField: bio division for comma.ai, clone people to drive cars for you
whyZaya: @georgehotz Wash your hands for 20 seconds.
brofessorbob: BioBrosAI
imafungi53: bio is applied math
Santiago_LHC: 20 seconds hand washing! You'll die!
fukurowlz: nasty
syzo__: excited for backspace.ai though BibleThump
jimmyadaro: no u didnt
sunole: Froze?
jimmyadaro: no way
iGalactic: Chat 🤦🏼♂️
Lizardan: Bio is a lot of memorizing unlike match which is a lot of reasoning
pz3300: Every day your NSA jacket is getting bigger. I’m starting to get worried about listening to you george because if they can get to you, they can get to me, and I can’t let that happen.
mineyful: wash them again
jimmyadaro: that was too quick
Br4nnon: tangerines > oranges
Nussinov: Kappa
logi6000: what is backspace tho
theonlymonkas: BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump BibleThump
tsAllySparkles: someone subscribed
vicmoney69: Kappa
braininavatt: tomorrow: "George Hotz says creating a COVID19 vaccine is easy"
pjayys77: uh I counted 15 seconds of washing
whyZaya: @georgehotz Four seconds is not long enough.
benchai18: Is that a blue bell
Mariosavitch: cheater
wholesome_pepe: hire pharma bro martin shkreli as CFO
brofessorbob: What tricks did you pul?
thrashtazs: are you worried about your company during this time
lefse: i wont was my hands until there is military poiting m16's at me
guapcollector: backspace is like canonical form for code right
cybergenik: me
jimmyadaro: WASH YOUR HANDS AGAIN
Mariosavitch: me
cybergenik: me /
TheZarkxs: not me
Lizardan: not me
Irdi18: Not me
AresRai: not me
cellophane11578: me
kwirny: bruh
devm0d: I'd pay $100
SpaceGhost8: if it was repeatable, me
brofessorbob: A lot
alameda13: not me
imafungi53: i dont think so
tsAllySparkles: i'd barely pay a grand for a comma 2
11plus4thinking: not me
HexaField: make it 100 and you're a rich man
Combat__ex: One of my best friends died of pneumonia symptoms. Not sure if coronavirus :( :( :(
Nussinov: I probably would LUL fuck it
theonlymonkas: not me LUL
brofessorbob: We all think we have it in SD
iGalactic: Nope
jimmyadaro: WASH YOUR HANDS
ak0ya_: not me
murkythunder: id rather get $1000 and corona than get the test
360Plato: that will get you alabelled a terorist
Mariosavitch: i have a test.. stay in door
Zameso: @georgehotz (just entered the stream) can you briefly explain what your working on at the moment pls ?
codelumberjack: now the serial killer bit makes more sense
ImJ4Gu4R: anyone herd about hantavirus? someone get infected
logi6000: how much can you get a thc test for. that much
cankunwang: testing is cheap, the problem is trump
tsAllySparkles: oh it'd be dope to have it at home
syns0r: franchise it
julien9877: @georgehotz add online signup and youre good
botbotboot: you need astronaut suits ahahah
jimmyadaro: 1k would be CHEAP
doctorgenus: or bio comma.ai can get self walking people. They don't need to think about walking from point A to B and think about other things
ImJ4Gu4R: its not new but got new case in china
swftdev: only if I can 3d print with it
inciMage: @ImJ4Gu4R i did
ziggyzergling: Problem is swab material is running low...
brofessorbob: we all have corona in SD
pz3300: I’ll test your weed for ya
TheZarkxs: nah, its much more fun if i dont know
jimmyadaro: "old"…
benchai18: @imj4gu4r Yup. We’re getting played like a fiddle out here in the statea
guapcollector: put the test in every mcdonalds drive thru
jimmyadaro: "30"…
wholesome_pepe: new york will buy them all right now
Mariosavitch: ..........
SpaceGhost8: monkaS
Irdi18: FBI
PiroFloydian: considering 40% of people cant afford a $400 emergency, probs not a lot @georgehotz
ahahahaitslit: is backspace ai donezo?
zwisch: monkaS
vicmoney69: monkaS
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: monkaW
logi6000: what were you like as a kid
SpaceGhost8: FBI, this guy here monkaS
devm0d: What if you could do more than just covid-19, you could test yourself for whatever sequence you download, similar to 3d printers
11plus4thinking: monkaS
jimmyadaro: WASH YOUR HANDS
zennydmt: do you feel different physically at 30 vs ur 20s?
iGalactic: Lol
Nussinov: yeah wake up in the morning, grab a coffee, butter your toast and stab yourself in the nose with a corona kit
itsxaos: good choice
elephantpandas: when did you monkaW
Mariosavitch: uh yeah
logi6000: time to find it
pjayys77: yea when I went to College I looked if there was a serial killer Major
ImJ4Gu4R: @inciMage yeah.. its on every news header
logi6000: out
benchai18: @georgehotz DID U WATCH LEX FRIEDMANS CORONA VIDEO?!???????
vicmoney69: you can still do it just dont wash your hands 5Head
pz3300: Why did you kill animals
theonlymonkas: it's never too late
Mariosavitch: who would be your first
imafungi53: whats so good about it
brofessorbob: SDSU
Lizardan: You do look like a serial killer
adamalex16: bruh the fuck is this stream
octeezy: Nah, its only you
Ayyyy420Lmao: you still want to become one you just need a bit of twitch chat support to go trhough
mashafique: monkaS
SpaceGhost8: lex friedman PogChamp
theonlymonkas: it's better late than never
cankunwang: 47
jimmyadaro: Lex <3
pjayys77: its true he's outting us all out
elephantpandas: amiloFeels FBBlock justke10Virus
inciMage: @ImJ4Gu4R where are you from its just on socil media where i live
brofessorbob: blowhard
mashafique: Lex PogChamp
Nussinov: who is this joker LUL
HexaField: that is so lex lol
julien9877: Lex PogChamp
rickoftheroot: I found you through his podcast PogChamp
iGalactic: LOL
adamalex16: mac
TheZarkxs: "existencial"
adamalex16: gross
ImJ4Gu4R: @inciMage Malaysia
theonlymonkas: WutFace
pz3300: Lex the robot
Mariosavitch: why
ShredderSherlock: 5 paragraph essay
jmv_chin: LUL
Incurs0: Lex PogChamp
PiroFloydian: who is this dude?
adamalex16: imagine using apple
murkythunder: lex fridman vids ResidentSleeper
adamalex16: fucking grosss
adamalex16: apple nastyyy
hypertextlabs: please
Nussinov: LUL
jimmyadaro: LU
theonlymonkas: ResidentSleeper ResidentSleeper ResidentSleeper
Lizardan: LEx is boring to watch
cankunwang: pllzzzzz
jimmyadaro: LUL
HexaField: flex freeman
ahahahaitslit: lex fridman hotz part 2
benchai18: @georgehotz you’re welcome
PiroFloydian: who is lex?
C4TFive: Lex is the best
brofessorbob: MAGA
logi6000: after this stream I'm boutta watch it too
Lizardan: Watch Eric Weinstein insteasd
opus_000: you should get on Eric Weinsteins podcast
Nussinov: give me hilary^2 before this one
doctorgenus: what do you think about lex? he interviewed you
nremind: he's russian though
jimmyadaro: @PiroFloydian Some other god
devm0d: you ever make with that chick that works with you?
mashafique: You gotta do another interview with Lex.
bytebacon: DOES LEX CODE?
SpaceGhost8: Lex would run this country like a machine, and we'd all be better off for it
itsxaos: LEX MADE A PODCAST WITH THE SOLE PURPOSE OF ASKING PEOPLE FOR AI GFs
elephantpandas: but they want a business man LUL
Zameso: @georgehotz (just entered the stream) can you briefly explain what your working on at the moment pls ?
benchai18: Yes he codes
ahahahaitslit: listen to the portal ffs
HexaField: go on Eric Weinstein's the Portal bro!
ahahahaitslit: by eric
jimmyadaro: @bytebacon Kinda
Lizardan: @georgehotz Benjamin Goerrzel
ahahahaitslit: thank fukc
brofessorbob: Not Donald Trump?
zennydmt: is lex friedman a polymath?
Hawklite: start a philosophy branch of comma ai
HexaField: It's Stein like Einstein
murkythunder: lex fridman isnt hype like trump ResidentSleeper
pz3300: Lex is a KGB robot
doctorgenus: and then read the new one punch man episode
zennydmt: would you consider urself a polymath?
pz3300: Eric is a blowhard
guapcollector: peter thiel sounded pretty unhinged on that portal pod
zennydmt: do u like ben shapiro?
Mariosavitch: plz
ahahahaitslit: lmfao
ShredderSherlock: are you a math guy or a bio guy or what?
hypertextlabs: haha
vicmoney69: 5Head
itsxaos: voteYay
TrippinFlare: LUL
rickoftheroot: LUL
Incurs0: LUL
Irdi18: LUL
TsarSec: thats some authoritarian shit LUL
jimmyadaro: LUL
vicmoney69: LUL
itsxaos: voteYea
Combat__ex: @georgehotz Do you think R is better for bioinformatics?
Abnico: Harvey Weinstein has a good podcast also
theonlymonkas: LUL
inciMage: @ImJ4Gu4R youre close to china maybe thats why new news widespread im on turkey only social media news are spread
brofessorbob: DBZ?
joshperri: Stop getting sidetracked
mashafique: You should watch Steins;Gate @georgehotz
itsxaos: VoteYea
nremind: the government is currently trying to ban encryption LUL
benchai18: @abnico Hahahahahaha
devm0d: LUL
SpaceGhost8: LUL
bytebacon: Joe Rogan 2020
zennydmt: Ben Shapiro?
pjayys77: what are the chances Yang knows how to code
Mariosavitch: authoritarian serial killer
Nussinov: print("But Her Emails")
jimmyadaro: @zennydmt Hell nah
zennydmt: Would you go on the joe rogan show?
elephantpandas: danX yes
pz3300: Eric will infect your mind george don’t let him
itsxaos: @georgehotz Lex wasnt born in US sadly
Lizardan: @zennydmt he said he wont
logi6000: @nremind EARN IT ACT GEORGE YOU NEED TO LOOK INTO THIS
benchai18: @zennydmt No. I offered to get him on JRE and he didn’t wanna
syzo__: trump is a poorly trained Markov anyway
devm0d: Mother Russia
zennydmt: @Lizardan thx
Mariosavitch: russia russia russia
ImJ4Gu4R: @inciMage yea maybe, the news here just add some more panic here.
Combat__ex: Edward Snowden for President Kappa
cankunwang: next putin
theonlymonkas: PUTIN
zennydmt: @benchai18 thx
pz3300: He was born in a factory
devm0d: So what comma hacks apply to bio?
bytebacon: What about Naval yo
SOmedude456: George when was the last time you opened IDA?
pepelaugh0: @georgehotz would you do Rogan now that you’re part time at comma?
eaterenrgy: @syzo__ What does that mean?
jimmyadaro: Lex
brofessorbob: Have you met Putin before?
Ayyyy420Lmao: there's no next putin he will clone himself
guapcollector: putin writes fortran
TsarSec: LUL
timi13462: what computer do you use
theonlymonkas: you resemble to putin
zennydmt: do you know anything about bayesian statistics
TsarSec: eugenics
Bloodswordz88: HahaThisisfine
octeezy: How is coding helpful for a politician?
vicmoney69: 5Head
joeyskitkat: WHY ARE THE FKING GROCERY BAGS OUTSIDE
Mariosavitch: thats the test?
imafungi53: thats too basic
theonlymonkas: P V A L U E S
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz Bernies good there
elephantpandas: if you are not putin you are tootin lirikHAPPY
pjayys77: Well Bernard is your guy
SOmedude456: @georgehotz when was the last time you opened IDA?
PiroFloydian: i would think
brofessorbob: Pootin in yo face
murkythunder: can they google their way to a stack overflow article answering their question
astrailz: Listening to experts would be a start
jimmyadaro: Stop consuming plastic
SolarBerry: putin is pretty based tbh
TsarSec: im pretty sure theres a name for that
Mariosavitch: experts.. lol @astrailz
vicmoney69: thats actually not a bad idea tho
timi13462: what computer do you use
zennydmt: Do you think Bill Gates would be a good president
logi6000: look up the earn it act
jimmyadaro: IT'S OK
kwirny: Its adorable
architectzs: what’s up geo what’s y#ur number one tip for learning to code?
brofessorbob: Pootin spell is better than Putin
knilecrack: putin is king
hypertextlabs: drink water
elephantpandas: wut lirikS
aMANT3: TOS
itsxaos: we still havent cured corona BibleThump
Lizardan: TRUE
pjayys77: uh oh *thinking about offending ppl
Mariosavitch: pootin
rickoftheroot: monkaS
mashafique: monkaS
doctorgenus: is that lipton tea?
echobrother: what do you think abou the deep state making the crona virus in a lab
Nussinov: monkaS
pz3300: You started it
TsarSec: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Technocracy @georgehotz
Waldoqq: tyler1Yikes Politics
Combat__ex: Merkel has a degree in quantum chemistry Kappa
o______________________k: monkaS
jimmyadaro: LUL
SolarBerry: riot in chat
imafungi53: did we cure corona yet
jimmyadaro: Nah man
Ayyyy420Lmao: have you read stuff by hans herman hoppe?
aMANT3: TOS TOS
Nuroki: one more word about mr. Putin and we shall deploy forces on u KKomrade
devm0d: when you gonna have some emotes on your channel? I got shit to unlock
aMANT3: BANNED
rickoftheroot: LUL
elephantpandas: justke10Gun
benchai18: @pepelaugh0 Dude I asked him just a few months if he wants to be on JRE and he said no. Said he doesn’t want the attention. Had nothing to do with comma
SOmedude456: inb4 george gets assassinated
bytebacon: PUTIN WILL SEND ELITE HACKERS AT YOU
logi6000: it's about banning encryption
AresRai: @Combat__ex thats true so why the Kappa x)
doctorgenus: is the coronavirus impacting your company? Is everyone working from home more productive?!
Nussinov: blessed is our lord and savior vladimir putin
vicmoney69: the govenmnent wants to ban encryption
knilecrack: he was in KGB
cellophane11578: 16 yrs
isalhi: Any good recs for a python task que that’s not celery?
vicmoney69: yeah he was
devm0d: Putin ROSE TO THE TOP bro
Incurs0: LUL
jimmyadaro: Yep
TsarSec: yeah he was / is KGB LUL
devm0d: Put in the work
o______________________k: Hassanabi vs got what a stream
Abnico: Congress anounced they are all going on the same tmobile plan to save money
elephantpandas: lirikS so he knows what you just said
jimmyadaro: Nothing wrong thertr
vicmoney69: he knows kung fu
dudvdx: how do you get sodium into cells!?
logi6000: earn it is about banning encryption
highxsnow_: puti mad
benchai18: Obv.
pz3300: He was the head
architectzs: what’s up geo what’s y#ur number one tip for learning to code?
AresRai: KGB taught them to code
SolarBerry: thuggin' around the berlin wall
benchai18: Putout
Nuroki: He is going down guys, RIP Hotz xxx-2020
brofessorbob: Pooootin was in the KGB.
guapcollector: onION
elephantpandas: quick maff lirikHAPPY
chucknorrisbeard12: KGB became FSB
C0deCane: LUL I always picture putin riding a horse with no shirt because of that meme ahaha
pepelaugh0: @benchai18 I wish he did. I remember him mentioning he doesn’t want the attention but I thought that was because of comma but might not be right
Mariosavitch: lol
opus_000: Putin looks like a thug tho
jmv_chin: LMFAO
jimmyadaro: lmaaaao
theonlymonkas: SCAM
jimmyadaro: LUL
braininavatt: HahaThink
cankunwang: Scam from NIH
echobrother: what do you think about the coronavirus was created by the deep state in a lab in china
Nussinov: I did the same thing when buying cheese this morning, am I the same as this hacker
TsarSec: added value Pog
jimmyadaro: quick maths
vicmoney69: scam
devm0d: What if Comma comes out with a DUI mode that you have to blow into to start the car AAAND sequences your data??
guapcollector: onION is only available on darkweb
C0deCane: do the 50, 000 and its a tax write of for comma LUL
Bloodswordz88: gofundme brother
julien9877: RND COSTS THO
Zameso: 5 bucks ducktape LUL
doctorgenus: use the comma trust fund to fund the bio department
theonlymonkas: LUL great math
architectzs: what’s up geo what’s y#ur number one tip for learning to code?
thecoder15: @georgehotz loss leader my
l1ght5p33d: Duct tape will work for sure
brofessorbob: Comma DUI?
AresRai: @C0deCane what taxes LUL losing business for now oh wait...
itsxaos: @georgehotz the GridION comes with 50 cells
murkythunder: does comma have free lunch
C4TFive: Make sure you check Ebay first HahaThink
guapcollector: stop spamming noob @architectzs
Nuroki: maan, its more than 48 per test
Nuroki: hours*
theonlymonkas: buy it
Nuroki: dont do it
Mariosavitch: 300 flow.. a billion dollars
theonlymonkas: do it
Itsmeek0: yea, but did you check ebay yet?
elephantpandas: lets just rent one and buy a bubble boy suit danX
Itsmeek0: or craigslist?
benchai18: Jorge is it true u stole sauriks gf in 2010?
cellophane11578: i wish i had some dinosaur DNa to sequence
logi6000: earn it act is about banning encryption. its important.
devm0d: What if Comma comes out with a DUI mode that you have to blow into to start the car AND sequences your RNA for Covid-19??
echobrother: what do you think about the coronavirus was created in a lab in china by the deep state
joeyskitkat: cmon, you have money. Buy the expensive kit
l1ght5p33d: I HATE when they don't do the math
doctorgenus: quick go find a coupon code
elephantpandas: LUL
Mariosavitch: lol
theonlymonkas: it's a great deal Kappa
C4TFive: LUL
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
Nussinov: LUL
Panda1Express: hahaha
Incurs0: lol
vicmoney69: LUL
360Plato: they sell to the government do you think they do mathj
theonlymonkas: LUL
l1ght5p33d: #DOTHEGODDAMNMATH
pepelaugh0: LUL
4zimut: by price?
PiroFloydian: B O O K
pjayys77: is this where we go to Dakest of Webs
doctorgenus: try the coupon freeshipping
l1ght5p33d: RTFM
pjayys77: you'll find it
pz3300: Just order a couple of hookers and an 8 ball george. Let’s get this party started
logi6000: earn it act is about banning encryption
jmv_chin: deep google tunnel
Nussinov: they foretold of the MiniON takeover
devm0d: Spindrift VS La Croix?
brofessorbob: We all have Covid-19
jimmyadaro: PogChamp
devm0d: I sure as shit do
devm0d: It burns when I pee
devm0d: that's a symptom right?
theonlymonkas: Kappa
codelumberjack: are you aggregating info for reference?
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz check the vietnam response to covid19
jimmyadaro: @devm0d Kreygasm
guapcollector: diet coke reigns supreme over all that dumb flavoured water
brofessorbob: @devm0d Sounds like you've been in Hong Kong too long
mashafique: Dr.Pepper gang.
jimmyadaro: @codelumberjack Yep, to his github repo
devm0d: I live near lake titty kaka
jimmyadaro: @codelumberjack https://github.com/geohot/corona
lefse: imagine living in north korea now Kreygasm
cellophane11578: ^
theonlymonkas: Kreygasm
echobrother: can you do hacking tutorials
l1ght5p33d: I wonder what kind of sex kim jun linkes
mrhdr: Kreygasm
codelumberjack: @jimmyadaro thanks, starred
logi6000: @echobrother what do you think this is
jimmyadaro: @echobrother a n a l
mashafique: @l1ght5p33d probably the kind involving chains and hand cuffs
Ayyyy420Lmao: this is shitposting on github
theonlymonkas: you better find the cure
thecoder15: living in Russia would be dope
brofessorbob: Going to watch some ASMR. Any recomendations?
timi13462: you open alot of windows
jimmyadaro: @brofessorbob cherry crush
brofessorbob: recomend to your bro
mashafique: @brofessorbob shibbysays
jimmyadaro: she does
jimmyadaro: iykwim
brofessorbob: thanks bros
jimmyadaro: ;*
Nussinov: you need a forward and reverse primer, there are websites you can design these on (WHO should have done this Kappa )
jimmyadaro: ^
Nussinov: actually idk for NGS
Mint2bSpiced: keep scrolling until the flow chart
Nussinov: im dumb
ImJ4Gu4R: test
l1ght5p33d: open source nanomaterials
Combat__ex: @georgehotz EXACTLY. RT-PCR is used to measure the amount of a specific RNA
ImJ4Gu4R: asmr
ImJ4Gu4R: lol
wisamalrawi: https://techcrunch.com/2020/03/24/mesa-biotech-gains-emergency-fda-approval-for-rapid-point-of-care-covid-19-test/
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz check the vietnam response to covid19
jimmyadaro: ^^
cellophane11578: if u were on joe rogans podcast, he would interrupt with a question regarding dmt
logi6000: why did you call it comma
ImJ4Gu4R: @PiroFloydian link bro
Ayyyy420Lmao: yeah RT stands for Real time
Ayyyy420Lmao: it measures quantity each cycle
l1ght5p33d: open source dmt
cellophane11578: yes
Combat__ex: @cellophane11578 JAMIE PULL THAT UP FOR ME WILL YA
Combat__ex: Kappa
cellophane11578: dna heal me bro
jimmyadaro: @l1ght5p33d i'm in
Nussinov: Ayyyy420Lmao reverse transcriptase. youre thinking of qpcr
mashafique: @cellophane11578 LUL
Ayyyy420Lmao: wtf they changed the acronyms or something since i studied this sthiet Kappa
logi6000: it's almost 1 am here
rickoftheroot: LUL
Bloodswordz88: HahaThisisfine HahaThisisfine HahaThisisfine
Nussinov: Ayyyy420Lmao no, its just that molecular biologists want us to be confused
inciMage: windows xp
julien9877: #ad
l1ght5p33d: Nano Lifee https://www.scienceinschool.org/content/decoding-dna-pocket-sized-sequencer
jimmyadaro: 1:45 a, here
o______________________k: such stupid pricing LULW
jimmyadaro: am*
lefse: 5:45 am here
yevheniiushtyk: yo
lefse: we on that corona time schedule
11plus4thinking: A LOW PRICE OF 19K :)
Bloodswordz88: windows XP homie
Combat__ex: LUL
knilecrack: :D
Combat__ex: on ebay LUL
jimmyadaro: LUL
knilecrack: you are getting raided
Lizardan: Next Heisenberg PogChamp
Bloodswordz88: piratebay
o______________________k: FBI OPEN UP
Nussinov: lots of lab equipment is bought on ebay guys chill LUL
SpaceGhost8: FDA, OPEN UP
wholesome_pepe: alibaba?
knilecrack: :D :D
cutza: "underground"
Irdi18: I can hook you up with the primers LUL
logi6000: change the title to starting an illegal corona lab
meteorlake: sumS
sneezy94: sneezy94 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
SofiaLouise: !uptime
jimmyadaro: @logi6000 yes
murkythunder: illegal biology lab where you cant talk louder than a whisper
o______________________k: squadQ squadQ squadQ squadQ squadQ squadQ squadQ squadQ squadQ squadQ squadQ
joeyskitkat: Hows your TSLA stock doing George?
syzo__: ice
eksdee_1_2_3: spare coochie?
SolarBerry: lack of PPE is slowing down testing
nomad119: https://openpcr.org/
jimmyadaro: Eat fkng onions mf
Combat__ex: @georgehotz You have to have make sure that absolutely no contamination occurs in PCR. Contamination was responsible for the hype for Tardi Gras being an immortal animal
logi6000: biology is one hop from chemistry. chemistry is one hop from George becoming Jessie Pinkman. I found the meaning to these streams
ziggyzergling: primers and swabs supplies are running low
meteorlake: lol @logi6000
architectzs: what’s up geo what’s your number one tip for learning to code? thanks
julien9877: @georgehotz thats what the news in germany said, "any basic lab can do corona tests with the machines they already have"
cellophane11578: @jimmyadaro i have a clip of me eating a raw onion like an apple
entangledbeing: @joeyskitkat When did he buy lol
Mint2bSpiced: It has to do with the fact that the test was not made for "High Throughput" testing. Meaning you can only test ~ 49 sample every 4 hrs per machine
0R4NG3: yooo
Combat__ex: yes, PCR isn't that hard to perform tho.
terradyn: theranos.ai
jimmyadaro: @Combat__ex Really??
meteorlake: i love the alternate universe where george is a drug lord.
jimmyadaro: @cellophane11578 Send it to me
Mint2bSpiced: *samples
THX1342: !uptime
Nussinov: @georgehotz oh remember that asmr girl? she codes in some of her videos 4Head another video for you to watch tonight Kappa
o______________________k: squadCozy squadCozy
SolarBerry: in NYC they are considering infusing blood of recovered patients with the very sick to transfer antibodies
cybergenik: 1 mol is nothing
itsxaos: pico > nano
itsxaos: right
cybergenik: that picomols
Santiago_LHC: DAFAQ
Thotshotgg: When are we playing plague inc?
Combat__ex: @jimmyadaro yes, google " tardigrade contamination "
DecayingSkullz: MedChemExpress
jimmyadaro: @Combat__ex i will
o______________________k: squadPH sweet
dingus74: lol
codelumberjack: if they are big pharma, are you small pharma?
11plus4thinking: gay walk KappaPride
cutza: attomols
Nussinov: huge brain
Ayyyy420Lmao: 2g is a normal amount of hydrogen?
jimmyadaro: @Ayyyy420Lmao 2g is like $10
wholesome_pepe: price gouging LUL
architectzs: what’s up geo what’s y#ur number one tip for learning to code?
Ayyyy420Lmao: dude just mix aluminum paper with hydrochloric
SpaceGhost8: smol pharma :)
murkythunder: its pricing for an institution not an individuaal
Ayyyy420Lmao: 10bucks my ass
d0ubletruth: big oil?
itsxaos: how long until shkreli gets out? LUL
PiroFloydian: we do
Rovelo: 🤔 what is he buying
jmv_chin: big brain
PiroFloydian: Big oil
ahahahaitslit: big tech
itsxaos: we need him on this
rickoftheroot: big brother
ahahahaitslit: is a thing
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: EZ SCAM
jimmyadaro: @Ayyyy420Lmao I'll do it for that money
PiroFloydian: bog tech
shoji22: indonesia here
roystang: is that a mandarin sir
julien9877: big data Kappa
Nussinov: big cock
Thotshotgg: How was your day today George?
BubbatheVTOG: big oil
o______________________k: big tech
jimmyadaro: BBC
isalhi: big paint
PiroFloydian: big tech
cutza: big pasta
Rovelo: im getting worried that you'll make a deadly virus george 🤔
Penguino138: Big Chicken
d0ubletruth: big pmol gang
joeyskitkat: bigAI
dingus74: Bbc lol
pjayys77: bigLy
l1ght5p33d: smol test
flvs: big cock
codelumberjack: big milk is an amusing local one
murkythunder: big nut
BubbatheVTOG: big tobbacco
jimmyadaro: big 9/11?
theonlymonkas: how do you feel?
isalhi: Big celery
dingus74: big pp
ShredderSherlock: p mol is smaller than nmol
sunole: 400,000 new people have joined Folding@Home’s fight against COVID-19 The quest to thwart the virus has strong help from distributed computing. Jon Fingas Jon Fingas, 03.23.20 The Folding@Home community has turned its attention toward the fight against COVID-19, and it now has massive computational power at its disposal as a result. The distributed comp
theonlymonkas: big p value
ShredderSherlock: isnt that good if you need less of the sample then
jimmyadaro: big nuts
elephantpandas: amiloScary probe wat
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
lefse: i lost
jimmyadaro: he's thinking about it, like fr
lefse: Kreygasm
FireDragon12: the fuk is going on
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
creasy_adc: Why Gorge look short af
vruthlessv: rip colon
jimmyadaro: eAT SOME GARLICK MF
jimmyadaro: MMMFFFFF
jmv_chin: it's cause he has a big brain
Nussinov: isnt he 6"2? LUL
jimmyadaro: and onions
jimmyadaro: u know
ShredderSherlock: where di you buy those sweatpants at
logi6000: George your birthday one day before mine
joeyskitkat: AND GINGER
Ayyyy420Lmao: does rtpcr need dna or rna primers?
Lizardan: @creasy_adc cause he's short duh
jimmyadaro: YEAH EAT GINGER MF
pjayys77: uh Big Mac *but should I go outside.. bruv
jimmyadaro: AND DRINK TEA
jimmyadaro: we need ya
jimmyadaro: stay alive
jimmyadaro: mf !
FireDragon12: people who eat into others ears can just go...
joeyskitkat: AND ICE MF
jimmyadaro: YEAH EAT ICE
jimmyadaro: wait, what
logi6000: no chewing ice
jimmyadaro: why ice?
architectzs: what’s up geo what’s your number one tip for learning to code?
joeyskitkat: Idk, just throwing it in the mix
joeyskitkat: ICE!
o______________________k: squad1 squad2 squad200
jimmyadaro: @architectzs Keep doing stuff
cellophane11578: take a bath in vinegar
jimmyadaro: @joeyskitkat Sounds good to me
C0deCane: Maybe you should change your nickname to biohot Kappa
logi6000: chewing ice is banned
julien9877: @georgehotz do they have free prime shipping?
jimmyadaro: YEAH VINEGAR MF
pjayys77: I think he said the other day, just do it
jimmyadaro: @logi6000 Nice
THX1342: did you buy a PCR machine, georgehotz ?
darkzade: KKona
theonlymonkas: BUY IT
lefse: BUY 1000 of em
jimmyadaro: We were talking yesterday about learning to program, just do stuff
Rovelo: PogChamp only 230 for 1000 ?
logi6000: chewing ice has been banned
vicmoney69: ?
jmv_chin: what's your crappycase repo about?
theonlymonkas: ResidentSleeper
itsxaos: dont you need the machine to run it still??
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Bloodswordz88: recreating sars DIY
Santiago_LHC: COMMABIO, yo!
theonlymonkas: LUL
AresRai: EZ
jimmyadaro: Comma Bio mf
Nussinov: LUL
elephantpandas: amiloScary FBBlock TheIlluminati
jimmyadaro: gg
vicmoney69: LUL
rickoftheroot: LUL
cutza: SMALL PHARMA
guinness84: have u tried running principal component analysis on Corona Virus
jimmyadaro: HAHAHAHA
Ayyyy420Lmao: nothing's legal
Rovelo: probably not LUL
jmv_chin: new startup is born Keepo
guinness84: The Secret answer
flvs: Small Pharma at its finest
pjayys77: uh What was the last part
OrlinTheMage: LuvSign LuvSign LuvSign
jimmyadaro: SMALL PHARMA b!tc#
ImJ4Gu4R: BIG PHARMA : knock2
theonlymonkas: LUL LUL
Nuroki: but u need someone infected to test KEKW
jimmyadaro: !Adderall
C0deCane: @georgehotz But a couple dozen 6 packs of those oxygen canisters off Amazon today, appreciate the great advice you gave us yesterday Kappa
theonlymonkas: F R E E
C0deCane: bought*
lefse: you look so evil when you drink
SpaceGhost8: any coupon codes?
logi6000: we all know this is how George is gonna get into the serial killer business. he's just going to unleash this on the white house
jimmyadaro: @C0deCane LMAO
SparksCx: infect yourself to test PogChamp
THX1342: did you play around with http://designer.genomecompiler.com ?
jmv_chin: how can you get a true boolean without bein infected Kappa
pjayys77: how does one drink evil
architectzs: hhkb
cellophane11578: lets swab up
jimmyadaro: Play Plague Inc again
Combat__ex: @georgehotz which protein or gene is the primer part of??????
architectzs: should i get an HHKB
ImJ4Gu4R: @jimmyadaro yo, they add new mods lol
64pillars: xacM
theonlymonkas: lol
64pillars: xqcM
SparksCx: xqcL
jimmyadaro: lul
julien9877: small NON COMMERCIAL pharma lab Kappa
THX1342: https://theminione.com/pcr-system/ < cheap PCR machine
nomad119: Did you see this project? https://openpcr.org/
barkazzaz: xqcM
guinness84: jupyter notebooks in 2020 LUL
jimmyadaro: wait what
bytebacon: What window manager is that?
C0deCane: Here at comma labs, we care about people and we are not big pharma were small pharma some even say little pharma
64pillars: xqcM then profit
elephantpandas: you are going to end up like aaron traywick monkaS
jimmyadaro: @bytebacon Idk his but i recommend Magnet
THX1342: miniONE is the one thoughtemporium uses in his lab I think
knilecrack: AHAHA
jimmyadaro: LUL
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
architectzs: what’s a window manager?
theonlymonkas: genius
ImJ4Gu4R: corona virus has corona...seems legit
logi6000: this is George's way into the serial killer business. he's going to make his self made sars 2 stronger and unleash it on the white house
jimmyadaro: @architectzs Google it
julien9877: FDA, OPEN UP
TsarSec: corona all the way down monkaS
l1ght5p33d: so f#*#nh leet
theonlymonkas: PogChamp
jimmyadaro: @architectzs You can't be a programmer if you dont google enough
Nussinov: thank goodness
itsxaos: PogChamp CORONA CURED BY GIVING IT CORONA TO KILL IT?!
bytebacon: @jimmyadaro thanks, looks good
vicmoney69: PogChamp
jmv_chin: STRESS LEVELS
jmv_chin: XD
jimmyadaro: @bytebacon I use that :)
Bloodswordz88: "Learn How to Google"
theonlymonkas: xD
4zimut: wait N3? there is anew version?
jmv_chin: this is the most action packed googling
architectzs: does magnet the windows manager work for windows?
jimmyadaro: @Bloodswordz88 Well, it's important!
Ayyyy420Lmao: man even if it doesnt have the exact sequence it can give a positive, you should be runing some alignment score shit instead of exact find no?
jimmyadaro: @architectzs I don't think so
Bloodswordz88: hail brethren
architectzs: shid
logi6000: are you going to confirm or deny what is said?
jimmyadaro: Spectacle
codelumberjack: where'd you get your "corone"?
architectzs: what’s a good one for windows?
codelumberjack: corona*
jimmyadaro: https://www.spectacleapp.com/
cutza: do you need to get infected?
C0deCane: @codelumberjack you can get it at your local grocery stores, fairly cheap
jimmyadaro: Spectacle is not longer maintained hahaha
jimmyadaro: Use Magnet
nozoke: what are we doing
jimmyadaro: @nozoke Reverse-engineering COVID
pz3300: History will show the virus that ended the world was cooked in a homemade lab in NJ
architectzs: what’s a good one for windows? an manager
TsarSec: just hack their website and get it for free 4Head
itsxaos: sure, just send in your FDA lab certification and youre good to go Kappa
nozoke: oh noted ty @jimmyadaro
logi6000: @pz3300 San Diego
jimmyadaro: https://apps.apple.com/es/app/magnet/id441258766?mt=12
pjayys77: you mean they aren't gonna price gouge the hell out of medical devices
jmv_chin: IM EXCITED
doctorgenus: @georgehotz has boku bucks
TsarSec: amazin
julien9877: coding PogChamp oh nvm FeelsBadMan
jimmyadaro: Not RT push
jimmyadaro: lmao
Lizardan: Treatments***
timi13462: what is the github link
sunole: 400,000 new people have joined Folding@Home’s fight against COVID-19 The quest to thwart the virus has strong help from distributed computing. Jon Fingas Jon Fingas, 03.23.20 The Folding@Home community has turned its attention toward the fight against COVID-19, and it now has massive computational power at its disposal as a result. The distributed comp
C0deCane: LUL soon enough this "lab" will be a mobile lab in an RV in an undisclosed location
ShredderSherlock: i want to know about the black hole quencher
mr_stochastic: @georgehotz How is not having vim in Jupyter Notebook going?
Nuroki: booooooring
rickoftheroot: LUL
logi6000: @c0decane in El Camino
jimmyadaro: @timi13462 https://github.com/geohot/corona
architectzs: Anyone know any good windows managers for windows?
Mint2bSpiced: here is their instructions https://biosearchassets.blob.core.windows.net/assetsv6/product-inseert_2019-ncov-ruo.pdf
darkhtx1: just make a covid-20 thats infects covid-19 and kills it
Lizardan: @architectzs the default
architectzs: oof
doctorgenus: that's buku bucks
C4TFive: wait until he goes to checkout and needs .edu email for that price Kappa
Ayyyy420Lmao: eat big to get big
mr_stochastic: @architectzs yeah not much other than default
theonlymonkas: LUL
architectzs: idk how to work this shit haha
jimmyadaro: @C4TFive omg
THX1342: https://theminione.com/pcr-system/
architectzs: the default one
Sniky83: go activate donationz
architectzs: idk the keybinds
doctorgenus: looks important
itsxaos: 2000$ LID
Knarez: im out of the loop, what's george up to?
Appz_x: check amazon
cutza: will you need to get infected?
doctorgenus: he's trying to create a small pharma in his room
jmv_chin: he's building a small pharma
jimmyadaro: @Knarez Creating an illegal small pharma
pz3300: Don’t you need a virus making license George?
logi6000: @knarez starting a non fda approved small pharma
Nuroki: https://theminione.com/pcr-system/
jmv_chin: this is how startups are born
OrlinTheMage: don't do it to yourself!
jimmyadaro: so he can do COVID tests
C0deCane: American meth manufactures racing to find a cure. Here tonight of Fox!
Knarez: monkaS
doctorgenus: it's the start of the bio division at comma
THX1342: NotLikeThis
DecayingSkullz: https://theminione.com/pcr-system/
jimmyadaro: @C0deCane We talked about meth earlier before hahaha
logi6000: @knarez and becoming a serial killer
theonlymonkas: DO IT
nomad119: https://www.chaibio.com/sahara-hot-start-pcr-master-mix
jimmyadaro: @logi6000 That too
Combat__ex: Quantitative
jimmyadaro: https://github.com/geohot/corona
ackxhpaez: Yeah I always forget about the RNA extraction
whycopper: Hi George
sunole: George, look into protein folding.
cregger: this little project might be up there in the rankings of craziest things i've seen george pursue on stream LUL
logi6000: this is all fake on his second monitor he's looking up arsenic pills to fake sell as adderall
doctorgenus: damn a lot of stuff you need. guess why there's money in pharma
jimmyadaro: @cregger Same
Nussinov: more letters = more expensive
AresRai: @sunole he looked into it in #2
darkhtx1: squadQ 🦠 squadOmega
cutza: torrent the rna
mehdi_tw: yo call walter white and start a new business MAN
cregger: i feel like i'm watching A Beautiful Mind 5Head
joshperri: What's the purpose of testing for it?
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz Comma Bio Pharma
Combat__ex: @joshperri memes
Zazens: 10K budget for pharma company?
C0deCane: Just 3d print it Kappa
itsxaos: i think you need a centrifuge if you want to extract DNA
doctorgenus: day 4 of stream, I need equipment, let's buy buy buy
almonte550: If you can create immunity with the virus, why no one here is actively looking to get infected?
THX1342: ### Shopping list
darkzade: ratirlToxic
jimmyadaro: go fund him
Mint2bSpiced: the FDA included a list of equipment you need to preform this test FYI
Combat__ex: @almonte550 thats actually a viable strategy. look up heard immunity
THX1342: so this is how 12 monkeys starts
Ayyyy420Lmao: @almonte550 you're implying no one is, i've broken quarantine everyday this last week
Combat__ex: herd immunity
C0deCane: @almonte550 because our health care system can't handle the surge, literally the only real reason
cutza: torrent the rna
logi6000: guys on his second monitor he's looking up arsenic pills to kick start his serial killing business. he's going to sell them as adderall in his small pharma.
elephantpandas: lirikS
jimmyadaro: but why
williamjennings1: NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
guinness84: just run PCA and run it through a conv net noob
cregger: xqcC
darkhtx1: -380 squadD squadQ 🦠 squadOmega 🦠 squadOmega 🦠 squadOmega
TsarSec: i feel like were working towards folding@home LUL
mr_stochastic: Did George already know bio or did he learn bio on the fly as well lol
ackxhpaez: Seriously though Everlywell is starting to sell a coronavorus testing kit eventually for at-home testing
xxxelent: 500 isnt that a shitload?
mehdi_tw: day 6 of stream : i need people to test on things in my illegal pharma
itsxaos: @georgehotz how can you be sure its a true negative though?
jimmyadaro: $10k to start??
jmv_chin: high quality googling
elephantpandas: 💉 justke10Virus = aaron traywick
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
whycopper: xqcC xqcC xqcC
Ayyyy420Lmao: bio is not easy it's vodoo science
jimmyadaro: ResidentSleeper
zwisch: math is just hard
nomad119: https://www.chaibio.com/coronavirus
DecayingSkullz: https://theminione.com/pcr-system/
jimmyadaro: https://github.com/geohot/corona
mehdi_tw: math is cool bro
ahahahaitslit: math is hard for basically everyone
nomad119: for research only ;)
darkhtx1: bio ez clap
MrTriharder: Math is actually hard
thrashtazs: both are hard practices
codelumberjack: maybe its because you delegate all math to software
vembumees: bio is easy because we dont know shit about the complex stuff
localcanofdutchgold: math is abstract, bio is specific
C0deCane: @georgehotz The real issue with bio is its acceptance in the world
logi6000: I took a biology course in 7th grade. that is my bio knowledge
PiroFloydian: mand doesnt work well for math and hacked the iphone at 17 WutFace
Nussinov: both are hard to be really good at
mr_stochastic: @georgehotz did you have to know a lot of math theory for self-driving car?
MrTriharder: Math requires out of the box thinking
opus_000: lol yeah this was the wrong stream to mention he's considered being a serial killer SuperVinlin
itsxaos: biosurveillance LUL
Mrclutch963: What is he trying to do?
Combat__ex: Yes, Bio is actually easy. But a lot more of memorization of jargon than math maybe
nremind: bio is like elementary school math
l1ght5p33d: There is no story to math, no beginning or end you have to look, remember and understand all of any proof or problem at once
jimmyadaro: IT IS
Ayyyy420Lmao: @mr_stochastic nope you just need to type import X
DecayingSkullz: its expensive AF
Santiago_LHC: commit and push!
Waywoah: It helps that most of this info was known before Covid-19
mr_stochastic: @ayyyy420lmao how does one not be a script kiddy then 😔
cregger: @georgehotz 1 bitcoin and some mcdonalds and i'll be your guinea pig
jimmyadaro: @DecayingSkullz $10K FOR SMALL PHARMA??? Its not expensive at all
MrTriharder: Put it on comma.ai misc expenses and but it 5Head
death_gadget: Math underlies everything. Math can explain bio, bio can't explain math.
lefse: ALL IN ONE????? PogChamp
Santiago_LHC: commit!
outlier2: peter thiel on math vs. bio: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SO_00POR-Po&feature=youtu.be&t=1131
DecayingSkullz: @jimmyadaro its like $5k i think
Ayyyy420Lmao: @death_gadget you're thinking about math because of bio because you're an animal famalam
jimmyadaro: @DecayingSkullz Even better then!
thrashtazs: @death_gadget bio explains life
theonlymonkas: did he buy it!?!
MrTriharder: @thrashtazs Life is math.
jimmyadaro: @theonlymonkas Not yet
death_gadget: ^
nomad119: Chaibio apparenlty used to do the manufacturing openpcr
cellophane11578: because were all biological?
thrashtazs: @MrTriharder youre not wrong
ahahahaitslit: math is great for explaining physics but is significantly weaker for modelling bio phenomena
doctorgenus: that's a lot of money. Spend it on a ventilator
THX1342: fluorophore is used in electrophoresis
MrTriharder: How many lungs(bio) do u have? 2 (math)
THX1342: the step after you do PCR
jimmyadaro: Spend it on adderall
guinness84: if u get one can i throw u some bills to test myself i live in sd
almonte550: I would get infected with covid-19 if I know I will recover
death_gadget: I challenge anyone to show that math doesn't encompass bio.
Nussinov: THX1342 LOL
THX1342: you do electrophoresis to measure the amount of DNA you got in your PCR
almonte550: The thing is, I don't know if I will
guest1GRjBAYo: suck my k e y b o a r d
THX1342: Nussinov am I tripping? I
Nussinov: THX1342 the 80s called they want their method back
cregger: anyone know if george's end goal is to profit off of a cure/vaccine or is this all for fun?
whyZaya: @death_gadget Are you telling me math explains classical logic? I doubt it. Classical logic explains math.
TalonFire: biology is expensive WutFace
THX1342: Nussinov well that's what I know amateurs are doing LUL
Nussinov: THX1342 they fluorophore is measured with some kind of CCD
Appz_x: built in wifi PogChamp
MrTriharder: @whyzaya Logic is a branch of math
Nussinov: THX1342 its quantitative, thats the point
jmv_chin: @whyZaya big brain
peter35_: math is overwhelming in learning the landscape of any "land" of math that was mapped over decades and centuries by geniuses. then doing original research is a whole new journey
logi6000: instead of getting all this stuff you could just buy a fuck ton of weed and wait til the end of the world. then be the first to overdose on weed
jimmyadaro: WIFI COVID TEST
almonte550: @TalonFire really expensive, it's high class toys
Nussinov: THX1342 it's done in the machine iirc
death_gadget: Classical logic != math. Logic is human, math is universal.
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
icyvran: Using the high-intensity X-ray light from the Berlin synchrotron source BESSY II, they have decoded the 3D architecture of the main protease of SARS-CoV-2 https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2020/03/200320101631.htm
ahahahaitslit: classical logic? it is a branch of math itself though
l1ght5p33d: @ahahahaitslit Not really, comparing Feynman diagrams used to describe LHC with optical data with a protein imaging laboratory ...
THX1342: Nussinov oh, so you also don't know :)
THX1342: Nussinov LOL /
Combat__ex: Does anyone know if you can do ELISA or protein mapping for the proteins (E,S,N) for coronavirus testing?
Nussinov: THX1342 LUL /
Ayyyy420Lmao: @logi6000 the first? there's been a handful already
jmv_chin: chat is going big-big brain
C0deCane: @georgehotz after you buy the minion thing, lets hack it Kappa
mehdi_tw: but can you jailbreak it @georgehotz ?
doctorgenus: that's how they get you
Ayyyy420Lmao: thermo wont sell to you
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
logi6000: @ayyyy420lmao I don't think so
julien9877: Small Lab LUL
lefse: jailbreak support?
coProof: Here we go again
jimmyadaro: WIFI COVID TEST
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
C0deCane: sure they will haven't you guys ever heard of social engineering
Nussinov: @THX1342 im 100% right tho i just double checked Kappa
icyvran: Using the high-intensity X-ray light from the Berlin synchrotron source BESSY II, they have decoded the 3D architecture of the main protease of SARS-CoV-2 https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2020/03/200320101631.htm
edu4594: did work?
doctorgenus: nice use those catelogs as toilet paper lol
jimmyadaro: LUL
Ayyyy420Lmao: @logi6000 100% confident it was reported that mom of 2 died of weed not spice in the UK
nitropiece: nitropiece subscribed with Twitch Prime.
joshperri: I don't get why he wants to reverse engineer a test procedure that a lab assistant could explain and perform.
itsxaos: small pharma screwed over once again BibleThump
daxyxy98: your price is highter, because you access their site from a mac LUL
logi6000: George if you were going to make a new startup what would it be
joshperri: Thought we were supposed to be REing a virus
Ayyyy420Lmao: @daxyxy98 big if true
jimmyadaro: @joshperri Not the procedure… The virus.
THX1342: @Nussinov I still didn't get what you think I said is wrong LUL electrophoresis, automated or not, is still used and that's the the fluorophores are used
guinness84: they make u take an IAT to buy it for discount
joshperri: @jimmyadaro This is all just to see if a sample contains the viral RNA
cregger: not to poop on the parade but how would george find a cure before established labs? or is this for the hell of it?
C0deCane: @Ayyyy420Lmao how would she have died, an overdose is completely impossible with current marijuana even in strongest form
itsxaos: LUL
Ayyyy420Lmao: @C0deCane nonstandard reaction to it
AresRai: @cregger this is just to learn about biology and try to have fun coding w it
Combat__ex: why test for coronavirus if everyone here likely has had it? Kappa Kappa Kappa Kappa
jimmyadaro: LUL
ahahahaitslit: @l1ght5p33d math is not as good at modelling biology and making predictions from models when compared to physics is my point
rickoftheroot: LUL
jimmyadaro: NOT YET
AresRai: LUL
RadricCSGO: we might
jimmyadaro: WIFI COVID TET
julien9877: BELIEVE
jimmyadaro: TEST
flvs: its greay
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: YES
itsxaos: we are SO CLOSE
C0deCane: @Ayyyy420Lmao I would say there was an underlying issue they didn't find/ didn't care too
mehdi_tw: GOOD TIME BROO
flvs: great*
ahahahaitslit: not an expert though obviously
logi6000: we are having an amazing time
doctorgenus: we're having a blast
aar0npham: Hahah
cregger: damn with the 5Head help of chat you may be able to Kappa
DecayingSkullz: HYYYYYYYYYYPPPEEEEE TRRRRAAAAIIIIIINNNNN
jimmyadaro: Now some Q&A!
williamjennings1: coffee? at 10:13
williamjennings1: WTF
CheeseManUchiha: wtf we arent curing corona i got scammazzed
mr_stochastic: Yup, super fun
Nussinov: @THX1342 god its been years since I've done this work, but I think the idea is that the flourophores are attached to the primers which are designed to specifically anneal to the target sequence as its amplified, allowing for real time quantitation by fluorophore detection
doctorgenus: we learn how geohot shops
cellophane11578: im having fun, might watch some pinky and brain after this
coProof: I’m not crazy yet :)
MrTriharder: Q&A time SwiftRage
voxelfox0125: I personally believe Geohot is one of the few people that actually knows how to use the internet to teach himself anything and apply it within a few days.
pec_adillo: just casually cure corona, no big
death_gadget: @ahahahaitslit How do you make a prediction without math?
Combat__ex: This is really educational
Combat__ex: love your stream
toasty_jk2: that was me
jimmyadaro: LUL
mr_stochastic: @voxelfox0125 true
ahahahaitslit: @death_gadget in bio? it's driven through experiment
DecayingSkullz: choo chooooo
Juhaa: poly A tail
C0deCane: @death_gadget you pay off the side your beating against
julien9877: so aaaaaa = end msg sign? thats cool
theonlymonkas: no choo chooo
ahahahaitslit: of course we need math as well
THX1342: i.e. the bufferoverflow
logi6000: scam train!
jimmyadaro: Now some Q&A!
julien9877: nice
ahahahaitslit: but i'm comparing it to physics
Knarez: thats pretty dope
timi13462: brute force
mr_stochastic: Anyone who watched George doing code for vid processing, does he ssh into a Linux server or something?
jimmyadaro: AAAAAAAAA
jimmyadaro: lol
death_gadget: @ahahahaitslit A prediction can't be made without math.
l1ght5p33d: rare As
Nussinov: @THX1342 so no, i dont think "electrophoresis" is used directly here, but yeah id have to double check if I'm missing a step
itsxaos: the virus screams at you in the code
cellophane11578: are there any viruses with low infection rate but huge fatality rates
PiroFloydian: every science can be abstracted to math if you go far enough
cregger: (not an insult at all) this is quite reminiscent of watching old Martin Shkreli streams in so many ways
MrTriharder: @death_gadget People haven’t heard of probability
TalonFire: AAAAA
doctorgenus: the corona virus needs triple A insurance
Combat__ex: AAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
logi6000: @cellophane11578 my plague inc virus
itsxaos: @cregger FREE SHKRELI
Ayyyy420Lmao: @cregger pray he doesnt end up in jail
itsxaos: whens he out btw
death_gadget: @MrTriharder Exactly what I was thinking. LUL
itsxaos: hes been in quite a while right
jimmyadaro: @Ayyyy420Lmao Yet.
cregger: @Ayyyy420Lmao they love to imprison the best of us
ahahahaitslit: @death_gadget i don't think i said that
joshperri: @cellophane11578 ebola
Ayyyy420Lmao: ross ulbritch, weinstein, etc
C0deCane: @death_gadget if your left enough you can make predictions with your emotions FACT
mrhdr: mizkifM
cregger: Shkreli would have already found a cure, hiked the price, and gone back to jail LUL
theonlymonkas: shkreli excel
cregger: WTF no weinstein but yes ross
death_gadget: @C0deCane Left in a political sense??
Bloodswordz88: free shkreli lol
jimmyadaro: @C0deCane Lmao true
Ayyyy420Lmao: T
zwisch: T
toasty_jk2: T
cregger: free shkreli and ross ulbritch
ahahahaitslit: @death_gadget my point was from what i've read mathematical models in biology are weaker than physics in terms of making predictions
PiroFloydian: t
jimmyadaro: Now some Q&A George
Nussinov: U Kappa
toasty_jk2: A with T, G with C
theonlymonkas: #FreeShkreli
ahahahaitslit: hence greater emphasis on experiment
C0deCane: yes but im just fucking with you LUL @death_gadget of course you can't make a prediction without math
thrashtazs: i hate to say it but this stream slightly reminds me of shkreli streams
THX1342: georgehotz if I am not mistaken you need two primers because you need a 'start' and 'stop' for the PCR process. THoughtEmporium has a good video on PCR that explains this, I shared on the 1st stream
MrTriharder: @c0decane your emotions are shaped by year Long math. True or false can be translated to any of your emotions
death_gadget: @C0deCane I'm with you there buddy.
williamjennings1: this guy is a machine
theonlymonkas: yes
death_gadget: @ahahahaitslit I was just making the point that "predictions" are themselves mathematic.
Nussinov: @THX1342 you're still going LUL
Sidhuu: @williamjennings1 it's called Adderall
jimmyadaro: DMT
THX1342: Nussinov are you a stalker, fam?
C0deCane: @MrTriharder Math is literally life i can't think of anything that doesn't or can't have a mathematical equation
williamjennings1: @Sidhuu didnt he say he had coffee too?
cellophane11578: gottacatchemall
cregger: is this a recording of the Zuck coding Facebook in '04?
cellophane11578: Kappa
theonlymonkas: Kreygasm it's called TEA
MrTriharder: @c0decane SeemsGood
death_gadget: @C0deCane TRUE!!
ahahahaitslit: @death_gadget of course. i was talking about models though
lsfa: Did you know anything about this prior to starting this project?
Nussinov: @THX1342 I don't like that you're speculating so much even after being wrong once LUL
williamjennings1: lmao
0R4NG3: lol
CompestLive: looool
Waywoah: He's using python, right?
l1ght5p33d: Hots is just better than all of us L 2 deal
edu4594: dayum
timi13462: whats his thiughts on adderall
ShredderSherlock: whats the concept behind jupyter notebooks
jimmyadaro: @Waywoah Yep
daxyxy98: !adderall
theonlymonkas: LUL
williamjennings1: is he staying up late tonite
mr_stochastic: @shreddersherlock exploratory analysis
jimmyadaro: No !Adderall here
williamjennings1: !Adderall
death_gadget: addrerall is a must!!
MrTriharder: He called us stupid PepeHands
logi6000: what a good laptop to buy to put arch on
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz make commands for the FAQ like !adderall
Ayyyy420Lmao: don't u need to reverse the list after you found the base pairs?
cellophane11578: !pokemongo
THX1342: Nussinov sorry, I wasn't wrong. flurophore IS used in electrophoresis. I never said it is the most modern or best method.
l1ght5p33d: all the plebs cant type crying performance enhancers
stuffedcrust45: @logi6000 thinkpad
edu4594: @ShredderSherlock execute separete parts of the code without running every piece
mr_stochastic: @shreddersherlock then he writes the code that works in a library using vim in his terminal
opus_000: should be an emote with his face on it MaxLOL
jimmyadaro: @logi6000 Any?
edu4594: seperate*
williamjennings1: why were your eyes dialted when you hacked the iphoen
THX1342: Nussinov and doesn't PCR use two primers one for the start and another for the end of the sequence you want to replicate?
edu4594: wtv
jimmyadaro: Literally any
SolarBerry: adderall is a recreational drug
lsfa: Did you know anything about this prior to starting this project?
0R4NG3: 5Head
timi13462: wtf
Ayyyy420Lmao: reverse the inverted list
vicmoney69: 5Head
ahahahaitslit: and think you're secure
OrlinTheMage: huh?
death_gadget: @ahahahaitslit I would just say, if you look at a low enough level math is at the core of even biological models.
jimmyadaro: @SolarBerry wtf
williamjennings1: you were on some kind of stimulant when you hacked the iphone
archeadis: have u tried adderall though/
logi6000: isn't Adderall really close to meth
theonlymonkas: PogChamp poetic
MrTriharder: 5Head
info303: what about being secure and knowing you are insecure?
whyZaya: What about being secure and knowing you're insecure?
cregger: xqcM
Combat__ex: @georgehotz theres a line of code reverse complimentary code in python
Ayyyy420Lmao: alcohol is banned by WADA tho
Combat__ex: alt_map = complement = {'A': 'T', 'C': 'G', 'G': 'C', 'T': 'A'} def reverse_complement(seq): for k,v in alt_map.iteritems(): seq = seq.replace(k,v) bases = list(seq) bases = reversed([complement.get(base,base) for base in bases]) bases = ''.join(bases) for k,v in alt_map.iteritems(): bases = bases.replace(v,k) return bases
death_gadget: I'm drinking beer right now! :)
RadricCSGO: addy makes me want to watch porn for 14 hours
timi13462: just try crack it's better
Arrthur: xqcM
C0deCane: performance if you need to perform at staying up all night
info303: @whyZaya jinx
l1ght5p33d: tesla did but he just liked fucking with metal in the garage
Waywoah: Unless you're shhoting
PiroFloydian: what about caffeine @georgehotz
williamjennings1: just mixed l thenine in my gatorade
Waywoah: shooting
ahahahaitslit: @death_gadget it is used all the time in biological models for sure
Ayyyy420Lmao: reverse the inverted list man
whyZaya: @info303 Yeah haha.
doctorgenus: summary of corona stream day 1: spike protein is the exploit day2: corona virus is no the flu, it's SARS! day3: shit hit the fan in a month day4: need to buy equipment to test on self because I might have coronavirus?
opus_000: I low-key want to shock my prefrontal cortex
miiiiiiim: weed is okay for creativity but like hell i'd want to code
thrashtazs: @logi6000 I mean yeah, its an Amphetamine
guinness84: i think alcohol is performance encoring and banned for archery competitions
info303: @whyZaya I think thats called paranoia lol
guinness84: enhancing
logi6000: @opus_000 wtf
C0deCane: @doctorgenus down the rabbit hole we all go
timi13462: coke > adderall
williamjennings1: meditation is good for focus
SolarBerry: i do however like psuedoephedrine which is much smoother than adderall and better for focus
whyZaya: @info303 Yup
jimmyadaro: @timi13462 Aha
Combat__ex: !addrerall
Combat__ex: !Adderall
jimmyadaro: @Combat__ex Nothing like that here
inciMage: @guinness84 it decreases cell performance hence shaking is omitted
opus_000: @logi6000 it works
logi6000: adderal
cregger: for anyone who has seen the movie Lucy, George is what happens when we tap into 40% of our brain power
coProof: Oh my god there it is boys! CTCGA
logi6000: aderall
death_gadget: @ahahahaitslit Don't take what I am saying as a discount of biology. I'm only stating that I believe math is at a lower level. That bio couldn't exist without math.
Ayyyy420Lmao: ffs i told you 3x in chat
AKspirits: just tuned in... i think im a few days behind the lecture prof
rickoftheroot: SeemsGood
C0deCane: Think about all the hypochondriacs out there absolutely losing there shit and eating up our healthcare system LUL
Nussinov: @THX1342 you are not 100% wrong on what you're saying, it is just clear to me that you dont understand how things actually work. there is no relationship between a reverse primer and the "stop" of a pcr process. the primers themselves anneal to the target sequence according to base complementarity, and the process stops when you stop the cyclic annealing/melting
C0deCane: there has to be a high number of them just my honest guess
jimmyadaro: @C0deCane Kinda sad
bluejimmy168: 1st time here. What are you trying to do?
logi6000: I stick to weed
C0deCane: Those people will fuck up the data too
miiiiiiim: god i miss python
joshperri: reverse compliment
williamjennings1: how do you have coffee at 10pm wtf
jimmyadaro: @C0deCane For sure
death_gadget: I've been without weed for over a year. :(
logi6000: it's 130 here
logi6000: am
Nussinov: okay now everyone give the streamer a reverse compliment
AresRai: 6:30
HellxNebula: @williamjennings1 its just coffee not cocaine LUL
cellophane11578: are u inherting the _invert function there? im not familiar with coding like that
MrTriharder: 11am :)
thecoder15: @georgehotz https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32133832/?from_single_result=32133832
ahahahaitslit: @death_gadget you think math is more fundamental than bio? this is definitely true imo. bio is emergent
samthedogg: what does the _ mean in _invert on like 64 on the left
ShredderSherlock: @SolarBerry Trump also likes pseudoephedrine
death_gadget: @georgehotz You ready to trade that Sub for Mod yet? LUL
samthedogg: call the parent function?
jimmyadaro: @cellophane11578 I think so
williamjennings1: good luck sleeping @HellxNebula
cellophane11578: @samthedogg thats essentially what im asking too
SolarBerry: @ShredderSherlock lmfao
mr_stochastic: @cellophane11578 not inheriting, just calling an internal function.
cellophane11578: ah okay
HellxNebula: @williamjennings1 its 7:25 am here and i had coffee like 14 hours ago
samthedogg: @mr_stochastic so its neccessary for recursive functions in python?
THX1342: Nussinov maybe we're having language issues... "stop" means one thing to you (and I know what you mean.. I know there are temperature cycles and all) and another to me :)
williamjennings1: @HellxNebula talking about george
jimmyadaro: What's happening rn?
cregger: does this project have any relation to comma ai?
jimmyadaro: @cregger Not yet
jimmyadaro: Thanks @georgehotz
williamjennings1: wtf
mr_stochastic: @samthedogg yeah you can see that kind of thing in recursive functions. But he didn't use it recursively. Just used in in a list comprehension he had
itsxaos: shkreli gets out in 2023
bluejimmy168: Can someone tell me eli5, what he is trying to do?
cregger: not soon enough
AresRai: @itsxaos time flies
williamjennings1: hows shrekli!
dairynuts: what is happening
jimmyadaro: Q&A
AresRai: shrekli FeelsBadMan
cregger: #FREESHKRELI
Ayyyy420Lmao: the girl from theranos didnt go to jail or did she?
Kebabpizza1993: geohotz trying to be the new shkreli lol.
dairynuts: is this the diary of a madman or....
death_gadget: Shkreli could cure Covid-19
Nussinov: @THX1342 language matters i guess. I was just suspect
yungdeli_: i used to watch shkreli every stream
roystang: shrkeli would fix the coronavirus
ahahahaitslit: why tf is that guy in jail for so long
yungdeli_: smart man
OrlinTheMage: he walks like such a bottom
C0deCane: @dairynuts geo is just days away from curing this thing for all of us.
thecoder15: shkreli and george the dream team right there
mutrx: yo
Codeoxic: @georgehotz What are you working on?
cregger: i miss Shkreli shitting on people calling in
edu4594: !time
timi13462: can someone any laptops to buy
mr_stochastic: @ayyyy420lmao don't think so, she just got fined I think
williamjennings1: biology exam
NagyOut: you seen nextrtain.org ?
dairynuts: @C0deCane actually?
jimmyadaro: @Codeoxic CO-VID
williamjennings1: omg biology looks hard
cregger: cregger subscribed at Tier 1.
l1ght5p33d: @bluejimmy168 Corona research and cure development also bioweapons
Ozonemaster: bio exams are naming theory
guinness84: FTC locked up the one man that could cure corona
jimmyadaro: SMALL PHARMA
C0deCane: @williamjennings1 nothing is too hard for @georgehotz Bio is EZ
theineffablebob: what's this guy making
mr_stochastic: @ozonemaster 😂
dairynuts: nothing you can't cram for in a day
Codeoxic: @jimmyadaro I noticed that, but what specifically?
cregger: just play Plague Inc 4Head
jimmyadaro: @Codeoxic Trying to decode the virus I guess
williamjennings1: @C0deCane i can see that
williamjennings1: Quizlet lmao
Nussinov: quizlet Pepega
jimmyadaro: ResidentSleeper
cregger: ResidentSleeper
Ayyyy420Lmao: latent
Nussinov: ResidentSleeper
C0deCane: I wanna see his test score lol
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: quizlet time
C0deCane: I bet it will be pretty good
l1ght5p33d: wtf is this
jimmyadaro: OhMyDog
mutrx: MHC 1
Nussinov: 2 PogChamp
mr_stochastic: @ideology_sniffing_raccoon Anki's where it's at
Ayyyy420Lmao: MHC
itsxaos: i think 2
logi6000: Quizlet good. iuse it all the time
PiroFloydian: gotta use context clues
o______________________k: squadR hey DUD where is my bio hacking jailbreak DUD squadR squadR squadR
PiroFloydian: decreased helps you here
jimmyadaro: LUL
Sidhuu: now do a math exam
mutrx: immunology > every other biological discipline
samthedogg: @mr_stochastic wait so is _function() the same as calling self.function?
C0deCane: squadOK
PiroFloydian: it's gonna look for things that are different than normal @georgehotz decreased is the helpful word
Ayyyy420Lmao: false
Nussinov: @mutrx oh lookie, a med student in the wild
mrhdr: o______________________k MY MAN squadW squadNation
itsxaos: false my guess
timi13462: 2x 4 = 16 Solve!!!
cregger: redsSmart
williamjennings1: lmao
ahahahaitslit: yes
Ayyyy420Lmao: no
C0deCane: squadW so many apes in here
ahahahaitslit: lmao
o______________________k: squadLaugh @mrhdr
THX1342: @Nussinov yeah I'm not a bio person (obviously) and not an english native so that complicates things :D just curious about this stuff
MrTriharder: admiralF1 admiralF2 Any cuties in chat?
theseusq: 🐵
wisamalrawi: picorna
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: poor squadW here :)
cregger: redsCorona
o______________________k: squadBrug squadBrug
jimmyadaro: Small pharma ftw
wisamalrawi: Not all have an envelope
mr_stochastic: @samthedogg It's just naming convention. He could of called "inside_inverted_function"
bytebacon: bacteriophages are the real deal
dorkmo: after we curve corona, can we cure herpies, asking for a friend
Nussinov: @THX1342 all good man, I hope my tone doesnt sound like im mad or scrutinizing - we should all be curious!
AresRai: EZ
mutrx: @dorkmo thanks for asking on my behalf
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz you can change question settings
itsxaos: 4
PiroFloydian: to get rid of flashcards and typing answers if you want
wisamalrawi: A
MrTriharder: Chat recommend some tv shows to binge watch :)
wisamalrawi: lol
o______________________k: what a fucked up day squadR squadR
cregger: in theory wouldn't Shkreli's startup he was working on before he was imprisoned be able to model the virus and thousands of interactions to it by different proteins?
timi13462: money heist
itsxaos: 4 again
lithiumx4900: uncoating?
mrhdr: squadR YO GEO
CompestLive: uncoating
itsxaos: dangit
wisamalrawi: uncoating
Ayyyy420Lmao: latent
cybergenik: autoimmune
lithiumx4900: retrovirus
Ayyyy420Lmao: same what lmao
Nussinov: LUL
Nussinov: these questions are so shit LUL
wisamalrawi: yeah
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz CHANGE THE QUESTION SETTINGS
itsxaos: VoteYea
AresRai: me :)
jimmyadaro: LUL
itsxaos: easy
0R4NG3: Kappa
Nussinov: VoteYea
cregger: me Kappa
theonlymonkas: me
o______________________k: not me :)
DecayingSkullz: Kappa
mutrx: immunology is better
guinness84: computational virology
Nussinov: AGREED!
joshperri: That's the first step in covid replication, it transcribes it's negative to positives, then replicates the positives to make negatives.
phrixus_bro: do you guys remember the old skreli streams this reminds me
PiroFloydian: 2 days ago you said you have nothing but time @georgehotz
cregger: HACKERMANS get back to work xqcM
itsxaos: microbiology questions: https://www.d.umn.edu/~rhicks/genmicro/Practice Exam Questions.pdf
Nussinov: i took a structural virology course taught by a physicist and it was incredibly interesting all the ways they've studied those things
THX1342: whats the hardest thing you ever tried to learn @georgehotz ?
DecayingSkullz: Down the rabbit hole we go
cregger: @phrixus_bro i said the same thing 10 minutes ago, makes me nostalgic
cregger: a lot of overlap in the fanbase it seems
phrixus_bro: oh yeah nice!
vybster: George, have you not changed your clothes?
Sidhuu: what kind of maths
DecayingSkullz: what kind of math
edu4594: what about coq
localcanofdutchgold: what kind of math?
Sidhuu: lol
jimmyadaro: @vybster what for
yungdeli_: i wish i understood what he's tlaking about
joshperri: It needs to make negative sense to replicate.
Nussinov: it just does another round
AresRai: just go through them again yea
joshperri: "RdRp directly mediates the synthesis of negative-sense genomic RNA from the positive-sense genomic RNA."
jimmyadaro: I love him
jimmyadaro: lol
Ayyyy420Lmao: @jimmyadaro no homo right?
AresRai: nature take the simple paths FeelsGoodMan
mutrx: i only know of sense and anti-sense strands
jimmyadaro: @Ayyyy420Lmao maybe… kinda… why?
mattdougherty22: please do Erics show the portal if you have the chance
roystang: hack the virus george
joshperri: "This is followed by the replication of positive-sense genomic RNA from the negative-sense genomic RNA.[19] The other important function of the complex is to transcribe the viral genome."
Nussinov: if biology made me money I would have sppent all undergard reading about it LUL
jimmyadaro: @Ayyyy420Lmao Not sexual tho
mattdougherty22: Please do Eric Weinstein's show the portal if you have the chance
jimmyadaro: @Nussinov What did you study?
Bowlgirlblergh: if virology had a red pill, what would it be?
benchai18: Corona has a lipid envelope. That’s why soap pulls it apart
Nussinov: @jimmyadaro computational chemistry / chemical physics
benchai18: That’s the only thing I know about anything. Had to say it
jimmyadaro: @Nussinov Cool
itsxaos: @mattdougherty22 im guessing we would have to bother eric about it first
DecayingSkullz: @jimmyadaro are you from Argentina
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 You're right
tensorspac3: what is he building chat?
jimmyadaro: @DecayingSkullz Yep, why?
Ayyyy420Lmao: lipid envelope? i thought it was always protein
DecayingSkullz: @jimmyadaro just wonderin
jimmyadaro: @DecayingSkullz ????
mattdougherty22: can we not bother Eric about it? The mutually know Lex @itsxaos
benchai18: @jimmyadaro U just made my week thanks bruh
l1ght5p33d: @Bowlgirlblergh you die from it
timi13462: who wins hulk or thor
InstaDeath: whats going on right now? new to stream just dropped in
tensorspac3: same ^
Nussinov: a kinase would add a phosphate
yungdeli_: hacking the virus
jimmyadaro: @InstaDeath He keeps learning about bio
itsxaos: @mattdougherty22 im just saying we need to get him invited first
keith282: it was wahtever interacted w ATP
Ayyyy420Lmao: should have its own
l1ght5p33d: open source covid 2019
vybster: Hacking the coronavirus DNA/RNA
lithiumx4900: Is this published somewhere where I can follow along?
l1ght5p33d: open source covid cures
benchai18: @lithiumx4900 His GitHub
jimmyadaro: @lithiumx4900 https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCwgKmJM4ZJQRJ-U5NjvR2dg/videos
keith282: what it was that reacted w the ATP produced phosphorous
jimmyadaro: @lithiumx4900 https://github.com/geohot/corona
mattdougherty22: True @itsxaos He also regularly has people on he has never met and simply disagrees with on twitter. should be doable
itsChopsticks: did we invent a vaccine yet
georgehotz: https://github.com/geohot/corona
lithiumx4900: thanks all of yous.
itsxaos: @georgehotz have you been invited to eric weinsteins show?
l1ght5p33d: we found several treatments
jimmyadaro: ;*
Sidhuu: didn't someone die from that?
timi13462: that killed somebody
doctorgenus: where do you get hydroxicloquine?
itsChopsticks: did you find the safe dosage?
kubaaa6: my mom bought that shit 2 weeks ago lol
yungdeli_: black coffee?
kubaaa6: i thought she was crazy
un3okapi: why?
wholesome_pepe: Phosphorylases
thecoder15: @georgehotz make sure you have the right zinc
lithiumx4900: lithiumx4900 is gifting 5 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 5 in the channel!
lithiumx4900: lithiumx4900 gifted a Tier 1 sub to elektroids!
lithiumx4900: lithiumx4900 gifted a Tier 1 sub to mattdacentaur!
lithiumx4900: lithiumx4900 gifted a Tier 1 sub to rraksut!
lithiumx4900: lithiumx4900 gifted a Tier 1 sub to hardtarget4!
lithiumx4900: lithiumx4900 gifted a Tier 1 sub to samthedogg!
l1ght5p33d: drink 10 gallons of water
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Do you know computations modeling? Here's someone looking for help https://twitter.com/CurlyJungleJake/status/1242553710183514112
jimmyadaro: lmao
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogU
mutrx: thanks @lithiumx4900
THX1342: I've been taking zinc suplements since China quarantined Wuhan
Ayyyy420Lmao: madman with the stolen credit cards
itsChopsticks: @georgehotz what's the safe dosage?
levinson2504: Google WutFace
jimmyadaro: @lithiumx4900 What about me
jimmyadaro: hahaha
AresRai: @Sidhuu self medication is bad yea but never self medicate on big doses
rafalive: people are already doing this in china at toxic amounts
doctorgenus: can you get it from a drug dealer?
DecayingSkullz: https://honeybeehealth.com/drugs/plaquenil
raystriker98: mee2
raystriker98: jk
localcanofdutchgold: lul
doctorgenus: there has to be drug dealers for this
lithiumx4900: lithiumx4900 gifted a Tier 1 sub to jimmyadaro! They have given 6 Gift Subs in the channel!
timi13462: i'm pretty sure that combination killed somebody
C0deCane: @timi13462 no that dude drank fish tank cleaner called choroquine not hydroxychorolquine
phrixus_bro: is the border open
Sidhuu: @aresrai yea
jimmyadaro: @lithiumx4900 Thanks for the gift sub!
kakurai: Please don't buy this medicament unless you need it very hard.
AresRai: wtf
samthedogg: @lithiumx4900 yooooo thanks dude!
raystriker98: whoa he actually did it
DecayingSkullz: https://honeybeehealth.com/drugs/plaquenil
guinness84: should out tijuana
WhiteTailedSpider: AHAHAHHA
vicmoney69: lmao
raystriker98: gg
l1ght5p33d: Take 1/2 fish tanks per day
guinness84: xanax and plaquenil
jimmyadaro: lol
mutrx: @lithiumx4900 thanks for the 6 gifted subs!!
WhiteTailedSpider: WTF AHAHHA
directrix13: unless you have some underlying heart rhythm issues
levinson2504: do drugs
zwisch: LUL
Trouser: yeah that is freaking brilliant right there...clean my fish tank or kill this virus?
Sidhuu: also don't mix stuff u don't know
doctorgenus: is about the mg, gotta measure
mattdougherty22: @itsxaos would this format be at all helpful for listening to podcasts? http://mattdougherty.online/Podscribe-mock/test/test2
tsAllySparkles: lmao
localcanofdutchgold: OMEGALUL
jimmyadaro: Q&A come on
360Plato: LUL we have to keep explaining this
AzzoDio: The primary risk is Long QT syndrome, if you've ever had your heart checked you can be somewhat sure you are safe from that
edu4594: how i clip this
thecoder15: yeah make sure it won't interact with any meds you are currently taking
doctorgenus: can't wait for Q&A
tsAllySparkles: psychonautwiki has a graphql api
doctorgenus: I'll wait all night if I have to
WhiteTailedSpider: call someone the embulense, this guy is crazy LUL
damagedcorn: What’s your philosophy on drugs
vicmoney69: @edu4594 alt t
patroniv: Hey George, ever heard of Lambda School? If not, it’s an online school(boot camp) I guess. Always hear about how these bootcamps behave sketchy
jimmyadaro: @doctorgenus Yesterday he said "maybe, or may be not"
jimmyadaro: But i hope some Q&A
localcanofdutchgold: @damagedcorn dank
vicmoney69: @edu4594 i mean alt x
C0deCane: @WhiteTailedSpider what?
AresRai: nano tech building blocks PogChamp
ShredderSherlock: prions are smaller
mutrx: yeah plants can get viruses too
zwisch: yeah prions are even crazier
jimmyadaro: nano s#!ts
edu4594: @vicmoney69 thx
mattdougherty22: @patroniv you can find other online learning options here if interested: http://mattdougherty.online/ed-space-landscape/
C0deCane: LUL stop
TsarSec: .... no shit
Nussinov: monkaS
normie4life: stop thinking monkaS
vicmoney69: monkaS
jimmyadaro: cells fuk!ng
TsarSec: you mean like cancer?
julien9877: monkaS
vicmoney69: thats how cancer happens
levinson2504: you get cancer
geobitz: hes on shrooms
directrix13: then cancer
toasty_jk2: they do like all the time
AresRai: mathematically they will mess up sooner or later monkaS
Ayyyy420Lmao: that's why they have a checksum man
C0deCane: Micromanage those fuckers literally!!
lawric_: cancer
capsimirhd: yoooooo
opus_000: south park
tornpaperyoyos: #stonerthoughts
Nussinov: 1 protein can be made in sub 10 seconds monkaS
localcanofdutchgold: probably
jimmyadaro: engineer
ShredderSherlock: lol yes
vicmoney69: yes
360Plato: its called cancer
jimmyadaro: bio engineer
jimmyadaro: ?
mattdougherty22: agent
TsarSec: ????? are you an android wtf
itsxaos: youll think of your computer as a biological thing maybe
mattdougherty22: yes
normie4life: thinking about thinking LUL
icekrieg: you're a biological computer
levinson2504: we are biological things
Mint2bSpiced: If they mess up it becomes cancer
directrix13: @georgehotz there is pretty much a CRC on the end of your DNA called telomeres
geobitz: good
rafalive: yes
jimmyadaro: IT is better, we control the world
subconix: I thought this was called learning
Br4nnon: probably based on expertise
localcanofdutchgold: both perspectives
rafalive: its good
LaheyFPS: probably become healthier @georgehotz
geobitz: perspective
zoogaezee: BRO YOU ARE A BIOLOGICAL THING THAT IS A FACT
pwnbase: it's arbitrary
mutrx: evolution fixed the bug in 20BC, check the changelog @georgehotz
WhiteTailedSpider: @C0deCane ambulance*
ShredderSherlock: you'll be able to model the biological system better in a program
jimmyadaro: YOU DIDNT WASH UR HANDS EARLIER
tsAllySparkles: sounds depressing
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: forget
cregger: forget
vicmoney69: f o r g e t
ahahahaitslit: i wondered this too lol
360Plato: different framework
jimmyadaro: nope
tsAllySparkles: i'd rather live forever as software anyday
Nussinov: everything in biology is just an arbitrarily large physical system of interacting components
jimmyadaro: that was
levinson2504: doctor stonks
PiroFloydian: 10 seconds isnt effective
mattdougherty22: when consuming drugs or food do you think of it as a computer
tornpaperyoyos: #stonerthought
jimmyadaro: like4 secs
Br4nnon: you should always wash your hands for at least 10
timi13462: with dial
mattdougherty22: or a system in genreal
thecoder15: you want to have fun, look at everything going on in your digestive system
tensorspac3: why wash ur hands if you've not come into contact with something new?
l1ght5p33d: Just keep the hookers to a minimum you should be fine
PiroFloydian: it's been tested
LaheyFPS: DansGame didnt wash hands
PiroFloydian: 10 seconds isnt effective
Br4nnon: i think it comes with the knowledge
thecoder15: @georgehotz you want to have fun, look at everything going on in your digestive system
williamjennings1: 10 seconds wtf
sunole: Nature trial and error
wholesome_pepe: systems biology is a thing
Br4nnon: @PiroFloydian i said at least. key word
jimmyadaro: geohotz call me "bro", i can die happy
Nussinov: there is!!
THX1342: have you seen these computer simulations of DNA/RNA replication? It's a real mindfuck https://vimeo.com/361099778 it's a nano factory... really amazing stuff
jimmyadaro: @THX1342 omfg
itsxaos: @mattdacentaur it could be really helpful for a few cases, its a good idea and you should continue with it
THX1342: what jimmyadaro ?
zoogaezee: I JUST TUNED IN , WHAT is your goal right now ? with all this research
mutrx: @THX1342 i always question those, like surely they have to animate that by hand somehow?
jimmyadaro: @THX1342 I was looking for that video yesterday
sunole: Duh
rgbeezus: you streaming every night?
jimmyadaro: @zoogaezee Mind-fukc us?
tensorspac3: well if it didnt would it be called a corona virus
l1ght5p33d: Too much information to visualize whole cell, you probably want to reduce complexity there
THX1342: mutrx wut lanaluHuh
rgbeezus: tryna get partnered
C0deCane: @zoogaezee hes making a stronger virus that can beat up the other virus
tensorspac3: yea
Nussinov: @mutrx there's probably at least SOME interpolation happening
timi13462: that's old news
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz https://vimeo.com/361099778
vicmoney69: Yeah thats why it has common cold symptoms
AresRai: they all reuse the source codes @georgehotz
passingremarks: i thought they all came from the same family
slurmdota2: colds are a coronavirus too
TsarSec: SARS is just an umbrella name @georgehotz influenza 'common cold' is related thats why people call it a 'flu'
directrix13: COVID-19 is a type of Sudden Acute Respiratory Syndrome
AzzoDio: What?
mutrx: @THX1342 like they're simulating the water molecule interactions, but what about all the reactions to?
tensorspac3: common cold = corona virus, Flu - Influenza
keith282: What is the edit difference between COVID19 and 229E?
THX1342: mutrx ohhhh ok.. I understoood what you meant now.. yeah I think it's mostly 'hand drawn'
levinson2504: corona git cloned common colds
mattdougherty22: @itsxaos thank you, I think it would be most interesting to reference like every question George or Peter Thiel has ever publicly answered, can be referenced much quicker
sunole: Cold is rhino virus, not corona
AzzoDio: 20% of positive tests did NOT have symptoms. They tested every person on the ship.
THX1342: mutrx I meant CGI not simulation
Ayyyy420Lmao: it's corona too @sunole
opus_000: congress has a package
TsarSec: you should prob do more research into influenza @georgehotz
dorkmo: god bless wikipedia
TsarSec: wikipedia andy LULW
Nussinov: wikipedia is god-tier for early research needs
itsxaos: @mattdougherty22 yea its good for looking stuff up you know you heard, searching stuff and also good if you want an outline of the conversation
gamerguy009: PogChamp
THX1342: georgehotz check this out https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Hk9jct2ozY
thrashtazs: @Nussinov factr
jimmyadaro: https://github.com/geohot/corona
b2kemann: Good morning
mattdougherty22: @itsxaos unfortunately the transcription tech isn't greats likely would have to crowdsource to scale. thanks for the feedback. Do you perhaps have a twitter I could ping you on?
AresRai: yup
jimmyadaro: Perhaps
THX1342: mutation?
TsarSec: good luck
AresRai: it evolves
mutrx: influenza mutates ALOT
jimmyadaro: "You need to let it go"
TsarSec: thats like the holy grail
LaheyFPS: it always changes
thecoder15: or we will never cure the coronavirus @georgehotz
PiroFloydian: cause theres a million different ones
itsChopsticks: viral mutations
CompestLive: The cold mutates
C0deCane: @THX1342 exactly
braininavatt: watch the pandemic show on netflix :)
tornpaperyoyos: its a virus
l1ght5p33d: you dont die from the cold you dont need anything people just die and the cold helps
THX1342: new strains every season
iGalactic: Not curing the common cold LUL
THX1342: perfect business model
inciMage: :(
Nussinov: colds are not really worth curing because theres like a billion things that could cause it
o______________________k: squadR hey DUD just stop colds DUD squadR
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: TheIlluminati
Waywoah: It mutates too fast
geobitz: corona mutations gonna be too fast, we have to create chrona cure
Mint2bSpiced: The common cold mutates too quickly
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Yes, on This Week in Virology they said it would have been easy to develop a broad spectrum coronavirus antiviral that would have worked against all of them, if we did in advance. Though the 'common cold' is not just coronaviruses, it has multiple.
mutrx: the Flu shot is comprised of what strains of influenza (bc if mutates so often) will be most prevalent each year @georgehotz
inciMage: its fkin changing bruh
iGalactic: Cancer industry is $$$
SolarBerry: imagine not curing the flu or common cold
xinthegame: https://www.twitch.tv/xinthegame
TsarSec: just cure influenza 4Head
itsxaos: ive stopped using twitter but ill get a notification @itxaos @mattdougherty22
dzid26: Cold is for boomers
360Plato: you may cause a selection bias to a more dangerous disease
paradox109: you can get vaccine every year. but it keeps evolving
cregger: why don't we just cure everything? i dont get it 4Head
wholesome_pepe: cuz it mutates every year
inciMage: just cure lungs
iGalactic: Inb4 mandatory vaccines
killmov3s: what he is working on?
zoogaezee: You think its easy to find a "CURE" for a rapidly mutating virus , that your own body's antibodies dont always work for?
THX1342: georgehotz https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Hk9jct2ozY
C0deCane: H1
cregger: @iGalactic sooner than you think
zoogaezee: WHY IS THERE NO VACCINE FOR AIDS?
jimmyadaro: LUL
Nussinov: just dont eat fast food 4Head
directrix13: exercise
gamerguy009: Bitchute . Com
tornpaperyoyos: CRISPR
peter35_: cure aging FeelsBadMan
geobitz: bad proteins
mutrx: cancer EZ
vybster: shouldn't everything be curable with stem cells CRISPR?
itsChopsticks: cancer is vague.
iGalactic: How do we reverse the aging process 🤔
itsxaos: @mattdougherty22 im sorry its @itsxaos like my twitch
THX1342: we don't even understand the source of AZ yet
mutrx: telomere bruh moment
inciMage: @zoogaezee there is all monkeys are vaccined :)
AzzoDio: @georgehotz There is also someone working on a total flu vaccine, though right now he's working on a monoclonal antibody for this virus. https://twitter.com/CurlyJungleJake/status/1242553710183514112
Nussinov: bruh moment
itsChopsticks: you can't cure cancer because there are so many types of cancer.
360Plato: cure alzeihmers by flossing
techtim123: heavy metals in a vaccine a good idea?
TsarSec: why?
not_bucket: What if you read Philosophy? How do you assume you will think of yourself then? @georgehotz
WhiteTailedSpider: :D
cregger: upload consciousness to AI 5Head
TsarSec: why is the cold different in your mind
Nussinov: comma.bio
iGalactic: LUL
raystriker98: hantavirus is now a thing too?
TsarSec: its just as hard of a problem as cancer
vybster: stem cells CRISPR
gamerguy009: Revere engineer chemtrails
o______________________k: politics DUD whata fucked up day DUD squadR squadR
jimmyadaro: @Nussinov I heard before it's like $70 something
wholesome_pepe: crispr synthetic mRNA
DecayingSkullz: There’s at least 160 different strains, or serotypes, of rhinovirus
b2kemann: Exersice
TsarSec: your body fights cancer too
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Bill Gates makes this point, how just a small investment would pay 100 or 1000 times in economic benefit, if you look at the whole world rather than just a drug company balance sheet.
barkazzaz: can you explain why you think it's possible to cure easily?
TsarSec: thats not a great argument
cregger: white blood cells PogChamp
tornpaperyoyos: In the future CRISPR will cure all
not_bucket: Heart disease is not a virus
PiroFloydian: probably not worth the effort to cure every cold considering the relatively small impact it has @georgehotz
jimmyadaro: @barkazzaz He's high? idk
Nussinov: your body fights alzheimers LUL im not sure where this is going
thecoder15: @georgehotz isn't cancer and heart disease pretty close like they are both rogue cells?
jimmyadaro: NOBODY
toasty_jk2: herpes bothers me too. Like 1 in 4 has it and you have it for the rest of your life
elephantpandas: nobody
jimmyadaro: not possible
barkazzaz: @jimmyadaro probably LUL
itsxaos: me :)
cregger: no one :(
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: wut LUL
jimmyadaro: :(
CompestLive: He forgot he altimeters
tornpaperyoyos: @Nussinov how
miiiiiiim: our bodies are killing cancers in our body every day
zoogaezee: Alzhemiers is permanent damage to your brain cells , its like cutting off your leg , no repairing dead cells
jimmyadaro: Q&A??
wholesome_pepe: cure aging or telomere attrition
pz3300: Cancer is immortal
Nussinov: what if you die before your cold is fixed, does your body now not fight the cold?
tsAllySparkles: it's like trying to cure necrosis vs trying to heal a wound
360Plato: alzheimers linked to gum disease
CompestLive: A person with altimeters forgets he has altimeters, easy cure kappa
iGalactic: What’s the youngest age someone’s gotten Alzheimer’s at?
xinthegame: https://www.twitch.tv/xinthegame
itsxaos: incels
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Drug Companies lose a lot of money on vaccines, they were especially burned by all the failed Ebola efforts. When the virus dies off there's no market. It's tough.
itsChopsticks: i have a herpes immunity :)
jimmyadaro: @iGalactic
jimmyadaro: 40 something i think
phrixus_bro: incels
Ayyyy420Lmao: i'm part of the 10% because im a kissless virgin
Nussinov: disease isnt something simple that can be "fought" against or not fought against
THX1342: iGalactic I don't remember
AresRai: @Nussinov no energy = no heat = no defense, drop by 1 degree and system shut down probs
cregger: xqcC
jesor24: Hello, Sorry off topic, do you have a macbook pro 13 2017?
jimmyadaro: @Ayyyy420Lmao But you're cool!
geobitz: effects on us arent bad
ShredderSherlock: @georgehotz what about lyme disease?
vruthlessv: maybe we are more resistiant to it
C0deCane: @raystriker98 hantavirus there is only one known kind that is transmissible and it is extremely rare and only been found in Africa. Hopefully this isn't something like that shit
Ayyyy420Lmao: @jimmyadaro not denying that
geobitz: i have simplex 2
geobitz: :)
miiiiiiim: 1 in 3 have HPV
iGalactic: @jimmyadaro really??
peter35_: Ayyyy420Lmao same bro FeelsBadMan
Br4nnon: LUL
phrixus_bro: nah
jimmyadaro: I didnt
mattdougherty22: go on The Portal Geeorge
AzzoDio: @georgehotz We do have HSV vaccines though!
roystang: how did u know
braininavatt: that'd be me :)
timi13462: no
vicmoney69: LUL
tornpaperyoyos: i do..... not
cregger: not me PogChamp
Nussinov: jokes on you im a virgin stemlord
l1ttlemtman: already solved ?
iuciferdk: this is twitch chat, the same ratios dont apply
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: monkaW
iGalactic: D;
itsChopsticks: i have an immunity to herpes. thank you nordic genes.
geobitz: no
itsxaos: sometimes i have somethign on my lips i think its probably herpes
pz3300: I haven’t got it
vicmoney69: monkaW
opus_000: DatSheffy
tornpaperyoyos: YOU GOT TESTED FOR HERPES
360Plato: I got it was ok
daxyxy98: is there a cure for ligma yet?
theseusq: i dont so must be u @georgehotz :)
guinness84: im the suspect
zoogaezee: During 2015–2016, prevalence of herpes simplex virus type 1 (HSV-1) was 47.8%, and prevalence of herpes simplex virus type 2 (HSV-2) was 11.9%.
pjayys77: jokes on you everyone's virgin's in chat
jesor24: Hello, Sorry off topic, do you have a macbook pro 13 2017?
tsAllySparkles: herpes tests only show positive if you're symptomatic
geobitz: breakouts never happen and testin for herpes can tricky
vicmoney69: ^
zoogaezee: in Persons Aged 14–49: United States, 2015–2016
geobitz: if no outbreak , you cant detect
orientalfish88: can cannabis cure covid20?
cregger: i've had a mouth sore though
Ayyyy420Lmao: after the hooker binge lmao
tsAllySparkles: yeah. i have done full panel tests every month for two years
pz3300: Your girl could have it and you fuck her every day for 5 years and don’t get it
itsxaos: mad curious about why you got that test
tornpaperyoyos: You speak as if you get std test often LUL
AresRai: kinda fucked up how alot viruses you had in your life stay in your body hidden forever @georgehotz
tsAllySparkles: yes
jimmyadaro: @pz3300 but how
l1ght5p33d: i haven't had sex in three years
tsAllySparkles: talenttestingservice.com
ahahahaitslit: lmfao
subconix: they are hiding the cold cure LUL
miiiiiiim: back before the lockdown i was arguing with someone about colloidal silver. it was so depressing
pz3300: How what?
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: squadW
TsarSec: just think of biological warfare as cyberwarfare @georgehotz, the programs gonna have vulnerabilities and they will eventually get exploited, a virus is just exploiting cell mechanisms
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Korea is working on antibody coronavirus tests, 10 minutes, portable, could give to every single person as they enter a public event
zoogaezee: be careful you heard about that fucking drug resistant goneherea
wholesome_pepe: OP genetic endowment
cregger: no women here so we're good Kappa
tsAllySparkles: services lol
TsarSec: there will never be a human w/o vulns
tsAllySparkles: yeah
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: squadW why not for man ??
jimmyadaro: LUL
geobitz: why did we bring up my genital warts?
Br4nnon: rofl
toasty_jk2: LUL
benchai18: @zoogaezee WTF r u talking about. Don’t play rn
360Plato: vaccine for men but no test for some reason
vicmoney69: LUL
zoogaezee: be careful you heard about that fucking drug resistant gonorrhea - it only has like 1 more antibiotic left that even works
tsAllySparkles: it's like the only PASS regulated provider
jesor24: Hello, Sorry off topic, do you have a macbook pro 13 2017? Maybe someone in the chat knows?
inciMage: apply
braininavatt: SeemsGood
THX1342: capitalism LUL
itsxaos: porn and prostitutes probably
caypoh: Broh, takes some bioinformatics courses before 'analizing' coronavirus ;)
tsAllySparkles: lmao
doctorgenus: what if herpes is the cure to coronavirus?
thecoder15: dude gonorhea sounds terrbile
vbrayon: Você pensa que o Flamengo é time?
doctorgenus: catch 22 yoooo
TsarSec: imagine paying for an STD test PepeLaugh
b2kemann: Chewing ice is the cure for herpise
iGalactic: Scam
l1ght5p33d: imagine paying for an STD
tsAllySparkles: trep sure eia is a vaginal swab
benchai18: I got hep c from a bad dope rig
pz3300: Are you talent.lol
jesor24: Hello, Sorry off topic, do you have a macbook pro 13 2017? Maybe someone in the chat knows?===========
benchai18: ^ jk. But my uncle did
tsAllySparkles: yes
jimmyadaro: @jesor24 I do
zoogaezee: there is a CURE for hep C now though
tornpaperyoyos: The real question is: why do you get std tests so often?? LUL
zoogaezee: Shouldnt HEP C go exctinct since they have a cure
geobitz: hep c is most common and easily spread, also curable
tsAllySparkles: i spend most of my time doing web dev now, haven't filmed since last fall
tsAllySparkles: also hacking my kia forte to have smart cruise control even though it's not equipped with it
360Plato: @jesor24 are you trying reserch for hardware attack lol
DecayingSkullz: @jesor24 He has a 2019 16in macbook pro
benchai18: @zoogaezee It’s not a cure. It reduces Viral cell count to minuscule
geobitz: hep b is in ficese i think
jimmyadaro: @jesor24 Watchu need
tornpaperyoyos: The real question is: why do you get std tests so often??? LUL
toasty_jk2: LUL
jimmyadaro: LUL
theonlymonkas: LUL
cregger: PogU
tsAllySparkles: words for the wise
jimmyadaro: WASH UR HANDS
jimmyadaro: MF
benchai18: My uncle had a liver transplant from hep c complications
peter35_: not engineered monkaS
360Plato: screwing a prostitute really cost 700$ with tesating
roystang: isnt the coranavirus super small?
cregger: emongHUGE
phrixus_bro: coronavirus is like godzilla
gamerguy009: Geo prob bangs lots of escorts
wisamalrawi: I like his apartment
TsarSec: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OR_7h5DaI-E
jimmyadaro: lmao
zoogaezee: @benchai18 Yeah but • people take it once for a month and than have no HEP C Viral in their blood for the rest of their life , isnt that a cure
braininavatt: Clap
theonlymonkas: 20 sec!
jesor24: @jimmyadaro @DecayingSkullz @360Plato Thank U
DecayingSkullz: Coronavirus engine for backspace.ai
tornpaperyoyos: The real question is: why do you get std tests so often?? LUL
vicmoney69: !uptime
whyZaya: 20!
3310: Is he doing coke?
jimmyadaro: WASH MORE
braininavatt: proud of you george
360Plato: @gamerguy009 better then being an incel
jimmyadaro: lmao
jimmyadaro: and eat garlic
jimmyadaro: and onions
jimmyadaro: we need ya alive
gamerguy009: Escorts much?/
DecayingSkullz: whats up with u and garlic
pz3300: Aromatics
braininavatt: ASMR Kreygasm
jimmyadaro: hahahhaa
PiroFloydian: Pog
zoogaezee: do you think adderall helps with programming?
equipollent_z: is that a mandarin oranges? I love mandarin oranges
jimmyadaro: sounds like fun
vicmoney69: PogChamp
gamerguy009: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
cregger: if you pay me in bitcoin and feed me McDoubles i'll let you give me Corona and do tests on me
TsarSec: why
williamjennings1: whip your CAWK out on stream
jimmyadaro: @zoogaezee Yep
theonlymonkas: NICE
tsAllySparkles: ah so you'll be 2 days clean of adderall eh?
geobitz: watch you fail for cocaine
TsarSec: we already know you dont have any stds
360Plato: @zoogaezee dumb question go away
jimmyadaro: Edibles are the shit
tsAllySparkles: you'll probably test like half positive for weed
cregger: it would
almonte550: What would be the limit of different viruses we can be immune of? Is there a limit?
jimmyadaro: Yep, it stays like 1 month
benchai18: HAHAHA
tornpaperyoyos: Adderall??
theonlymonkas: LUL
benchai18: nah, meth
williamjennings1: oh so you take addearall
doctorgenus: why do you need adderall? for work?
braininavatt: online drug test PogChamp
theonlymonkas: when
tsAllySparkles: 2 days adderall i called it
iGalactic: Have you taken psychedelics ?
cregger: i passed mine with a 16 day buffer PogChamp
tornpaperyoyos: Wait you actual;ly do take adderall??
localcanofdutchgold: "all of these"
pwnbase: you had better start studying now
pz3300: Make sure your girl bit watching the stream
benchai18: Dude he doesn’t take addy. He hits a pookie
TsarSec: occasionally Kapp
jimmyadaro: WIFI-BASED COVID TEST
geobitz: do hair test
tornpaperyoyos: RECREATIONALLY??
pz3300: Not
subconix: wait a minute... if COVID-19 is essentially just another "coronavirus" wouldnt we want to let it run its course so the population can build immunity?
pz3300: Blood for sure
360Plato: do tests even pick up adderal
b2kemann: Why are everyone so fixated om adderall??
zwisch: LUL
Ayyyy420Lmao: does ketamine give crosspositive for opioids?
rgbeezus: meth qualuudes
jimmyadaro: Like wOLFIE
esence: why would you take adderall
jimmyadaro: LMAO
benchai18: Lol. Small dose. I took 90 mg a few hours ago and it’s 11pm
PiroFloydian: what are quayludesL
edu4594: why d you use adderal
vicmoney69: LUL
DecayingSkullz: Wolf of Wall Street
AresRai: @b2kemann they want an excuse to do the same
cregger: GET THE LUDES
PiroFloydian: what are those?
tornpaperyoyos: So the truth comes out LUL adderall is the secret to george's success
iGalactic: Imagine thinking adderall is worth the come down LUL
benchai18: @pirofloydian The best thing ever
TsarSec: does adderall use put you in a higher risk bracket for rona's?
jimmyadaro: THOSE LUDES KICK'NG
theonlymonkas: peyote
ahahahaitslit: thoughts on psychedelics
itsxaos: ask bill cosby
benchai18: Methaqualone
benchai18: Lufes
cregger: IM NOT DYING SOBER
benchai18: LUDES
pz3300: Blow
PiroFloydian: @benchai18 *doubt*
benchai18: yes
rgbeezus: meth qualuudes seems like they would cancel out
tsAllySparkles: pcp test will test positive with ketamine, mxe and others
ShredderSherlock: drug tests should be illegal
AzzoDio: why is cannabis 30 days?
Ayyyy420Lmao: billy used roofies not ludes no?
360Plato: Lets make them in a bioprinter
DecayingSkullz: I WILL NOT DIE SOBER
cregger: lsd is the shit
williamjennings1: what about dxm
tsAllySparkles: dmt is the only cool one
pz3300: Ya
timi13462: look up cocaine
jimmyadaro: @AzzoDio It's the way it is
tsAllySparkles: yeah that will as well
benchai18: Y’all don’t know. LUDES were the best thing ever. Barbs too
equipollent_z: fractals man
sunole: Lots of ways to screw
iGalactic: LSD will open your mind ;)
benchai18: GEORGE. SYNTHESIZE TUINAL
Ayyyy420Lmao: @benchai18 ok boomer
benchai18: YOU WILL BE A LEGEND
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz what are ludes?
jimmyadaro: I will stick wth weed tho
equipollent_z: the 2.5D universe
pz3300: Wet blunts man
gamerguy009: Smoke crack its always fun LOL
tsAllySparkles: only on an much higher than fda approved dose would dxm test positive
benchai18: @ayyyy420lmao I’m 30 chill bro. Just connected
THX1342: LSD in the desert is a cool thing
ConnorMusarra: tune in, turn on & drop out
geobitz: do you believe in a god?
itsxaos: heroin?
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: joe rogan time PogU
l1ght5p33d: U guys all dissapoint me
ImJ4Gu4R: "quite"
Ayyyy420Lmao: ketamine?
Andremm2: acid is great
itsxaos: alcohol?
pz3300: Drop out
Santiago_LHC: Love?
thecoder15: lol cocaine is an amphetamine @georgehotz
tornpaperyoyos: Slightly positive on amphetamines???
Hawklite: do you think drugs are essential to answer some questions? or can all questions be answered without drugs?
iGalactic: Lol my man tried it all
cregger: plenty of lsd experience, all good times of self-reflection
C0deCane: @georgehotz but he would never recommend any of this to you chat. Kappa
rndmsqnce: when was your last trip
TsarSec: opiods monkaS
dairynuts: WHAT IS THIS
williamjennings1: kratom
benchai18: George. TUINAL man.
b2kemann: McKenna ?
Ayyyy420Lmao: @thecoder15 lmao @ u
vicmoney69: meth monkaS
pz3300: Turn on, tune in, drop out
Br4nnon: i just drink tea
itsxaos: DMT?
Abnico: sexy time is good on mushshrooms
iGalactic: Smoke weed then take a hefty dose of acid & take 3 hits of DMT at the peak then report back ;)
pwnbase: have you done enough mdma to lose the magic
Santiago_LHC: "Full trip"
C0deCane: Stay in School kids don't do drugs LUL good luck with that now
theonlymonkas: gaming time
tsAllySparkles: culturally you're like elon musk's little cousin
pz3300: Negative on mdma
benchai18: Any other ex H junkies in here??? Besides me
geobitz: do you believe in a god?
360Plato: Opioids are for when your done being productive
almonte550: That was when you founded comma ai?
ahahahaitslit: any bad trips on them?
pz3300: Must of been shit swag george
un3okapi: what are your thoughts on love?
Abnico: burning man gonna be cancelled
l1ght5p33d: You can die from all of it first time more likely
SolarBerry: psychedelics are too crazy for me i'm already tripping day and night
benchai18: George. When u dissected checkm8, you had a chick over
benchai18: Who was she
TsarSec: did you see this yet @georgehotz https://i.imgur.com/3nXp0ni.mp4
inatreecrown: why not
pz3300: Negative thoughts on ecstasy’s?
gamerguy009: Whiskey mushrooms and a machete
cregger: can you imagine the shit george says when tripping holy shit i'd pay to be there
tornpaperyoyos: This stream is very eye opening on george's drug use LUL
peter35_: it's a warm hug, for me at least
barkazzaz: why would you use these things tho?
THX1342: SOMA
theonlymonkas: thoughts on peyote
ahahahaitslit: lmfao
geobitz: id get fucked up offa bean
PiroFloydian: thats fuckin scary man
jimmyadaro: @cregger Same
pz3300: Tripping while swimming in the sea is awesome
Ayyyy420Lmao: no, mescaline
tsAllySparkles: no
TsarSec: spirit molecule Pog
christianthefalco: just saw your Lex Fridman interview. so good!
williamjennings1: what about ssri's
equipollent_z: doesn't peyote make you puke?
cregger: tripping and VR is the bomb
vicmoney69: ioaska monkaS
jimmyadaro: @equipollent_z Sometimes
iGalactic: Infinite DMT trip when we die? 🤔
oGobby: just had a crazy good trip on shrooms
maxprogram: finally found it, this guy explains why no cold/flu vaccine here (economics) https://threadreaderapp.com/thread/1240498037958545410.html
geobitz: u dont wnat payote
360Plato: you feel warm and numb on opioids
Ayyyy420Lmao: thoughts on ketamine?
esence: IVE NEVER TAKEN DRUGS, AM I MISSING OUT?
geobitz: its supposed to suck alot
b2kemann: What do your mom say to all this geo??
pz3300: Your a smack heeed
christianthefalco: @iGalactic you wish
SolarBerry: what about blueberry concentrate
benchai18: Y’all. Opioids changes what matters to u. I was on a 10 year run. Started with Oxy’s, ended up shooting black for years... IF U CAN SHOOT DOPE LIKE A GENTLEMAN, I WOULD HIGHLY RECOMMEND IT!!!!! But alas, I can’t
almonte550: Did you founded comma ai before or after the full trip?
edu4594: @esence hell yea
AzzoDio: Czech Republic, 100% mask usage in 10 days: https://twitter.com/jeremyphoward/status/1242572288962240517
vicmoney69: @esence yes
C0deCane: @cregger I just imagine some dipshit breaking his new Index LUL
iGalactic: @christianthefalco well why does so much of it release when we die?
pz3300: Cactus
Sidhuu: high doses of dextromethorphan cures everything
williamjennings1: lol
theonlymonkas: now what
pz3300: Shite
thecoder15: lo
cregger: @C0deCane its safer on the comedown
jimmyadaro: We need @georgehotz high af on DMT, live, on Twitch!
theonlymonkas: ResidentSleeper
gamerguy009: Coke is fun to cook in a spoon
Santiago_LHC: @esence It's like sex, a lot of it is hyped.
williamjennings1: are we breaking rules on twitch
TsarSec: young people are way less affected
christianthefalco: @iGalactic times passes when you're tripping on DMT. It's just weird and slow
pz3300: There’s a reason people been doing cocaine fir thousands of years
guacDev: What do you think about krokodil
opus_000: DMT is overrated
condoram: The drug?
cregger: xqcTOS
pz3300: Yabba
ImJ4Gu4R: How about kratom
benchai18: @gamerguy009 Sure is. Esp when you’re making a speedball
condoram: No drug talk y0
ahahahaitslit: how long does dmt last? 20 mins?
TsarSec: you should look into how vaccines work
cregger: NO SNITCHES
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Yes, the hypothesis is kids are immune. Old hypothesis. Being worked on. It's OC43 specifically though
pz3300: 10-15
benchai18: @pz3300 Yabba is tweak right? In Thailand?
itsxaos: still did the stream tho king
ImJ4Gu4R: @pz3300 thats shit horse pil
프랑2: if you are immune to the virus version that you got infected but if you got a evolved version of it... it repeats over and over
AzzoDio: Not immune, but better outcomes, because of greater oc43 exposure
iGalactic: They think O blood type might be immune @georgehotz
pz3300: Snitches get ditches
almonte550: Do you mean that being immune to sars 1 will make you immune to sars 2 and viceversa?
condoram: This is the FBI you are all under arrest due to being 13 and talking about drugs
TsarSec: its mostly the human immune system that generates a cure
AzzoDio: @georgehotz https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC2095096/pdf/JIDMM17330.pdf
ahahahaitslit: lmao
equipollent_z: aren't there good biohackers in Oakland?
C0deCane: @condoram geohotz is a bio engineer this was merely a scientific study
jimmyadaro: @condoram wtf
Ayyyy420Lmao: you're implying it's sequenced and youll get a hit when searching the sequence man
tornpaperyoyos: Seriously? YES IM O-NEG
theonlymonkas: what were the symptoms
wisamalrawi: I'm O-
toasty_jk2: a cold lasts for 1 week w/o medication or 7 days with
AresRai: O Type gang
Br4nnon: How strong is the immune system on a general level
condoram: I thought he was a college dropout?
tbodt_: is this an xkcd reenactment stream
Sidhuu: is it bad to want corona just to see how it feels
tornpaperyoyos: YES
jimmyadaro: O J Simpson Gang
tornpaperyoyos: IM O-NEG
rgbeezus: how do you know your blood type
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Also this, newer data http://virological.org/t/remarkable-age-distribution-of-oc43-vs-sars-cov-2-in-china/399
AresRai: @wisamalrawi same we give to everyone and receive only from each other :(
wisamalrawi: I heard blood type A is most sensitive to Corona
SolarBerry: i just read an anecdote from someone O blood type who had terrible symptoms from the coronavirus
opus_000: O ftw
williamjennings1: george should make his own strain of weed
C0deCane: my brother has O blood type im bout to drain him LUL Kappa
benchai18: How tf y’all know ur blood type.
condoram: aww but I am blood type A I believe
benchai18: It’s true. And A is worst
pz3300: George will be pissing in bottles next week like Howard hughes
localcanofdutchgold: is it immunity or affects you less
Santiago_LHC: @benchai18 it's in your blood work
jimmyadaro: @williamjennings1 "Comma Weed"?
iGalactic: Maybe not immune but less likely .. I don’t have a link sorry just been hearing that a lot
benchai18: @santiago_lhc I never looked at that shit. Prob shoulda. I rly was a junkie though... sooooo yeah. I was checked out for a decade
condoram: @benchai18 if you cut your finger the color of the blood decides your type
oGobby: #LI5
AzzoDio: Serological = antibody tests
b2kemann: Lizards are immune. Coincidens?
oGobby: ELI5
theonlymonkas: O negative or positive?
jimmyadaro: @b2kemann lmao
almonte550: How do you know so much about herpes again?
Ayyyy420Lmao: @b2kemann mind = blown
pz3300: If it’s green your a lizard
condoram: His mom had it
jimmyadaro: @almonte550 He had it
benchai18: @condoram Source? Send pantone palette so I can reference
jimmyadaro: @almonte550 fr
williamjennings1: comma weed
tornpaperyoyos: Im so happy to be o-negative right now
williamjennings1: igM vs lgG
jimmyadaro: Comma Weed seems alright
almonte550: @jimmyadaro makes so much sense
benchai18: Any Type O Negative fans round here?
equipollent_z: comma bio
joshperri: Test on your serums
Br4nnon: learning is fun
jimmyadaro: @almonte550 He was talking about that like 10 minutes ago
localcanofdutchgold: knowledge tree 5Head
tornpaperyoyos: @benchai18 Im o-neg
cregger: the real question is, has anyone seen any birds since quarantine?? NOPE because they are changing out their batteries
Mint2bSpiced: Try Elisa
condoram: I see plenty
almonte550: @jimmyadaro sorry I missed that
r3mote: Good morning :-)
jimmyadaro: SMALL PHARMA IS REAL B!TC#E$
benchai18: @tornpaperyoyos Nah I meant the band. Type O Negative. Lucky bastard u
theonlymonkas: i'm O negative
tornpaperyoyos: @benchai18 oh you mean the band LUL
pz3300: I say we drown all the people that don’t die if corona just in case
subconix: so its just a blood test?
Codeoxic: @georgehotz How long have you been working on this?
williamjennings1: its hurts my eyes to read chat sometimes
condoram: they just don't hang around where people used to because we are not there to drop shit for them
equipollent_z: can people who are immune pass that immunity to others?
jimmyadaro: @equipollent_z Yep
THX1342: as long as there is no reinfection. we'll know from wuhan soon
benchai18: @tornpaperyoyos Yo lemme get a few pints of that fine shit.
condoram: Only through sex, equ
jimmyadaro: @equipollent_z That's the main issue
condoram: Go make your parents immune!
benchai18: Cuomo’s kind of a twat
benchai18: Sorry
iuciferdk: https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2020.03.11.20031096v1 blood type
Sidhuu: @condoram WeirdChamp
cregger: lets just colonize Mars and leave Corona behind
oGobby: so O- negative blood type is immune to corona
AzzoDio: @georgehotz The hypothesis is that previous OC43 infections explains why children tend to do so well: http://virological.org/t/remarkable-age-distribution-of-oc43-vs-sars-cov-2-in-china/399
gamerguy009: Prepare the gas showers
almonte550: @oGobby wait what
Mint2bSpiced: Serological test are usually ELISA based unless they are POC (point of care) like lateral flow tests
Br4nnon: I'm ready to leave Earth Kappa
equipollent_z: I remember hearing something about married donors not able to share organs, maybe it had to do with sex also
doctorgenus: what time do you sleep @georgehotz
condoram: The thing is even young adults do well
l1ght5p33d: reverse transcriptase PCR is the most vague general term
benchai18: @mint2bspiced LAM ELISA = TB test no?
williamjennings1: dang his gonna be up!
williamjennings1: not sleeping until 6am
gamerguy009: Take me to mars
theonlymonkas: LUL
peter35_: in the coffee zone FeelsGoodMan
phrixus_bro: no sleep until vaccine
equipollent_z: are there med students in the chat too?
williamjennings1: drink more coffee
cregger: no sleep until rocket
opus_000: I'm here for the energy
iuciferdk: @georgehotz "CONCLUSION People with blood group A have a significantly higher risk for acquiring COVID-19 compared with non-A blood groups, whereas blood group O has a significantly lower risk for the infection compared with non-O blood groups." https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2020.03.11.20031096v1
condoram: I used to study medical lab science but ended up switching to CS
benchai18: Anyone else here ever had Consumption?? Shit’s vicious
williamjennings1: can you shotgun a coffee on stream
thrashtazs: yeah wait are there any med students to back up what hes talking about
gamerguy009: Corona. Py LOL
pjayys77: any one into cold brew
Mint2bSpiced: @benchai18 yes
gamerguy009: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz USE GOOGLE SCHOLAR
Ayyyy420Lmao: dying from comon cold? KappaPride
Nussinov: "Is the Flu the Cold" LUL
equipollent_z: I feel like I'm watching the OverTheWire Bandit version of Corona
cregger: WAPO ResidentSleeper
theonlymonkas: and who answers to those questions?
vicmoney69: use duckduckgo
benchai18: @mint2bspiced Shit’s rough huh? U had that White Plague?
iGalactic: Jew York times LUL
williamjennings1: @pjayys77 kind of want one
tornpaperyoyos: Washington "Abu Bakr Albagdadi is an austere scholar" Post LUL
Nussinov: @vicmoney69 what a terrible suggestion LUL
r3mote: exclude sites with "-"
gamerguy009: We are a cult
condoram: Google scholar is babe
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Only like 15% of colds are coronavirus, there are many others
equipollent_z: maybe a lot more advanced than Bandit
tsAllySparkles: go to scholar.google.com
THX1342: duckduckgo > 1st result is CDC LUL
benchai18: @mint2bspiced Oops. Ignore
condoram: https://scholar.google.dk/
vicmoney69: @Nussinov ? why
tsAllySparkles: lmao
tsAllySparkles: im tired
jimmyadaro: Going full med student right there
jimmyadaro: @tsAllySparkles Same
equipollent_z: immune2own
benchai18: @mint2bspiced I thought you were saying “yes” when I asked if anyone has had consumption
Nussinov: @vicmoney69 it is not helpful to suggest that is what Im saying
THX1342: LUL
b2kemann: Next time se should do economics. Find out when the dollar is gonna crash
THX1342: names and logos
condoram: aaand back to IT! Yay
THX1342: we need Corona logo
Zazens: scholar.google.com @georgehotz is pretty good
cregger: i'm getting sleepy can you make the vaccine already
Br4nnon: meltdown
THX1342: call the bizdev guys
Tyrant_01: GEORGE WOULD YOU ENCOURAGE ME TO STUDY FOR PROGRAMMER OR NETWORKING SO I CAN HAVE I BETTER BASE FOR HACKING...OR PROGRAMMER JUST MAKE STUFF IN GENERAL
itsxaos: it was a pretty crazy bug tho
condoram: https://scholar.google.dk/
jimmyadaro: @Tyrant_01 wtf is wrong with you
benchai18: GEORGE. MY FAV WAS THE ANNA KOURNAKOVA WORM
condoram: DK version is superior
pz3300: I’m off george. It’s 5am. If I don’t see you through the week, I’ll see you through the window
Br4nnon: PogChamp whole new world
Ayyyy420Lmao: when are you hacking reality??
vicmoney69: PogChamp
williamjennings1: comma ai
jimmyadaro: @pz3300 Check out his YT channel later on
benchai18: Deez nuts finna do it for u
pz3300: Cool. In a bit dude
christianthefalco: Do not get into biohacking. Biology doesn't follow simple rules like software. It's ALL spaghetti code
almonte550: @georgehotz must look -> https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/18818423/
tornpaperyoyos: Washington "Abu Bakr Albagdadi is an austere scholar" Post LUL
williamjennings1: YAAASSSS
benchai18: What does a car decoder do?
Ayyyy420Lmao: there's no skoda in there man
Mrclutch963: Do you meditate? @georgehotz
ShredderSherlock: lol are manufacturers ok with that
theonlymonkas: LUL
jimmyadaro: @pz3300 "Comma AI archive" on YouTube
vicmoney69: LUL
b2kemann: Lol
benchai18: How do u interface with the car George?????? Not that OBD shit right???????
PiroFloydian: WutFace
theonlymonkas: PogChamp
JohnEGQ: we all meditated together yesterday on air
C0deCane: LUL @georgehotz do you use CBD oil
localcanofdutchgold: didn't he say the opposite last stream ?
360Plato: I can hack the rats first
PiroFloydian: cmonBruh
Santiago_LHC: @Mrclutch963 He has medidated on stream many times
c1tr0n75: cheer50
williamjennings1: can you make comma ai drift by itself
ahahahaitslit: i think so lmao
b2kemann: Hack ALL the cars
iGalactic: Do you use essential oils pepega
theonlymonkas: only yesterday
THX1342: anti-histo... isn't this allergy related?
Nussinov: never meditated, thought about becoming a serial killer in his youth, streams on twitch --- we got ourselves an incel boys
jimmyadaro: @williamjennings1 That would be amazing
Nussinov: Kappa
benchai18: How do u interface with a standard car George?????? Like a Kia. Not that OBD shit right???????
pjayys77: you know what they say When in Rome... wait does that apply
jimmyadaro: ^^
itsxaos: oh thats right i forgot we meditated
Tyrant_01: So Hacker or programmer what is the way george...need you guidance man..
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 8 in the channel!
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 gifted a Tier 1 sub to mattdougherty22!
l1ght5p33d: I think this has been a complete success
doctorgenus: do you have enough TP for two weeks?
itsxaos: PogChamp free sub
Jehhred: How does it feel knowing that hot chicks are dancing on stream with triple the amount of viewers.. They aren't even good dancers........
jimmyadaro: @Tyrant_01 What you need to do? Or whant to do?
williamjennings1: can you make a program where you make the car do donuts
architectzs: bow long has geohot coded for anyone know?
jimmyadaro: want*
christianthefalco: @Tyrant_01 just become a programmer and have an easy life
DecayingSkullz: lets get a hype train going...
b2kemann: He also never chews ice
SofiaLouise: any tips on how to get into meditating?
0R4NG3: LMAO
AresRai: LUL
JohnEGQ: I'm watching BOTH
Nussinov: ^
tsAllySparkles: i'm actually working on a camgirl site that is more free speech oriented
condoram: Yea, start dancing for more views!
C0deCane: @Tyrant_01 Hes a jack of all trades, master of some
tsAllySparkles: webrtc is tricky
benchai18: Y’all. How do I interface with a basic ass Kia
thebiggaeboi: talk about backspace
iGalactic: LUL
not_bucket: do you believe in god george?
jimmyadaro: PLAGUE INC!!!!
theonlymonkas: you still need to play
directrix13: dance for us @georgehotz
itsxaos: twitch thots are stupid, porn is free
THX1342: watch this later georgehotz https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Hk9jct2ozY
iGalactic: Simps smh
Roundlay: LUL
bytebacon: Sam Harris Waking Up is pretty cool too
ahahahaitslit: don't forget eric weinstein
cregger: do ASMR for us
ahahahaitslit: lmao
syrio16: ımhhhh amma head out
condoram: What time is it over in US?
C0deCane: LUL
benchai18: LEX FRIEDMAN
jimmyadaro: PLAGUE INC MF!
tsAllySparkles: i wanna make a twitch-like site that allows titties. current cam sites don't even allow TVs to be in frame even when they're off
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 9 in the channel!
dorkmo: to be honest ive been playing plauge inc
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 gifted a Tier 1 sub to brownyyyylocks!
l1ght5p33d: we already decided on some good treatments and running up against knowledge of the experts
theonlymonkas: gaming
jimmyadaro: PLAGUE INC! PLAGUE INC!
northumb: what time do you get up?
archeadis: @georgehotz is that tmux in ur terminal?
b2kemann: Georg is slowly transistioning into terence mckenna
condoram: @c1tr0n75 what does that mean the thing you are doing?
benchai18: I take huge pride knowing that I told George to watch Lex and some day they’ll talk about me
360Plato: Eric Weinstein is long
Ayyyy420Lmao: so meta
brownyyyylocks: @c1tr0n75 yo thank you!!
itsxaos: pneumo as in pneumonia
theonlymonkas: are you going to stream tomorrow?
itsxaos: yes
jimmyadaro: 4%
UniversalGeneve: water?
PiroFloydian: OH SHIT
itsxaos: h2o 4Head
PiroFloydian: THIS STUFF FUCKS YOU UP
archeadis: @georgehotz is that tmux in ur terminal??
pwnbase: sounds scary
jimmyadaro: COVID is 4% death rate
b2kemann: Miss the kong curly hair
Roundlay: Ugh
thebiggaeboi: LMAOOO
dairynuts: i love that
vicmoney69: water???
jimmyadaro: @archeadis Yep
C4TFive: killer chemicals man
vicmoney69: H2O
condoram: Dihydrogin monoxied? LOL that hoax
Nussinov: monkaS
directrix13: I'm drinking some right now
c1tr0n75: @condoram you mean gifting subs ?
benchai18: George’ll be like “this dude Ben told me to watch ur corona video. Fucking loved it dude. Thank god for Ben”
AzzoDio: We have lots of clusters where like 90% of the cluster got infected. That seems unilkeyl
ahahahaitslit: water
thebiggaeboi: some quality bio right here
condoram: Did you know 100% of people that consumed dihydrogin monoxied died?
thecoder15: its wate ryou idiots
Ayyyy420Lmao: be careful if ur weed is not dried properly it has dihydrogen monoxide
jimmyadaro: PLAGUE INC
julien9877: H2O monkaS
condoram: or will die!
theonlymonkas: oxygen can
iGalactic: monkaHmm
JdPaulBlart: so covid19=water?
dairynuts: ?? how are you comparing covid19 to....that? a bit of a mischaracterization, no?
williamjennings1: so much clutterr
architectzs: what is george’s iq lmao i’m curious ?
condoram: @c1tr0n75 ah, well don't gift me, I am not a regular on twitch. I just come to see george sometimes
Ayyyy420Lmao: @dairynuts water is more dangerous, at least i can drown on it
jimmyadaro: @condoram Same
dairynuts: @architectzs maybe 110
julien9877: @georgehotz maybe it doesnt spread as fast?
localcanofdutchgold: rate of transmission?
THX1342: what's it's R0 tho
SolarBerry: that virus hasn't been collapsing world-class healthcare systems
pjayys77: is it time to detab
b2kemann: Lol great troll
itsxaos: yea a big problem is that its new and we dont know how it will develop
benchai18: Can I be serious for one second. NOT kidding now. I would pay $11,000 plus expenses to get George and Joey Diaz in a convo
jimmyadaro: 3:25 am here, i'm tired
c1tr0n75: @condoram it's really to support George streams, the persons who gets gifted are totally random
benchai18: Anyone want in on this?
FlightOfGrey: Isn't it because of the combination of transmission rate and the death rate as well as symptoms requiring hospitalisation
Nussinov: read the WAPO article Kappa
equipollent_z: did anyone ever identify which lab it originated from?
opus_000: TheIlluminati
benchai18: Hotz / Diaz 2020
architectzs: what is the thing he has on the top left of screen
Br4nnon: @FlightOfGrey yup
jimmyadaro: @architectzs VIM
architectzs: vim?
Mrclutch963: Who is eric weinstein? @georgehotz
ahahahaitslit: george how much to see you do shrooms on stream
tsAllySparkles: it's tmux with vim
b2kemann: But r0?
benchai18: @architectzs It’s a terminal window running Vim. It’s on his GitHub
miiiiiiim: there are more metrics to it than just mortality rate......
tsAllySparkles: vim is a text editor for a terminal
ConnorMusarra: the death rate will skyrocket when hospitals can no longer sustain everyone ie italy
tsAllySparkles: tmux is a terminal multiplexer
Mint2bSpiced: It has to do with how fast it can spread and IF it mutates with a higher mortality rate...
vicmoney69: betacoronavirus? so it is a bioweapon monkaS
theonlymonkas: emacs
architectzs: will it work on windows?
architectzs: in cmd?
tsAllySparkles: with windows subsystem for linux enabled
tsAllySparkles: or with cygwin
tsAllySparkles: probably
jimmyadaro: @architectzs Maybe, just buy a Mac or use a virtual machine with Linux
benchai18: @architectzs @jimmyadaro will come through with the GitHub link for u. He’s a legend
Abnico: الله أكبر الله أكبر الله أكبر
tsAllySparkles: just get wsl
jimmyadaro: F!ck windows
nremind: use wsl with windows
boengels: still going!! Dude you are a machine!! :D Love your work
condoram: Yea, as long as the health systems are capable then we will not have a massive death rate
condoram: but yeah, act too slow and you end up in Italy situation
jimmyadaro: @architectzs https://github.com/geohot/
benchai18: @boengels He smokes meth dude. He just told us a few min ago
ahahahaitslit: the health system is ass for most countries
architectzs: scale of 1-10 how much better is linux compared to windows
Br4nnon: hospitals only have so many beds LUL
dr_set: corona is supposed to be between 10 to 20 times more deathly than the flu, but data is trash so we don't really know
jimmyadaro: @dr_set Isn't death rate like 4%?
benchai18: @dr_set Yup. And sample size is in flux and LIKELY very inadequate
ahahahaitslit: too many journalists raping the data also
AresRai: @jimmyadaro cant know how many infected there really are thats the prob
dr_set: some regions of china say 0,4 others, 4%
vicmoney69: @architectzs 0 for casual use cause a lot of programs dont work in linux. If u have a decent pc u can get a linux virtual machine
dr_set: so data is trash
Ayyyy420Lmao: @jimmyadaro nah infected is probably way higher than reported
jimmyadaro: @Ayyyy420Lmao In China maybe
c1tr0n75: @jimmyadaro no because they are not testing everybody so the total infected numbers are not right
benchai18: @jimmyadaro Even fatality rate of 4% isn’t necessarily true. Likely way more people infected that aren’t accounted for
dr_set: the cruise ship had 1% and that is a older people population
nremind: @architectzs 9, only thing windows is better at is games and maybe some apps like onenote
THX1342: what I'
jimmyadaro: @nremind Word
c1tr0n75: @jimmyadaro actually, the best experiment we had is the Diamond Princess
condoram: With 422989 recorded cases and a death of 18919 it ends up to 4.47% death rate
Ayyyy420Lmao: @jimmyadaro not because their hiding it but because asymptomatic or lil simptoms not enough testing
jimmyadaro: @c1tr0n75 What is that?
C0deCane: @architectzs Check out linux mint I think you'll like it if your like trying to convert or something
benchai18: @dr_set And Italy has the highest population of elderly people
PiroFloydian: DansGame
dairynuts: 20 tabs of chromium based browser open...
jimmyadaro: @dairynuts So?
condoram: Italy helped a lot with getting the death rate up, not sure if all countries will have the same fate
architectzs: i still play games with linux fuck it up?
CheeseManUchiha: tab gang
benchai18: @jimmyadaro Cruise ship
dairynuts: @jimmyadaro im jealous
THX1342: what I've heard from doctors in the front line is that the great difference between covid and a flu is the general condition of people who have bad to severe cases. covid is way more aggressive and demands a lot more resources to stabilize
Ayyyy420Lmao: @architectzs just get dualboot
dairynuts: my comp would freez
C0deCane: @architectzs not really
l1ght5p33d: get Ubuntu if you want linux
condoram: I use arch btw
AzzoDio: @georgehotz From what I understand, people expect this virus to eventually turn into a recurring common cold type virus with very mild symptoms, after years have by and basically everyone has antibodies forit
nremind: yeah I dualboot, but most games are windows native
l1ght5p33d: actually i take that back Ubuntu if you actually program
dr_set: @benchai18 yes, Italy is a bad sample, to many old people, but still I wan't to see the numbers in a couple of weeks
c1tr0n75: @jimmyadaro well, it's a boat stuck in Japan, with someone in it who had the virus. since no body got in or out and everybody got tested, we know that in a scenario like that similar to a laboratory test, the mortality is arount 1%
jimmyadaro: @AzzoDio Sounds right
equipollent_z: missed it, but is that an old corona virus
Br4nnon: Gotta dual boot if you play games
jimmyadaro: @c1tr0n75 With how many cases?
dairynuts: @architectzs you should get a VM. download vmware or virtualbox and install any linux distro you'd like
jimmyadaro: Like, how much people on that boat?
condoram: Also the virus mutates when it gets into a person. I forgot the source but the virus eventually becomes less aggressive
vicmoney69: 15-50 have a low death rate for both were safe LUL
equipollent_z: crazy
l1ght5p33d: if you don't know Linux by now i'm tempted to say just avoid it
architectzs: how helpful is linux? if i wanna mess around with a raspberry pi or something or just learn in general
bc10000: can you explain what is your goal here? i just joined
condoram: Italy is unfortunate because it is nr 2 on the list of countries with most old people and they acted way too late on lockdown
c1tr0n75: @jimmyadaro you can google it up man, Diamond Princess, 712 persons got the virus
vicmoney69: @bc10000 hes trying to cure COVID-19
Ayyyy420Lmao: @georgehotz thought on chainlink? do you know sergey nazarov?
dr_set: @jimmyadaro 3100 people on the boat 700 got the virus 8 died
jimmyadaro: @c1tr0n75 I'll check it out
THX1342: c1tr0n75 how much support do those people get on the ships, btw? do they have ICU setup inside the boat? that is also a factor
condoram: so their health system collapsed and now they need to pick between who should live
benchai18: @vicmoney69 Here’s a trippy thought for u. What if age is not the attribute that distinguishes infected.
THX1342: small sample?
nremind: I use linux for development and because it doesn't have a lot of spyware overhead. It doesn't offer much else over windows though
vicmoney69: @benchai18 did u see the chart
Maizlow90: What are you trying to do btw?
igg44705: finally caught the stream
K177: LUL
mik12f4: So are we going to be injected with OC43 to get protected?
condoram: I do however think US is going to be the country to end up having the most deaths in the long run, mostly due to lack of support for people that can't afford it
condoram: unless of course they change their shit around
C0deCane: @georgehotz if it does that just get the no script add on and get around it lUL
christianthefalco: Science people have finally started putting pressure on the publishing industry. It's awesome what's changed in the last couple years
AzzoDio: @georgehotz That can't be right, maybe 5% of people severe enough to be hospitalized?
K177: just find a cure 4Head
benchai18: @vicmoney69 No, but I’m suggesting that the correlation isn’t necessarily the cause.
Nussinov: LUL
directrix13: shit's hard
jimmyadaro: PLAGUE INC
benchai18: $$$$$
igg44705: how long has he been streaming for?
Abnico: PogChamp
Nussinov: because its too easy
Maizlow90: Anyone can explain what he is trying to do/accomplish?
condoram: Finding a cure would mean less money to hospitals because people don't need them
C0deCane: Probably because the regulations that they have to pass
directrix13: !uptime
AzzoDio: @georgehotz People tried to get funding for general coronavirus broad spectrum antiviral, years ago, never got off the ground.
condoram: It is not profitable to find a cure!
c1tr0n75: @THX1342 it depends on the countru that takes care of that situation. In the situation of Diamond Princess, it was really good actually, they sent medics and doctors by helicopters, got everybody tested, and keep in mind that, most of the passengers were elderly, and we only have a mortality of around 1,5%
Abnico: TriHard TriHard TriHard
benchai18: Yup
Abnico: BrainSlug BrainSlug BrainSlug
K177: its also not profitable to overwhelm hospitals and kill off their staff
C0deCane: plus also long term effect testing
equipollent_z: need the penicillin for viruses
pjayys77: Big Pharma rearing it's ugly head again
Abnico: SeriousSloth
condoram: That's what you get for having capitalism, money > people
benchai18: @k177 It’s different. Pharmaceutical industry is LONG game.
jimmyadaro: Small Pharma will overtake
CheeseManUchiha: unpaywall extension gang
JdPaulBlart: google collab is poo poo
solitarynative: why are they called corona
condoram: it is the strand of virus
DoomBoomer1: geohot :O
Abnico: OSFrog OSFrog
solitarynative: where does the name come from
C0deCane: @JdPaulBlart just get VR collab its free
K177: @benchai18 oh yeah i'm aware, but in a case like the COVID-19, this shit will hurt them short term and long term
Abnico: OhMyDog OhMyDog OhMyDog OhMyDog OhMyDog
C0deCane: Kappa
Diefunction: Latin name
Maizlow90: Anyone can explain what he is trying to do/accomplish?
igg44705: @solitarynative because it has those crown spaces things sticking out, so they named it corona
Diefunction: corona = crown
Ayyyy420Lmao: corona is mexican for 'beer'
jimmyadaro: @Ayyyy420Lmao LMAO NO
condoram: The family of viruses is called Coronaviridae
Br4nnon: he's trying to hack the mainframe
solitarynative: and corona is latin for crown?
jimmyadaro: "Beer" is "cerveza"
condoram: so it got its name from there
vicmoney69: @Maizlow90 hes trying to cure COVID-19
Abnico: Corona is chinese for “gay”
jimmyadaro: @solitarynative Yep
theonlymonkas: george = Jorge
jimmyadaro: Spanish, I think
theonlymonkas: si es español
igg44705: he trying to slove corona virus and upload to github @Maizlow90
solitarynative: 5Head of course
JdPaulBlart: i meant google colab
l1ght5p33d: open source protiens
guacDev: Corona is wuhan for bat soup
nvda9: hello
CheeseManUchiha: hes trying to find a backdoor into humans
jimmyadaro: @CheeseManUchiha We already have one
Alexthematey: gachiBASS
igg44705: he's hacking the simulation
theonlymonkas: LUL
C0deCane: how did the epicenter of all this turn out not as bad as the surrounding cities in China
nvda9: what does George do for living nowadays?
ConnorMusarra: good thing I got a C in high school biology
CheeseManUchiha: Kappa
o______________________k: squadR hey DUD I want my cure now DUD squadR
almonte550: If we see this pdf since the beggining it would be so much easier
jimmyadaro: @nvda9 Comma AI?
condoram: But hey on the bright side we have the positive outcome: - More appartements will be free to be moved in - Pollution is down - Governments wont need to pay pension to old people - Dogs are happy to see their owners 24/7
JdPaulBlart: squadR any oil princes in chat
benchai18: @k177 How long term? I’m not disagreeing, just curious. Also consider that efforts to “remedy” this are recent. There was no impetus a year ago, obv. So corona hasn’t been a factor in the way they handle business for the past 50 years
theonlymonkas: link
igg44705: @nvda9 comma ai, but i don't think he need to earn to live
o______________________k: what a fucked up day squadR
condoram: I think corona will become like the common flu
jimmyadaro: @condoram A lot of countries have their pension system broke
CheeseManUchiha: BIIIIIG dud
condoram: just keep spreading forever
localcanofdutchgold: lul
igg44705: BTW sars is a type of corona virus
condoram: MERS too I believe
benchai18: @igg44705 GIVE THIS MAN A MEDAL GOD DAMNIT
inciMage: chinese virus
Maizlow90: @georgehotz https://www.karger.com/Article/FullText/89211
JdPaulBlart: squadW
Diefunction: why they don't use quantum computers to find a vaccine ?
jimmyadaro: "wow"
benchai18: @incimage 🤫 u wanna get banned for the truth?!
Maizlow90: @georgehotz https://www.drbrownstein.com/corona-virus-what-to-do-2/?fbclid=iwar1oerar3hh9f2kh9ohcqxmdsxlq01o2huowfnfeijqkowiwf8qnyglhit0
o______________________k: squadPH
condoram: George looks like me when I am reading something I have no idea what is going on
northumb: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hydroxychloroquine what do you think about this? @georgehotz
jimmyadaro: @Diefunction It has nothing to do with processing power
THX1342: c1tr0n75 "only" 1.5%? isn't flu mortality at around 0.1%? and that's 650,000 people worldwide each year. So 1.5% would put it at almost 10 million ignoring the fact that Corona is more contagious
JdPaulBlart: squadQ
o______________________k: squadQ
JdPaulBlart: 4Weird wrap it up george
igg44705: @benchai18 lol geo hotz said corona virus is sars, but sars is a type of corona virus
nvda9: iGeorge challenged Elon musk
nvda9: is
wholesome_pepe: imagine nCov being man made Kappa
THX1342: c1tr0n75 I also question the ship statistics because of the close support they had from doctors which is not indicative of 'in the wild' scenario
THX1342: not question, but I don't think it is a perfect representation
benchai18: Guys what if this WHOLE time these past few days, George has just been bullshitting. Like what if he doesn’t understand anything he’s reading. He’s just yelling out terms and acronyms.
condoram: yea but that's the flu after so many years, it could easily have been mutated into something less lethal. I think the same will happen with corona
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 Check out his GitHub
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 https://github.com/geohot/corona
benchai18: @jimmyadaro I know mate, just kidding around
condoram: The difference is, we are experiencing a pandemic in its early stages so it is usually now we will feel the most
C0deCane: @georgehotz Do you think Corona will kill more than the annual suicide rate in America?
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 WELL FU!CK YOU THEN
Ayyyy420Lmao: press F to pay respects for kary mullis
igg44705: @benchai18 i mean he doesn't understand eveything fully, he said it himself
jimmyadaro: lmao jk
ShredderSherlock: damn did Kary get the Noble for dat
benchai18: @jimmyadaro Lol. U hit me with the link!!!
condoram: now until 1-2 years ahead
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 I always have it around
condoram: after that it should calm the fuck down
jimmyadaro: hahaha
benchai18: Lol
K177: @benchai18 incase a cure doesn't come out, due to the theory of pharamcy "hiding it from us" would mean that you would essentially be killing off a huge chunk of the population which could potentially harm the economy, AKA the pharmaceutical companies. All of this is speculation since none of us actually know the outcome of this shit show
jimmyadaro: SMALL PHARMA BABY!!!
THX1342: can't they do microscopy for HIV?
theonlymonkas: maybe it is a derivative or combination
equipollent_z: making a cheap at-home test would be nice
Nussinov: a bunch of physicists sort of used viruses to learn about some basic biological things in the 40s and 50s
condoram: A early cure would either be: Herd immunity through infecting a lot of people or vaccine
FastCashCoding: EM scopes
igg44705: you need an eletron microscop
c1tr0n75: @THX1342 that's right, but let's not forget that, all the other pandemic situations that humanity knew, this is actually the mildest, compared to the spanish flu, and malaria (malaria is responsible for 1/2 deaths in the humans over history)
bytebacon: Viruses need electron microscope
Sidhuu: did u order a swab
THX1342: virus vary wildly in size IIRC
condoram: or wait it out and hope the virus starts mutating into something less lethal
FastCashCoding: tiny
jimmyadaro: who ordered a swab
C0deCane: Maybe if China never said they could destroy America without ever going to war they wouldn't be so suspect right now in the publics eyes LUL
igg44705: very very small
condoram: It is bigger than pollio
theonlymonkas: but where do you get the sample
Harm133: its was 1nm right
FastCashCoding: angstroms
jimmyadaro: 1pl
nvda9: corona is airborne or not?
wholesome_pepe: Cryogenic electron microscopy
condoram: not airborne
igg44705: @georgehotz would you say you are as good with hardware as sofware
Maizlow90: @georgehotz https://www.karger.com/Article/FullText/89211 https://www.drbrownstein.com/corona-virus-what-to-do-2/?fbclid=iwar1oerar3hh9f2kh9ohcqxmdsxlq01o2huowfnfeijqkowiwf8qnyglhit0
benchai18: @k177 Fair... but if fatality rate really is low as 0.5-1.5% they’re not worried about death of their customers. Economy may crash, but medicine is one of those things that people will need no matter what. Whether it’s govt subsidized, investor-backed, like whatever
ShredderSherlock: is 100 nm smaller than 90 nm?
THX1342: micrograph?
benchai18: My uncle Israel has polio
Ayyyy420Lmao: @ShredderSherlock yes.
condoram: The virus travels with your spit when you cough dropplets
benchai18: Had**
roystang: wtf polio is so small
C0deCane: population size was way smaller then tho too
nvda9: @condoram airborne
guinness84: shout out salk
Sidhuu: only 10?
bytebacon: SARS-Cov2 is over 10 times the size of smallest transistors we make
condoram: Yes but if you breathe into the room it won't infect
Harm133: thats 8 million deaths right
K177: @benchai18 thats if the fatility rate stays like that, and incase the hospitals get overwhelmed, you'll see people dying indirectly from the virus
JdPaulBlart: at that point our economy is more important
braininavatt: #coronascam
dyslexicat: scammed WutFace
l1ght5p33d: @ShredderSherlock yes
jimmyadaro: Who ordered some swab???
deva73: markets are crashing if its a scam
equipollent_z: bogaScam
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Where does the 10% upper bound come from? We have isolated clusters, like pysch wards, that hit 90 or 95 % infection rates
Bombapil0t: it is a scam
roystang: millions
condoram: it is because you are coughing and spitting tiny droplets but gravity pulls them down
Ayyyy420Lmao: @bytebacon 10nm transistors are not 10nm they are 30
THX1342: wait... a CORONAVIRUS is called that way from the way it looks under a microscope.. thats the first thing I heard about coronavirus in the news LUL
condoram: it doesn't float in the air
julien9877: US vs world wide
ConnorMusarra: they predict 40-70% of US population infected
Hawklite: isn't the fatality rate actually 13%?
K177: the god damn coronavirus is a scam KKona
FastCashCoding: lol sometihng that is .09 meters is smaller than something .1m
Ayyyy420Lmao: 10nm is a trademark thing
julien9877: 8 mil world wide
paowikx1214: LOVE YOUR STREAM MAN!
Harm133: worldwide pancake, not US only
FastCashCoding: nneway
jimmyadaro: LUL
condoram: Fatality rate is 4,47 % right now
jimmyadaro: PLAGUE INC
theonlymonkas: i think it depends on the place and its conditions
benchai18: Wait, I nodded off for a moment... why are u using “10%” as a hypothetical size?
benchai18: Of people who get it
bytebacon: @Ayyyy420Lmao oh I did not know of that
deva73: check malaria
itsxaos: 500k i think
Vindalis: current fatality rate is 15% and climbing
THX1342: 650,000 deaths a year from Influenza
THX1342: worldwide
condoram: @Vindalis explain your math?
Ayyyy420Lmao: @bytebacon yeah it blew my mind when i was told, fucking marketing
C0deCane: 300, 000 is only 6x the suicide rate in America
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 For flu
Maizlow90: @georgehotz https://www.karger.com/Article/FullText/89211 https://www.drbrownstein.com/corona-virus-what-to-do-2/?fbclid=iwar1oerar3hh9f2kh9ohcqxmdsxlq01o2huowfnfeijqkowiwf8qnyglhit0
benchai18: @vindalis No, it’s not. You’re not considering the multitude of variables
Vindalis: condoram visit plague dot com
condoram: We are talking about corona right
AresRai: 10 to 15x
christianthefalco: if we allowed all 300,000 to happen quickly it would overwhelm the hospitals and cause other bad shit to happen
Vindalis: based on current infected vs deaths it's 15%
AzzoDio: But it hits all at once. You better you hope you don't need chemo or emergenncy surgery while it's hitting!
JdPaulBlart: this is all a part of the rothschilds plan
subconix: Its just a new coronavirus, its going to run its course.
equipollent_z: is it a lot of hype because it's made in a lab?
benchai18: @jimmyadaro So flu hits 10% of people a year?
condoram: 422989 infected with 18919 death, how is t hat 13%?
jimmyadaro: ｐｌａｇｕｅ ｉｎｃ
C0deCane: either way its a lot of people and we can't handle the surge in our hospitals
localcanofdutchgold: lot of old people dying in italy, not 15% overall proabably
THX1342: 15% what
nvda9: I read in Wikipedia it's not airborne, but found an article on al jajira where they claiming it's airborne
c1tr0n75: @georgehotz yes but the more we let it infect people, the more we encounter the risk of it mutating and becoming more deadly
C0deCane: No its definitely not 15%
pjayys77: just in the US
Bombapil0t: check death rate in Germany. its a big joke @Vindalis
benchai18: @c0decane Speak for yourself mate, I live in Sunny California!
l1ght5p33d: because 90 is more than 100
jimmyadaro: @l1ght5p33d quick maths
elonsmuskygooch: why you quarantined in logan pauls apartment?
bytebacon: World covid-19 death rate is 4%
benchai18: (Jk. Our states fucked)
condoram: yea, it is at 4,7%
ConnorMusarra: the US is absolutely fucked
Waldoqq: SIMP
deva73: 37
K177: the curious thing about the cruise ships, is if there was transmission after the passengers were isolated. Stuff like ventiliation and seweage system
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Why 10%? From where do you get that? Viruses have to double over time even in a cruise ship and they tried to maintain a quarantine
condoram: it could easily get to 15% if people don't give a fuck and infect older people
igg44705: @elonsmuskygooch Logan paul's apartment?
C0deCane: @benchai18 what are you talking about lol
Ayyyy420Lmao: you guys bought the dip in hooker prices?
AresRai: 🤔
theonlymonkas: 1% on the USA right?
christianthefalco: The fact that people can't understand that the mortality rate is dependent on the amount of treatment people are able to get is infuriating
AzzoDio: @georgehotz So currently at 10 out of 760 or 1.31 percent fatality on the cruise ship, with 10 more still in the ICU.
THX1342: they need ventilatoras
jimmyadaro: What if we NEED coronavirus?
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Severe = oxygen, Critical = ICU/Vent
condoram: Respirator is intensive care
AresRai: oxygen related anyway
timi13462: oth
THX1342: from doctors I heard: ventilators
timi13462: both
Br4nnon: help breathing
deva73: supplemental oxygen
dorkmo: i think it means youre in the ICU?
Nussinov: id be interested to see how the ratio of symptomatic to asymptomatic changes as more people are infected
directrix13: ventilator oxygen
jimmyadaro: We were talking about world death rate @georgehotz
jimmyadaro: Almost 5%
benchai18: @c0decane Nah nothin, I’m an idiot. Don’t listen to me
Vindalis: the 4.4% death rate of corona is not taking into account those who have been infected over the past week, 295,583 new cases without an outcome
igg44705: @georgehotz how good are you with hard ware? making circuits?
condoram: Cruise ship death rate also would require the sample is a good sample but if 99% of people on the cruise ship were young people
Ayyyy420Lmao: they're probably infected the same bu asymptomatic
condoram: death rate would be lower
Harm133: monkaS
localcanofdutchgold: lul
AzzoDio: @georgehotz it does infect young people? What do you mean? They just don't end up wtih as many symmptoms
Waywoah: A cruise ship is pretty much worst case scenario for a virus
ShredderSherlock: does it assume the passengers all had an orgy and contact with each person with each person
christianthefalco: There is a number, but no one can say
nvda9: the fatality rate is 4℅, it's scam
FastCashCoding: cant do that
sunole: Out reads in hotels too
FastCashCoding: hhaha
manouchehri: What’s the goal of the stream tonight? Helping testing, vaccine, or treatments? Because ultimately, researching the fatality rate is gonna help with those three. TakeNRG
THX1342: Brazil's president is giving 0 fucks
JdPaulBlart: political suicide
condoram: Death rates will be way higher in countries where there are more older people
ConnorMusarra: hospitals in New York are already reaching their breaking point
Eyachi: they never would it sounds weird
Nussinov: 1$
almonte550: 5 millions
igg44705: 7 billion people
Ayyyy420Lmao: no such number
cellophane11578: 1 million
Lizardan: how much does a human life cost?
Ayyyy420Lmao: fuck ppl
directrix13: It just doesn't hardly affect the young people like it does the older and immunocompromised
condoram: I think Germany is mislabeling their deaths on purpose
ELITEGAMS: trillion
igg44705: @georgehotz how good are you with hard ware? making circuits?
subconix: it sounds sad, but its true... there is a number
dorkmo: are the people that are going to die from flu going to just die from this instead?
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Do you think people will go to restaurants with bodies all around and no hospital care though?
K177: wouldn't it also depend on the skillset of the population that would be killed off?
C0deCane: @georgehotz I think a good question is how much of the virus do you need to contract to become ill?
jimmyadaro: Asymptomatic infected means n*n infected people?
inciMage: @Lizardan around a hundred
Sidhuu: Trump is already valuing the economy over lives
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: < 20K in US
Bombapil0t: 32k infects and about 150 deaths in Germany. 15% ?!
directrix13: so it spreads easily
Lizardan: @inciMage sounds about right
almonte550: with 5 million I think people will start get scared
jimmyadaro: 1M?
Ayyyy420Lmao: i think that closing stuff will always have deleterious effects compared to doing nothing
FastCashCoding: couple btc of satoshis worth
pjayys77: one politiican did just say somehting about letting old people die for the economy to be saved
blondephilia: Please don't assume any data from China is accurate. Subtract them from all hypotheses and calculations
nremind: they would never publicly say a number
wholesome_pepe: i wish new york and seattle would break down the cases by age and race
jimmyadaro: Word-wide??
qlutoo: 1 million
Br4nnon: The flu infects millions
PiroFloydian: 500K maybe lower
FastCashCoding: 250k probably fine
condoram: US is likely to have up to half to 1 million death at the end of this year
AresRai: what about 1.2m
cybergenik: I think if we stand to lose more than 15% of the nations gdp in stocks, then we need government intervention.
inciMage: @dorkmo in addition ppl who wouldnt die from flu will die
jimmyadaro: 1M would be enough
SofiaLouise: The problem is, if the hospital capacity breaks, we might lose control
condoram: If they don't start caring
c1tr0n75: @georgehotz it depends on which age will be more affected by the deaths
passingremarks: 250k is a lot of dead people
AzzoDio: @georgehotz It's probably easier to hold it low, like Kora right now, than it is to 'squeeze' out like 200k and then stop. It probably snowballs!
braininavatt: lol, so where do you draw the line?
bytebacon: Some think Italians are more vulnerable to covid-19 because of genetic reasons. See Nassim Nicholas Taleb's tweet: https://twitter.com/nntaleb/status/1241446601475919873
benchai18: @sidhuu Don’t be reductive. It’s not that simple. And the economy is all of our fucking lives
igg44705: it has to be at a point where, the economy won't grow because of the lack of people
localcanofdutchgold: megadeath x5 Pog
AzzoDio: Like Korea
verxile: Deaths are delayed by 3 weeks
peter35_: if recovered have diasability?
passingremarks: 500k is also a lot ofdead people lol
jimmyadaro: Are we talking word-wide???
THX1342: I think there is also a generalized fear withing the researchers because this is a new strain that we don't know how it could change/evolve
Lizardan: 100K dead? .... deal SeemsGood
directrix13: the problem with this vs the flu is that this infects far more rapidly than flu overwhelming our system leading to considerably higher deaths
jimmyadaro: Oh ok
PiroFloydian: na thats about 1%
C0deCane: I'd say if we can all stay alive we will have more people to get the economy back in action if were still somewhat stable after this
nvda9: we are gone develop herd immunity
cybergenik: 350mil
theonlymonkas: and what about other parts of the world with less medical capacity, the virus could propagate again?
itsxaos: 330 now i think
l1ght5p33d: Its literally everyone flipping out about the flu
JohnEGQ: I thought the computer models were showing over 1 million deaths unless we quarintine
localcanofdutchgold: 360 ?
l1ght5p33d: im so glad I bought BTC
manouchehri: 5 million of what age groups?
Bombapil0t: 2017/2018 died 25k ppl in Germany from flu. just saying
fujikekw: think last reported was 337 million pop in us
blondephilia: 10 million could die. Who cares. America is nothing and means nothing. The country doesn't exist.
AzzoDio: @georgehotz It might be cheaper to hold it down to 10k, than it iwould be to hold it at 250k -- you'd have health care workers dying, it might not be a thing you could stop at that point without going evne more extreme, to stop it at 250. It's not a linear modle
condoram: Italians are nr 2 on the list of most old people in country and they all lived together, like 2/3 generations under the same roof and the younger people don't seem to care about social distancing.
JdPaulBlart: much more efficient just to have a civil war
jimmyadaro: @manouchehri Overall
brownyyyylocks: death rate > birth rate
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: 500K that a lot of bodies monkaW
dr_set: https://www.statnews.com/2020/03/17/a-fiasco-in-the-making-as-the-coronavirus-pandemic-takes-hold-we-are-making-decisions-without-reliable-data/
braininavatt: what about the rate of sick people?
dr_set: that's the article he mentioned
christianthefalco: Do too little => hospitals get overwhelmed, many die for no reason. Be responsible => it fizzles out and people accuse you of being irresponsible with their money/economy
nremind: but if this causes even 5% long term complications, it would increase healthcare costs substantially
pjayys77: well that's 61,000 without any measures taken place, but considering with the shelter-in-place in some areas currently
condoram: I think US will have 500k death at least in this year from corona
c1tr0n75: @georgehotz I mean if we had 2 millions deaths from working people, it's not the same as 5 million retired people
ELITEGAMS: coronavirus look worldmeter info
jimmyadaro: PLAGUE INC
b2kemann: end of america
ConnorMusarra: it's already too late
l1ght5p33d: Corona virus taskforce ::: sells masks::: buys bitcoin::::
manouchehri: Why not publish your own models?
Ayyyy420Lmao: you can start one in augur no?
blondephilia: ^
mik12f4: directly?
THX1342: georgehotz there's another very important factor. these patients NEED ICU. if they don't take it they die. and they take space from other people who need it... more people can die, not from corona
FastCashCoding: @georgehotz get your boys from Augur on the line
Sidhuu: I don't think there will be millions of deaths because of the way china has handled it
ahahahaitslit: they would have to risk their model being accurate and things not going horribly wrong
Saltyballss: asked my marble, it will be 500k
manouchehri: You’re noteworthy enough that somebody will read it.
directrix13: because then people could literally profit off promoting deaths
THX1342: the whole thing is about not killing the health system
l1ght5p33d: Common cold taskforce 2020
PiroFloydian: directly or indirectly @georgehotz ? cause it affects healthcare availability
condoram: I think China is full of shit and hidding
joshperri: Tobacco Cars flu >= 500,000 deaths/year
Bombapil0t: the numbers are fragile as fck
K177: lmao
joshperri: In the US alone
bluejimmy168: China lies LUL
K177: china made it worse if anything
christianthefalco: China did a good job
deva73: max 7k deaths in worst case
Br4nnon: The deaths would be higher without lockdown
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Your assumption is that its just as easy to stop it at 250k as it is at 25k -- that's an assumption. It might be cheaper to stop it at 25k! South Korea etc
roystang: US is definitely not china
bluejimmy168: we have no idea what the real numbers are from China
Nussinov: @christianthefalco Kappa
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 10 in the channel!
JohnEGQ: maybe we let it kill and then no more Social Security !???
c1tr0n75: c1tr0n75 gifted a Tier 1 sub to CompestLive!
jimmyadaro: 1M would be okay
Sidhuu: china did a really good job in containg the virus
Maizlow90: @georgehotz https://www.karger.com/Article/FullText/89211 https://www.drbrownstein.com/corona-virus-what-to-do-2/?fbclid=iwar1oerar3hh9f2kh9ohcqxmdsxlq01o2huowfnfeijqkowiwf8qnyglhit0
blondephilia: Boomer deaths would actually spur an economic boom. Home prices, Social security loosening, etc.
condoram: US has the issue of not caring if you got no money, this will result in a lot of deaths
jimmyadaro: We're not experts
christianthefalco: @Nussinov not kappa, it's pretty clear
C0deCane: I think if the numbers continue to rise in Italy we will know China is full of shit
ELITEGAMS: china kickout foreigners reporter from the Wuhan city so..
nvda9: found an interesting article on NY times.
Ayyyy420Lmao: @blondephilia based
Br4nnon: Which is what saved them
nvda9: https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/03/22/world/coronavirus-spread.html?fbclid=IwAR3eUtUzoRl5Tqwel3bcjoHkReaIo5R3OOUbDT1Jmz9TLHg6EfsL3nUvBds
AzzoDio: @georgehotz The effects of being at 250k, the side effets, might make STOPPING it at a 250k cost even more economic damage at that point
condoram: Also china is a dictatorship, helps a lot in something like this
rafalive: T𝕙𝕚𝕤 𝕚𝕤 𝕒 𝕤𝕡𝕖𝕔𝕚𝕒𝕝 𝕡𝕣𝕠𝕥𝕖𝕔𝕥𝕖𝕕 𝕗𝕠𝕟𝕥. 𝕐𝕠𝕦 𝕔𝕒𝕟𝕟𝕠𝕥 𝕔𝕠𝕡𝕪 𝕚𝕥. 𝔾𝕠 𝕒𝕙𝕖𝕒𝕕, 𝕥𝕣𝕪.
phaxxN: not from the us, how is your medical care compared to like italy, they have 10% death rate right now
Nussinov: christianthefalco define good Kappa
Harm133: LUL
bluejimmy168: LOL we all are banned from china for talking shit about them LUL
PiroFloydian: vietnam went full socialism and ultra contained @georgehotz
igg44705: @georgehotz where would stop the deaths?
Vindalis: LUL
mik12f4: Don't 2 million people die every year in US
Vindalis: Dr Hollistic LUL
C0deCane: at some point they have to level out in Italy correct?
FastCashCoding: you think China has tried or successfully stolen information from Comma?
pjayys77: check out Japans infected
fujikekw: LUL
joshperri: https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/fastats/deaths.htm
braininavatt: what did they do in vietnam?
christianthefalco: @Nussinov they probably saved millions of lives globally...
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: anything more than 100K Americans would go crazy
Harm133: https://virusncov.com/ Closed cases deathrate = 15%
jimmyadaro: 250k is not "JUST" 250k, that means a lot of asymptomatic people
tybutnowyoudie: @georgehotz you recently said comma had a new programming challenge, didn't you?
condoram: @phaxxN Italy's health care system collapsed, it will happen to US too if they don't start taking care of spreading it
theonlymonkas: and what if the virus propagates again from some country with poor health system?
Daniel_Duan: China is most likely posting fake numbers
condoram: New York is on the verge of collapsing too it seems
almonte550: Do you think that there are new vaccines that were added in China and only the young population has it and that's why they don't have it that much?
nremind: those who think china is full of shit, do you also think korea is full of shit?
igg44705: @tybutnowyoudie yeah new challange
ShredderSherlock: i just wish i could choose which people it takes out
Bombapil0t: @tybutnowyoudie no comma here TriHard
bankzed: is a wholistic doctor a doctor that's a full doctor and not half ass, like Dr. Phil
jimmyadaro: @nremind Which one
jimmyadaro: 250k is not "JUST" 250k, that means a lot of asymptomatic people
Br4nnon: But do people from colds need hospitalization ?
THX1342: 0.1-0.2%
Nussinov: @christianthefalco im skeptical of that number, but more importantly; at what cost to the well being of their population?
nizero: George your stream has grown a lot
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Czech Republic has 100% mask wearing: https://twitter.com/jeremyphoward/status/1242572288962240517 deaths and have no growth in daily new covid-19 case
Harm133: common cold monkaS
condoram: South Korea tests a lot, that is why they are able to keep it down
C0deCane: Remember the WHO predicted 7.5 million Americans would die from swine flu
lupo_1: coronovirus is not like cold
Saltyballss: Saltyballss subscribed at Tier 1.
K177: crazy stat was that 50% of people hospitalized were young people
phaxxN: @condoram okok, yeah i think they need to take it serious
localcanofdutchgold: @Harm133 what's distribution of infection by age?
PiroFloydian: in vietnam all testing and hc relating to virus is free, food can be delivered to people free, full sick leave pay etc
deva73: i dont't believe ch8inese figures.
manouchehri: It doesn’t matter for what you’re doing it.
bytebacon: India approved Hydroxychloroquine for prophylaxis. See the official dosage: https://www.mohfw.gov.in/pdf/AdvisoryontheuseofHydroxychloroquinasprophylaxisforSARSCoV2infection.pdf
aMANT3: what matter is the fatality rate
Sidhuu: if china were full of shit why would they open Wuhan
Ayyyy420Lmao: nothingburger PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
jimmyadaro: https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/03/22/world/coronavirus-spread.html
verxile: 30-90 million Americans get flu a year
Waldoqq: Were going to pass Italy in 2 days
teapoted: teapoted subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Diefunction: G20 the Group of 20 major economies on Thursday to discuss a global response to the coronavirus pandemic.
THX1342: did america do anything to prevent swine flu?
verxile: 60k deaths
christianthefalco: @Nussinov yes, it's a tradeoff with freedom. no perfect answer. I think they did well with a tough situation. We'll see how the US does with the opposite approach
Waldoqq: 500k americans will be dead by June
condoram: Like they say most people will get through the virus no problem but these people that don't show massive symptoms can spread it to other people that's where the issue is
PiroFloydian: SCAM TRAIN PogChamp
korgy111: What do you think about c ?
theonlymonkas: chooo chooo
equipollent_z: bogaTrain bogaTrain bogaTrain bogaTrain
directrix13: hype train?
nvda9: think about black death
C0deCane: India just gets the virus and already making more moves than America typical
directrix13: lol
condoram: that's why by testing as much as possible you can minimize the spread
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp DAMN
jimmyadaro: DAAAYUMNNNN PogChamp
montecarlo: SCAM TRAIN Pog
Bombapil0t: get me in that scam train boys
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: CHOO CHOO TRAIN
Ayyyy420Lmao: consooome train PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
jimmyadaro: SCAM TRAIN
jimmyadaro: PogChamp
korgy111: What do you think about c
jimmyadaro: LMAO
b2kemann: but is the world overracting? i can't seem to land on either yes or no
korgy111: What do you think about c ??
TheLastMrX: wow scam train
korgy111: What do you think about c ????
jimmyadaro: EXTRA CHROSOMA TIME PogChamp
igg44705: @C0deCane but the people are't following tho
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Santiago_LHC: CORONA TRAIN
AzzoDio: @georgehotz There is a Univ Minnesota study, they overnight you the drug if you were just exposed.
condoram: What is this train about?
braininavatt: HYPE TRAIN PogChamp
ELITEGAMS: https://www.worldometers.info/coronavirus/
C0deCane: bogaScam bogaTrain
directrix13: Take arsenic. It can't hurt what is dead.
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp YEAAAAH
Ayyyy420Lmao: @condoram it brings us to the gas showers PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Bombapil0t: keep asking the right questions SeemsGood
condoram: ooo been there done that
korgy111: What do you think about c ? MrDestructoid
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz https://unpaywall.org/
bankzed: the world is under reacting
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Post Exposure Study https://twitter.com/boulware_dr/status/1239944721386164225
btpisroot: Would you rather over react or regret later tho?
korgy111: What do you think about c ? MrDestructoid ?
Nussinov: @christianthefalco you have to consider the "tradeoff with freedom" over hundreds of years though LUL its not simply a matter of what they do during the pandemic
ConnorMusarra: the lack of testing in the US just sealed our fate
Br4nnon: China did what needed to be & had the resources
korgy111: What do you think about c ? MrDestructoid
jimmyadaro: https://unpaywall.org/
martinkirilov: martinkirilov subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 3 months, currently on a 1 month streak! Sup George, good to see you back
raystriker98: !uptime
blondephilia: Why do you think the China numbers are accurate? Do you think Russia has 0 deaths?
0R4NG3: lol
Ayyyy420Lmao: @btpisroot you can also regret overreacting sweaty
PiroFloydian: yeah brazil is SUPER fashy
doctorgenus: is everyone at comma.ai working from home?
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
braininavatt: brazi's president doesnt believe in it #coronascam
theonlymonkas: what about third wolrd countries
THX1342: my first sign that shit was real was China locking down Wuhan. Who shuts down 10 million people if shit is not serious... then I learnt about the lab in Wuhan and feaked out LUL
Nussinov: this is what brazil is doing to prevent corona virus spread https://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/fn3p40/brazil_using_helicopters_to_blow_people_off_the/
igg44705: @georgehotz would you lie under outh
condoram: Gotta say though, loving Bings https://bing.com/covid
guinness84: the cruise ship was a sick experiment too honestly
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp lmao
c1tr0n75: cheer50
K177: PogChamp 💳 scam train
0R4NG3: scam train PogChamp 💳 scam train PogChamp 💳 scam train PogChamp 💳 scam train PogChamp 💳
K177: PogChamp 💳 scam train PogChamp 💳 scam train PogChamp 💳 scam train PogChamp 💳 scam train
condoram: Only time I use bing
0R4NG3: scam train PogChamp 💳 scam train PogChamp 💳 scam train PogChamp 💳 scam train PogChamp 💳 󠀀
likespuppies: @georgehotz its not an overreaction!!! If we can't treat people, it becomes SARS in terms of CFR and we can't treat people if the healthcare system caves (which it is in Italy & Spain despite lockdown)
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Brazil data incoming PogChamp
jimmyadaro: follow PogChamp the PogChamp damn PogChamp train PogChamp CJ!!!!
subconix: why is the cruise ship thing so sketchy?
joshperri: https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/fastats/deaths.htm
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp
InfiniteReddit: HahaLean
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
ahahahaitslit: isn't brazil in lockdown
AzzoDio: @georgehotz That Twieet is a liink where they test of your family taking hydroxychloroquine can prevent infection, they overnigh you the drugs if you have a case in the family
Ayyyy420Lmao: dopamine rush train PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp FailFish PogChamp PogChamp
equipollent_z: have there been any cases in DPRK?
0R4NG3: PogChamp
THX1342: Brazil's president is as dumb as they come
Harm133: scamtrain PogChamp
igg44705: @georgehotz would you lie under oath
jimmyadaro: Argentina is lockdown too
korgy111: In your opinion what's the most universal and useful programming language?
theonlymonkas: madagascar is inmune
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
Diefunction: India
condoram: Italy is at 69k infected and US at 55k
bluejimmy168: Japan isnt even testing people.
northumb: is this the cure https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hydroxychloroquine ?
condoram: Shit is escalating
b2kemann: i do think the economic consequences will be more devastating in the long term though. So in that sens the world is acting like the immun system under the spanish flu
visheshsinha: India in Complete LockDown for 21 days
thezilion: Tem brasileiro aqui? rsrsrsrs
doctorgenus: trump is about to do that after easter
christianthefalco: @Nussinov eh, we're talking about this corona virus. Who knows if authoritarianism is the best for China. Too complex a question to write off with twitch emotes
likespuppies: data visualization engineer as a career?
iuciferdk: free shkreli
igg44705: hahahah that's a lie @georgehotz
pjayys77: how is it possible not everyone coming through airport entry, in the US at least, are being tested
Sidhuu: @blondephilia china lifted the lockdown in Wuhan. they wouldn't do that if coronvirus was still spreading there
jimmyadaro: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
jimmyadaro: PogChamp
PiroFloydian: yeah our healthcare system sucks
vbrayon: @thezilion é claro
directrix13: In 3 days we will overtake China
AzzoDio: South Korea is not that authoritarian, and neither is Taiwan
directrix13: at this rate
AzzoDio: And they both did ok
nizero: senate passed 2 trillion deal
almonte550: Why do you think young population in China doesn't have so much cases of coronavirus?
theonlymonkas: spain reaction was to late
Ayyyy420Lmao: 10% we back bullbois
deva73: it surged
Bombapil0t: :D
Nussinov: @christianthefalco of course, highly complex topic. not trying to debate you, was just pointing out something I found funny LUL
teapoted: Isn't it more useful to only look at death numbers because infected numbers are vastly skewed by number of tests conducted or what criteria country a tests by (see diff in Germany vs Italy)
K177: trueee
doctorgenus: ohh yeah good thinking
GReeN_HuMaN: do you think the economical effect will kill more people than the virus?
vbrayon: @thezilion 10° de quarentena:
zwisch: the market likes certainty
jimmyadaro: PogChamp !
bluejimmy168: Play them like toys
equipollent_z: DPRK Christmas Gift? 🎄
blondephilia: @Sidhuu I asked about the numbers.
korgy111: In your opinion what's the most universal and useful programming language? ?
condoram: @Sidhuu it is about spreading propoganda, make people think everything is ok
THX1342: China will do some Marshall Plan soon...
jimmyadaro: @korgy111 C
igg44705: @georgehotz what foods did you buy?
btpisroot: Puppet master
almonte550: Why do you think young population in China doesn't have so much cases of coronavirus?
K177: lmao
nvda9: pronhub premium is free on lockdown areas
zwisch: LUL exactly
Nussinov: what if its MY life though
jimmyadaro: @nvda9 PogChamp
codezillla: lol
Lizardan: paying people to stay home = bad idea
C0deCane: If Trump keeps holding conferences do you think he will catch it? and if he doesn't should we go outside LUL?
thezilion: stop stupid questions
likespuppies: shut down the economy and go full socialism -- literally eat the rich
jimmyadaro: "i did get the ad"
K177: OMEGALUL
jimmyadaro: LMAO PogChamp
blondephilia: @nvda9 porn is a weapon.
theonlymonkas: master of puppets
jimmyadaro: LUL
condoram: I am on Italian VPN to visit pornhub :D
ShredderSherlock: maybe we need to slow down consumption
AzzoDio: @georgehotz Probably the economy collapses if their are a million deaths, so it's not really a trade of one or the other
pjayys77: so feds pumping $1trillion every day for a month in the market to stave off the crash .. brosef
AresRai: tru
northumb: twitter is bullshitt
C0deCane: FUCK YOUR ECONOMY SAVE MY LIFE!!!!!
directrix13: @georgehotz so would your order a pizza delivered right now where you are?
Nussinov: i cant prove that anyone else exists, we live in a simulation Kappa
l1ght5p33d: I haven't had sex in 3 years think i give a fuck if i die
C0deCane: LUL
jimmyadaro: fuck your life, save my economy
almonte550: Why do you think young population in China doesn't have so much cases of coronavirus? @georgehotz
PiroFloydian: hypotheticals against actual lives seems pretty sus @georgehotz
MrTriharder: @georgehotz Things we should learn from Japan
CheeseManUchiha: @l1ght5p33d based
bankzed: wait pornhub premium is free for Italians??
bluejimmy168: True
l1ght5p33d: ill go around licking stuff
thezilion: It's needed VPN to access italian website
C0deCane: @jimmyadaro im joking dude LUL
lupo_1: economy doesn't crash because of 1 persons live
likespuppies: @georgehotz if this gets unchecked the economy crumbles and we end up at war
blondephilia: Imagine the suicide rate in a depression in current year.
martinkirilov: fuck your economy, fuck my life
c1tr0n75: @georgehotz at the time being, they are trying to flatten the curve, not limit the casualties, they are just giving hospitals and morgues a room to breath
ahahahaitslit: yeeboi
bankzed: turns on the VPN
jimmyadaro: @bankzed Yep, every lockdown
jimmyadaro: city
b2kemann: the economy was shit. Corona was the pin that pricked the everything bubble.
jimmyadaro: or country
braininavatt: GHOTZ 2032
directrix13: Everybody: write in George Hotz
christianthefalco: TROLLEY CARS EVERYWHERE
deva73: jail break elections
THX1342: @c1tr0n75 I agree
MrTriharder: WHAT LIFE GEORGE? PepeHands
zwisch: PiroFloydian it's not a hypothetical, death rates go up during an economic downturn
teapoted: People vastly underestimate the amount of background deaths.
bankzed: oh, so I can just use NYC VPN then
l1ght5p33d: triple kill
pjayys77: said to say recently tho, life expectancy in the states has gone down
Ayyyy420Lmao: @b2kemann sweety we will have new ATH later this year
doctorgenus: what will you do after Tesla buys you guys out for 1 Billion?
peter35_: alphaGov 2028
K177: PepeLaugh
thezilion: go to jailbreak coronavirus
zennydmt: is comma ai safe
braininavatt: dont be afraid to buy Kappa
lupo_1: @georgehotz what if it was the only person who would stop the super virus that dies?
Nussinov: #ad
igg44705: @georgehotz people can't drive tho
subconix: George does not want to be the guy to decide what number of people is acceptable to die from this LUL
Harm133: little plug LUL
Br4nnon: it's only temporary
likespuppies: AHH guys we forgot, he's a CEO he has CEO biases
jimmyadaro: We had a lot of stupid Angel and VC investors putting money on stupid shit, the market needed a correction!
benchai18: The economy was NOT shit. Just Trump haters
bankzed: time to pivot to freight trucks?
Santiago_LHC: I want to invest in Comma Bio
itsxaos: we improved life expectancy and quality by making adavances in technology and science not by coming up with another way for bankers to profit
martinkirilov: Shameless plugs
l1ght5p33d: comma ai is safer than you
anotherkidnamedaustin: 602 viewers?
almonte550: How much money do you have in the stock market?
anotherkidnamedaustin: stream bot?
PiroFloydian: @zwisch i think thats more a flaw of our economic system than anything
nizero: George I can label your data set for you
Ayyyy420Lmao: do you own any chainlink???
JohnEGQ: I need some Hotz merch
benchai18: @itsxaos Dude. You’re speaking like a child.
northumb: then is where AI appears
THX1342: Do you think the USA would accept financial help from China?
K177: LUL
zennydmt: are u an expert in deep learning?
Br4nnon: Stocks are on sale
deva73: fcuk
jimmyadaro: What about BTC?
pjayys77: see we're talking about companies sells numbers but not the middles class or just average worker's outlook
Harm133: whats your expectancy of crypto in teh coming week
btpisroot: lol
eiscosogin1: i wish mine had only gone down 30
bankzed: also, you didn't get the early warnings given out to VIPs to pull out of the market? KappaWealth
blondephilia: UL
georgehotz: Choo Chooo HypeGriffin1
b2kemann: stocks are still expensive
braininavatt: real reason why he's creating a vaccine Kappa
martinkirilov: Choo Chooo HypeGriffin1
localcanofdutchgold: scam train Pog
igg44705: @georgehotz which app do you use for stocks?
jimmyadaro: PogChamp
Saltyballss: damn i earned a lvl1 hype train emote
c1tr0n75: Choo Chooo HypeGriffin1 haha
blondephilia: I'm at -40% :(
o______________________k: !claim Kappa
Saltyballss: Tut-tuut HypeGriffin1
thezilion: STAY SAFE!!!!!!!!!!
Ayyyy420Lmao: do you own chainlink???
jimmyadaro: I'm at 10%
anotherkidnamedaustin: complaining about -30% after a 28% 2019 year hmm....
jimmyadaro: PogChamp
cybergenik: Wait did you pull out or are you just standing your positions?
salpu_: ryryAloha ryryAloha ryryAloha
jimmyadaro: PogChamp DAMN TRAIN
jimmyadaro: HELL YEAH
deva73: does anyone benfit from this coronascare?
Sidhuu: justified loss
anotherkidnamedaustin: THE MARKET WAS UP 28% IN 2019
stillneedswork: https://coronavirus.jhu.edu/map.html
anotherkidnamedaustin: YOU SHOULD BUY MORE
l1ght5p33d: dude i just bought ETH at 117
theonlymonkas: for how long it's gonna be until we can go back to normal
likespuppies: you have money but no autonomous rocket :rage: lazy
Chrimo: No picnic sellout!
ryanm0012: YOU SHOULD BUY MORE
K177: eh, it'll still drop
doctorgenus: if Elon buys you guys out tomorrow but fires you, will you run for political office?
b2kemann: how was the economy good? how much of the hardware stuff you use in comma is coming from the us?
MrTriharder: @georgehotz u planning to buy more?
phrixus_bro: you guys seem ok... get your money out while you can
anotherkidnamedaustin: anyone selling is either retiring this year or pussy
jimmyadaro: fuck taxes
pjayys77: the market doesn't represent the average person, just corporations ..
igg44705: @georgehotz if you don't work another day can you still maintain the same lifestyle?
Br4nnon: Honestly I just want our ppl to be taken care of
solitarynative: it wont go back up to where it was unless fed pump
anotherkidnamedaustin: 1099 life i trade options for living
bankzed: my stock market stat is the same as with unprotected sex, I want to pull out but it feels much better not to pull out
blondephilia: If nothing gets passed in DC it'll dip again. Buy then and ride it out.
l1ght5p33d: Good patriots don't pay taxes
anotherkidnamedaustin: quite nice actually
jimmyadaro: @pjayys77 That's plain stupid
MathmAddict: Geo, I know this is way off topic, I bet sports for a living which is clearly not making much of a living atm. I use linear regression models for handicapping. wondering if you think using ML specifically neural networks will be able to improve on EV?
benchai18: @b2kemann The economy being good doesn’t mean we lived in a PERFECT world
solitarynative: because baby boomers selling to retire
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: bolsonaro went from corona is fake to it might be real to fake again LULW
bankzed: *strat
stillneedswork: that link shows a map for the deaths
bytebacon: create sarscoin
bravetraveller: Are you trying to write an antivirus to inject into the simulation?
fujikekw: what stock would you buy right now ? @georgehotz
igg44705: @georgehotz we need some rants
anotherkidnamedaustin: buy apple now
anotherkidnamedaustin: intel amd
Br4nnon: Boeing
Sidhuu: herd immunity
InfiniteReddit: rant!
anotherkidnamedaustin: boeing
nvda9: comma ai recruitment process is brutal
jimmyadaro: @Br4nnon lmao
anotherkidnamedaustin: united airlines
zwisch: UK would be the control
eiscosogin1: yeah but govt here cucked out to media scaremongering
Chrimo: What's that, contaminate everyone and get it over with?
likespuppies: @georgehotz it would not have been nice to see LOL
bytebacon: @nvda9 did you go through it?
jimmyadaro: More Q&A please
igg44705: @nvda9 did you go through it?
Ayyyy420Lmao: do you own chainlink?
pjayys77: with this "raise in the economy" how much of the average person felt any noticeable increase in their standard of living, income .. what have you
C0deCane: a good corona virus strat is convince enough people that it doesn't exist and deny it until the end
blondephilia: Having to pay taxes instead of moving gains into crypto LUL
nvda9: @bytebacon nah
l1ght5p33d: yea how do you get the speed from a video
anotherkidnamedaustin: i wanna apply to commabio
jimmyadaro: @pjayys77 What's your point?
l1ght5p33d: so many assumptions
AzzoDio: @georgehotz The UK medical workers said "WE WILL WALK AWAY FUCK YOU"
zennydmt: so u need years of coding for comma ai?
martinkirilov: I would have liked to see our PM do that, but he shat his pants.
bytebacon: do you hire from india george
jimmyadaro: @l1ght5p33d How many FPS?
eiscosogin1: to be honest i think we're mostly fairly happy with our leadership at the minute he's like a more respectable version of trump
directrix13: All I know is I'm gonna start wiping my ass with American dollar bills because of all the inflation this shit will cause after it's over.
thezilion: @georgehotz WASH YOUR HANDS!
pjayys77: saying the economy is doing good is a huge misrepresentation it shows how corporations are doing
igg44705: it has something to do with the framrate
b2kemann: in a good economy you produce and consume, the US is only consuming now
zennydmt: can u be an average coder and work for comma ai
nizero: George do you ask questions like reverse a res black tree? for interview
ryanm0012: dude move your retirement into crypto and dont pay taxes on it
likespuppies: @georgehotz hey george if im an average coder at 23 can i be great at 30?
nizero: red
leopolddr: Would you study genetics?
JdPaulBlart: just by using google ive got my model at 20 mse right now @georgehotz
benchai18: @eiscosogin1 Explain
jimmyadaro: @pjayys77 Are you stupid? Just asking
C0deCane: @thezilion its ok hes got zinc and canned oxygen
solitarynative: why would he need to wash his hands...
almonte550: YOU'LL DO VISAS?
condoram: @zennydmt you are either a coder or not, stop labeling yourself as average
bytebacon: I messaged you on LinkedIn last week!
xhunter0001: The economy point is interesting tho
braininavatt: GHOTZ ASMR Kreygasm
Ayyyy420Lmao: how do i know if im average?
MrTriharder: You will sponsor visa PogU
condoram: We all start somewhere
doctorgenus: how do you determine if someone is a good coder?
AresRai: @almonte550 work visas
anotherkidnamedaustin: better ??
anotherkidnamedaustin: no
MrTriharder: You will sponsor visa for indians PogChamp
tybutnowyoudie: monkaS
almonte550: @AresRai awesome!
Vindalis: how many applicants do you get before you actually would hire someone with the skills you need?
anotherkidnamedaustin: no way
K177: welp rip
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Kappa
MrTriharder: monkaGIGA
christianthefalco: LOW BAR
whycopper: What about internship requirements
YoMessi: How much do you pay?
jimmyadaro: @Vindalis Like… 50?
Sidhuu: can I get a sponsor yaar
wholesome_pepe: farm chat to label data Kappa
Nussinov: LOW BAR Kappa
THX1342: that's good leadership
CoachMeech: ez LUL
roystang: should be easy
likespuppies: @georgehotz i don't want to work for you, i want to be a good coder
immaestrolol: how do you get better than you?
Ayyyy420Lmao: how do we know if we're average coding?
Br4nnon: not high enough Kappa
condoram: I got my first job without ever coding a full product
Chrimo: Better at leadership too?
anotherkidnamedaustin: literally no way
pjayys77: again what average person has seen any noticeable incrase in their standard of living continue to ask am I stupid doesn't change that @jimmyadaro
benchai18: @christianthefalco LOL
igg44705: @georgehotz wow imma drop out of college for the comma ai visa
MathmAddict: Geo, I know this is way off topic, I bet sports for a living which is clearly not making much of a living atm. I use linear regression models for handicapping. wondering if you think using ML specifically neural networks will be able to improve on EV?
eiscosogin1: yeah ai is very specific prety much i understand cnns fairly well but svms and shit i don't really get
leopolddr: that's great, it's difficult to find good people to work with
Br4nnon: child's play Kappa
zennydmt: I mean as a coder do you have to be an expert at the minutiae, or can you learn some of the coding tricks on the job
Chrimo: Are you the coffee guy then
whycopper: Gimme an internship
solitarynative: do you care about a degree on a resume?
Nussinov: prove that you get a lot of applicants Kappa
jellyjar: how do you filter through them all?
MrTriharder: Everyone graduated from CMU 4Head
jimmyadaro: @pjayys77 Every-fucking-body on this world? Like 95% of it?
directrix13: Hire me. I can eat more pizza than you.
nizero: can u tell us a story of a funny bad interview?
bytebacon: are you good at web design george?
THX1342: how old is too old?
equipollent_z: twitch channel hackquarantine sounds interesting, but it looks liek it may only be web dev
bankzed: you can get speed from a video by identifying a point of reference and then using two frames to see how far that POR has shifted in two frames, and you do that over and over until you've got a good estimate of speed
leopolddr: How do you choose people in comma.ai??
anotherkidnamedaustin: I would rather take someone who learned on their own than someone who went thru the scam of college
l1ght5p33d: Whats the best feature tracker ORB or no
almonte550: Have you done visa sponsorship in comma?
igg44705: @georgehotz if you don't have a degree can you get a work visa?
jimmyadaro: @THX1342 Like 100 y.o.?
stahks_: how did you find your first employees?
manouchehri: Hiring anyone in security without programming skills?
doctorgenus: can I breakdance on your huge living room floor?
localcanofdutchgold: what do you consider good at programming?
verxile: How do you interview technical person
pjayys77: @jimmyadaro you know we're referring to the US market right
THX1342: jimmyadaro :P
Mlewii: Do you actually look for people that are really good or that are willing to be really good
anotherkidnamedaustin: i learn more studying on my own then my stupid professors taught me
Br4nnon: do we have to move to CA? it sucks there
solitarynative: Do you look at resumes without degrees?
Insanit13s: Could you give an example question for a comma.ai interview?
jimmyadaro: @pjayys77 I didn't know
likespuppies: @georgehotz How do I become a good coder? :)
Ayyyy420Lmao: you have any cute female employees?
ahahahaitslit: how's the pay tho
anotherkidnamedaustin: who needs degrees
jimmyadaro: @pjayys77 Still stupid
GoldSkis: So, I want to do a quick-mount for the comma two, you plan on releasing the cad files for the case?
anotherkidnamedaustin: scam
martinkirilov: @georgehotz Please tell me you do something more interesting than these shitty FANG companies
zennydmt: how about data science people?
bytebacon: Multiple View Geometry and Photogrammetry is the real deal bois
l1ght5p33d: i do nmap
MrTriharder: Pepega
eiscosogin1: can i send you my dissertation when i'm done? lol
directrix13: Hey I thought you didn't talk work on this stream.
btpisroot: LUL
CoachMeech: hahahahhahaha
jimmyadaro: @pjayys77 Life is a lot better and easier than it was 50, 100 or 200 years ago
christianthefalco: lmao
Nussinov: you need a henchmen?
64pillars: lol
bluejimmy168: yes
Chrimo: How would you take programming to the 'next level'?
0R4NG3: lmao
MrTriharder: LUL
williamjennings1: lol
condoram: Guys, for all of you that keep labeling "good/bad programmer" just get over it. You simply do and eventually you do things better.
K177: LOL
localcanofdutchgold: lul
INTeaRs: yes
ahahahaitslit: lmfao
tybutnowyoudie: LUL
nremind: I heard that companies are backing out of promised internships because of covid19
xxxelent: there is a challenge problem on their website
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
fujikekw: LUL
phrixus_bro: paul blart security
williamjennings1: do you guys have janitors
zennydmt: what do you look for in data science people
Nussinov: @georgehotz are you hiring cooks
leopolddr: police security
pjayys77: @jimmyadaro thanx for still not refuting anything I said but okay
PiroFloydian: i can order pizza super well do i have a job lol
Bootyclub: Security theatre? Like the Enterprise IT kind
Ayyyy420Lmao: you have any cute female employees?
igg44705: @georgehotz i can sweep the floors tho
YoMessi: "Security is everyone's job", is how data breaches happen.
RunnerMD: @georgehotz do you need doctors? :D
doctorgenus: do you interview everyone personally?
anotherkidnamedaustin: im down for commabio. forreal
condoram: @georgehotz Can you hire me remotely to be your twitch chatter thing?
Chrimo: Best way to improve your programming?
jimmyadaro: @pjayys77 You're throwing shit to this chat and expect me to answer you… what exactly?
likespuppies: how do i become good and get a job :monkaCRY:
braininavatt: do you offer any hardware jobs?
williamjennings1: hire greeters?
bravetraveller: never underestimate the power of a knight stick
Nussinov: You hiring strippers? I know a thing or two
tybutnowyoudie: are you hiring phd students for an internship?
whycopper: Computer engineer?
nvda9: that screening test is a nightmare for me
subconix: can I just be the office bitch?
leopolddr: 5 people, must be tough
zennydmt: do u offer data science jobs
MrTriharder: I'd even work as a Janitor tbh 4Head
ImJ4Gu4R: Geo, make me mod, i'm subscriber!
GoldSkis: Are the 3D files for the case on the comma two open source? I can only find the gopro mount and I wana draw up a quck mount for it.
manouchehri: Like I pop Chrome but hate programming in it.
Hawklite: are you hiring philosophers
ahahahaitslit: what about backspace ai
anotherkidnamedaustin: commabio would be fucking sick and im down lol we can be the scammers instead of being scammed. biochem degree from iowa..
christianthefalco: You need frontend people? I'm kinda sick of Google
Ayyyy420Lmao: are you diverse enough? how many black guys?
igg44705: @georgehotz would you say you are good in hard drive?
montecarlo: git gud
btpisroot: I would ride a Segway all day for 50k
yesokboss: what about a janitor i clean a mean toilet
equipollent_z: what about hiring coronavirus engineers?
nizero: George you hiring front end devs?
immaestrolol: how do i get good geo
brownyyyylocks: biz dev
benchai18: @christianthefalco Lol again
Chrimo: What would you do to improve your overall programming 'skills'?
cellophane11578: @georgehotz can we have a moment of silence for the end of Adobe Flash
Br4nnon: comma bio
doctorgenus: you guys looking for marketing people that can code?
TeaLeafi: georgie i love ur coding
janpoonthong: HOW TO GET BETTER AT PROGRAMMING???
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz If I do every test alright but have a shitty Github, would I make it??
condoram: Comma hack when?
braininavatt: comma.bio
wholesome_pepe: do u hire kali linux scrpt kiddies?
anotherkidnamedaustin: i can fold da proteins in a non scam way
igg44705: @georgehotz would you say you arer good with hard ware*
64pillars: tres.comma
christianthefalco: @benchai18 lol what?
julien9877: marketing LUL
TeaLeafi: coding is boring though tbh....
Br4nnon: i can code hello world LUL
zennydmt: start ups are very stressful
CoachMeech: everyone at comma is a programmer ?
bankzed: going full circle and doing some Bioinformatics?
deva73: whats upcoming in commaAi?
btpisroot: Security Marketing for Compliance
localcanofdutchgold: what do you consider proof?
ahahahaitslit: what even is the recruitment process
MrTriharder: @georgehotz the day u make it big in pharma, dont become one of those asshole who scams poor souls like me for expensive medicine
jellyjar: whats your interview process like?
leopolddr: hahahahahaha marketing people
TeaLeafi: its allabout making that stock money!!!
LaheyFPS: i can do a for loop do i qualify :) @georgehotz
bytebacon: Do you ask Leetcode type of questions?
williamjennings1: do you shave your own head?
nremind: so is comma ai really going to offer internships even if the covid19 situation doesn't improve?
Ayyyy420Lmao: are you diverse enough? how many black guys? cmonBruh cmonBruh cmonBruh
jimmyadaro: @georgehotz If I do every test 10/10 but have a shitty Github, would I make it??
GoodOlSmokey: @georgehotz see you man, gotta go git good
benchai18: @christianthefalco You keep making me laugh. First the “low bar” and then the “I’m sick of google”
INTeaRs: what kinda programmers you looking for
janpoonthong: HOW TO GET BETTER AT PROGRAMMING???
wholesome_pepe: lets get this bread
anotherkidnamedaustin: def commabio(x)
roystang: is the hackerrank public?
Chrimo: What do you consider a 'good coder'?
anotherkidnamedaustin: x = give me a job
NetAce: @georgehotz what do you define as "good at programming?" Like, not objectively, just in your subjective opinon
igg44705: @georgehotz why no remote jobs tho?
zennydmt: how is the work life balance at comma.ai
solitarynative: do you have a diversity quota I can fill?
jimmyadaro: lmao alright
doctorgenus: do we still have to pass that question where you give us a video and we need to determine the speed of the car?
condoram: is it QA time since all of these questions or are kids in EU just woken up?
o______________________k: how to get better at programming?!
Mrclutch963: What's your favorite meal? @georgehotz
montecarlo: yellow/red in codeforces
theonlymonkas: what coding skills are necessary for working at comma
CoachMeech: All of what?
Br4nnon: advent of code monkaS
likespuppies: Do all of what?
zennydmt: go all in having to code?
Nussinov: Advent of Code
LaheyFPS: i can do a for loop do i qualify :) @georgehotz
anotherkidnamedaustin: lol
zennydmt: what did u recommend?
Ferr0vax: @georgehotz You've an interesting paper from Weiss and Leibowitz up. What are your thoughts on their studies compared to more recent work? Also what were the accession numbers of the the protein sequences you were blasting in the other screens?
janpoonthong: do you have a wife?
Nussinov: https://adventofcode.com/
christianthefalco: so that's a yes?
ahahahaitslit: lmao
igg44705: @georgehotz there is no work life only WORK
zennydmt: advent of code i see
condoram: Are you hiring any CEO's?
benchai18: FUCK YES
TeaLeafi: u have kids?
pjayys77: @jimmyadaro this shows that you aren't "reading" anything I'm putting just sticking to your talking points - for the third time the economy being deemed "good" only represents corporations and is a misrepresentation because the average worker hasn't seen any noticeable increase in their standard of living
TeaLeafi: will ever have kids?????
directrix13: diversity quotas by definition are racially discriminatory
zennydmt: thats a very unhealthy attitude
anotherkidnamedaustin: ban that guy
nvda9: George, give us some interview tips
trustME_SC2: Good morning from Germany sacDAD
MrTriharder: WTF
montecarlo: mizkifWeird
Nussinov: LUL
MrTriharder: BAN THIS GUY
williamjennings1: why haven't you put your grocerys up
raystriker98: whoa
itsxaos: YIKES
deep5: Yikes
benchai18: FUCKING LOVE U Georgie! Diversity quotas are dumb
condoram: How do I mute someone?
jimmyadaro: "So why comma.ai? Because you want to do something with your life. You want to see progress being made. You want to change the way the narrative will play out. You are bored, and want the world to be less boring. And at the end of the day, you want to win." That's marketing boie
Ayyyy420Lmao: lmao elon must has entered the chat
raystriker98: BAN THIS GUY
MrTriharder: Yikes
anotherkidnamedaustin: @georgehotz make me a mod..
btpisroot: jeeze
localcanofdutchgold: WutFace help
MrTriharder: BAN THIS TARD
INTeaRs: ban this dude
toront0saur: pen testers ???
MrTriharder: WutFace mods
zennydmt: I feel its a very unhealthy attitude to work that much
williamjennings1: omg
fujikekw: REEEEEEEEEEEEEEE
roystang: make me mod
birkett0011: ban plz
nozoke: mods
jimmyadaro: @georghotzselfdrivingfail Spamming
directrix13: can we ban this dumb fucker?
0R4NG3: WutFace
AresRai: I will mod :) @georgehotz
Ayyyy420Lmao: lmao elon musk has entered the chat
INTeaRs: BAN
Br4nnon: LUL
Vindalis: LUL
Mrclutch963: Who is eric weinstein? @georgehotz
anotherkidnamedaustin: lmfao
birkett0011: LUL
AresRai: I will mod :) LUL @georgehotz
Nussinov: LUL
tybutnowyoudie: LUL
bytebacon: LOL
nvda9: @georghotzselfdrivingfail dude
TheLastMrX: LUL
0R4NG3: LMFAO
nozoke: george pls
bravetraveller: ffs man
Vindalis: LUL LUL LUL
MrTriharder: LUL
earthbender: LUL
o______________________k: LUL
cortickal: lmao
thecoder15: @georgehotz Advice on starting a hardware/software company and bootstrapping?????
ahahahaitslit: lmfaoooooooo
deep5: KEKW
Santiago_LHC: This is beautiful
blondephilia: Agreed
MathmAddict: Geo, I know this is way off topic, I bet sports for a living which is clearly not making much of a living atm. I use linear regression models for handicapping. wondering if you think using ML specifically neural networks will be able to improve on EV?
montecarlo: KEKW
jimmyadaro: ffs
mritzing: good bit tbh
itsxaos: RIP
immaestrolol: lmaoo
MrTriharder: lol
xSynchronizeD: LUL
igg44705: hahahaha
localcanofdutchgold: OMEGALUL
4FUN_PLAYER: LUL
Zaegen: ok that was good
THX1342: LUL
PiroFloydian: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
anotherkidnamedaustin: i was mad at first now im laughing
AresRai: Good one LUL
btpisroot: LUL
INTeaRs: LUL
Nussinov: that was beautiful
NetAce: adventofcode [.] com if anyone is interested in the site Geohotz mentioned
MrTriharder: LUL
PiroFloydian: KEKW
christianthefalco: wtf that guy was cool
TeaLeafi: he speaks the truth?
THX1342: Stream is getting famous LUL
christianthefalco: why ban?
C0deCane: LUL ahahaha
Saltyballss: it was my dog, sorry for that
Br4nnon: PogChamp
nizero: Georgehotz your best employee is Harald
MrTriharder: PogChamp
theonlymonkas: LUL
benchai18: It was Saurik dude
Ferr0vax: Just to differentiate, I'm not spamming I'd like an answer to @georgehotz You've an interesting paper from Weiss and Leibowitz up. What are your thoughts on their studies compared to more recent work? Also what were the accession numbers of the the protein sequences you were blasting in the other screens?
jimmyadaro: "So why comma.ai? Because you want to do something with your life" THAT'S MARKETING YOU BOY
toront0saur: any pen testers?
o______________________k: PogChamp
igg44705: @georgehotz that's awesome man
christianthefalco: CENSORSHIP!!!!!
64pillars: xqcM
dorkmo: wait for the checks to send out
leopolddr: that's great
likespuppies: Enough money for beer PogChamp
janpoonthong: Why and how you can code for long period of time? any advice
northumb: have you read life 3.0 from mag tegmark? what do you think?
btpisroot: rekt
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Mrclutch963: Who is eric weinstein? georgehotz
itsxaos: PogChamp
benchai18: George. That was Saurik ‼️
doctorgenus: will you sell tomorrow if someone offers 1B
INTeaRs: @georgehotz What kinda programmers you looking at?
anotherkidnamedaustin: @georgehotz congrats man. thanks for the inspiration that studying and focus goes a long long way
l1ght5p33d: Yeeeaaaaaa good jobb guys
NetAce: @georgehotz appreciate the recommendation on coding, love the stream
equipollent_z: what would you do if you had to reinvent computer architecture?
christianthefalco: CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!!
GoldSkis: When we gonna get the 3D files for the comma two case? I want to make a magnetic quick mount.
anotherkidnamedaustin: eric weinstein is a math genius
condoram: @georgehotz do you think once autonamous cars are a thing that if all people are gone that cars will keep driving around without us?
janpoonthong: how could you code for long period of time???
christianthefalco: CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!! CENSORSHIP!!!
igg44705: @INTeaRs C python mechine learing i guess
likespuppies: @Mrclutch963 outcast mathematician with good ideas
timi13462: rapist
T3chHS: "We will evaluate your test.txt using mean squared error. <10 is good. <5 is better. <3 is heart." hahaha
C0deCane: I smoked crack with eric weinstein
benchai18: The slammer
jimmyadaro: @condoram What for?
benchai18: Spammer
Br4nnon: would open pilot work on old cars?
northumb: have you read life 3.0 from mag tegmark? what do you think?? @georgehotz
solitarynative: Would you ever go public
64pillars: lol
kaboomyoo: incognito mode always for safety?
benchai18: Saurik was the spammer
anotherkidnamedaustin: @janpoonthong have u not seen his videos? this dude codes 13hr like its nothing
qlutoo: whats your take on peter thiel
williamjennings1: shave your head on stream?
TeaLeafi: how can you code for such a long time?
MathmAddict: Geo, I know this is way off topic, I bet sports for a living which is clearly not making much of a living atm. I use linear regression models for handicapping. wondering if you think using ML specifically neural networks will be able to improve on EV?
ahahahaitslit: the portal with eric is great
jimmyadaro: @kaboomyoo lmao
zennydmt: what companies do the rejects go to
immaestrolol: how do u get good lmaoo
TeaLeafi: what if you get hacked?
likespuppies: @georgehotz ever been depressed?
xhunter0001: does datascience jobs in commaia is specifis to images or just datascience skills in general
montecarlo: do you hire math phds
roystang: does your hackerrank have a difficulty?
fujikekw: Martial Law up in this bitch
solitarynative: Have you played alyx?
deva73: RICK AND MORTY NEEDS TO COME BACK
timi13462: good programming languages to learn now
jimmyadaro: @kaboomyoo That's Mac's dark mode
kaboomyoo: @jimmyadaro xD
Ayyyy420Lmao: your favourite house md girl?
bytebacon: Do you ever remote control cars through Eon?
doctorgenus: do you hire for coding abilities or potential coding abilities?
MrTriharder: @georgehotz how do u even get int oCarnegie? like so smart?
903284hg39408gh23098h093f: anyone at comma ai have a phd?
thecoder15: @georgehotz advice on starting a hardware/software company
igg44705: import tensorflow as tf i am bit of a machine learning engineeringmyself you know
condoram: @immaestrolol keep doing it lol, it is not rocket science. You simply do, you challenge yourself and keep doing!
christianthefalco: STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME .
anotherkidnamedaustin: guys are asking the wrong questions. if u want to get good at something, just sit down and fucking study and shut up
christianthefalco: STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME .
janpoonthong: at what age you started coding?
christianthefalco: STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME .
christianthefalco: STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME .
0R4NG3: WutFace
christianthefalco: STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME ...
likespuppies: Thirteen
deep5: yikes
T3chHS: 13
bytebacon: FOREMAN
blondephilia: Jenna
benchai18: Is it true you banged Ryan Petrich’s girl in 2010
christianthefalco: STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME STOP CENSORING ME .
jimmyadaro: More spam…
itsxaos: BRO are you mentally ill
igg44705: oliva wild
MrTriharder: WutFace
solitarynative: WutFace
Ayyyy420Lmao: 13 srsly? that manly face...
Br4nnon: he's twitch prime
RunnerMD: @georgehotz what's your opinion on high IQ people. Do you think they will do better job in your team ?
montecarlo: he's not a sub
Mint2bSpiced: Where are the mods?
Nussinov: @itsxaos do you even have to ask
itsxaos: hes not a sub dude
AresRai: hes not a sub
0R4NG3: twitch prime pleb WutFace
anotherkidnamedaustin: guys are asking the wrong questions. if u want to get good at something, just sit down and fucking study and shut upp
christianthefalco: shhhhh chat
mritzing: olivia wilde
igg44705: oliva wlid is the new girl in house md @georgehotz
cellophane11578: LUL foreman
williamjennings1: blocked!
christianthefalco: shhhh
kaboomyoo: @jimmyadaro oh ty
equipollent_z: lol
deep5: Hes not a subscriber. icon says hes a prime member
MrTriharder: Kreygasm
jimmyadaro: @kaboomyoo np
anotherkidnamedaustin: high iq making u smart is a myth....
aMANT3: DISTRACTED
janpoonthong: at what age you started coding?
bytebacon: SHE LESBIAN
Nussinov: oh hell yeah
williamjennings1: omg!
braininavatt: 13 wins
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz hes not a sub thats prime
anotherkidnamedaustin: this chat is scuffed
rustduck: PedoBear
Lizardan: Kreygasm
Bombapil0t: 10/10
Br4nnon: yes ma'am
itsxaos: hot Kreygasm
Vindalis: Kreygasm
montecarlo: OLIVIA WILDE Kreygasm
Jehhred: Olivia Wylde is wild
MrTriharder: Kreygasm oh yea
TeaLeafi: WAIT how much BTC do you have? Also in an interview you said nation state will kill you for certain codes/exploits is that true? Have you ever had death threats?...
benchai18: Is it true you banged Ryan Petrich’s girl in 2010
nvda9: George did you part icpc word final
likespuppies: @georgehotz How long has it been since you had a warm bed, sir?
anotherkidnamedaustin: house is the best show
jimmyadaro: SHE'S HOT
Mrclutch963: Favorite series @georgehotz
localcanofdutchgold: lost agane
solitarynative: 7/10
TeaLeafi: WAIT how much BTC do you have? Also in an interview you said nation state will kill you for certain codes/exploits is that true? Have you ever had death threats?...??
directrix13: directrix13 subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 4 months!
inciMage: this lady has huge forehead
jimmyadaro: Yeah
toront0saur: have you ever been exploited?
montecarlo: do you hire math PhDs
williamjennings1: sleep stream?
903284hg39408gh23098h093f: anyone at comma have a phd?
THX1342: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Hk9jct2ozY
equipollent_z: any opinion on LangSec?
TeaLeafi: WAIT how much BTC do you have? Also in an interview you said nation state will kill you for certain codes/exploits is that true? Have you ever had death threats?...???
PiroFloydian: @georgehotz thoughts on spicy food?
anotherkidnamedaustin: @georgehotz how do you focus for long periods of time. i tap out at 6hr
jimmyadaro: "So why comma.ai?"
roystang: @georgehotz what difficulty is ur hackerrank
jmv_chin: what's the crappycase repo about on ur github?
christianthefalco: @georgehotz thoughts on Jonathan Blow?
zennydmt: do you implement trading algos?
deep5: Kappa
MrTriharder: @georgehotz your life goals?
itsxaos: have you looked at the urbit programming language? its kinda ridiculous
o______________________k: how to improve programming skills?
nizero: @georgehotz your best employee is Harald
thecoder15: @georgehotz Advice on starting a hardware/software company??? and maybe on bootstrapping too
igg44705: @georgehotz how much weed do you do? does it affect you rmemory
cybergenik: Would you actually consider making a biotech company?
TeaLeafi: In an interview you said nation state will kill you for certain codes/exploits is that true? Have you ever had death threats?...
blondephilia: Most lucrative crupto in your opinion?
TeaLeafi: In an interview you said nation state will kill you for certain codes/exploits is that true? Have you ever had death threats?... ?????
williamjennings1: why do you always wear a hoodie?
Mrclutch963: Favorite book?
benchai18: UGH. FAMED JAILBREAK TWEAK Dev!!!!
pjayys77: does she give off that look like " I will cut you"
Mlewii: I love how his tone changed haha
TeaLeafi: In an interview you said nation state will kill you for certain codes/exploits is that true? Have you ever had death threats?... ???????
zennydmt: do you ever want to get married and have a family/kids?
benchai18: HE MADE ACTUVATOR
TeaLeafi: In an interview you said nation state will kill you for certain codes/exploits is that true? Have you ever had death threats?... ?????????????????
903284hg39408gh23098h093f: anyone at comma have a phd?
TeaLeafi: In an interview you said nation state will kill you for certain codes/exploits is that true? Have you ever had death threats?...??????????????
directrix13: @georgehotz do you think the universe is simulated?
ggtom: montecarlo just get some programming experience u can prolly get hired tbh. depends what kind of math u do tho.
INTeaRs: What type of programmers you looking for?
solitarynative: crypto portfolio?
likespuppies: @georgehotz How do I be a cool guy?
doctorgenus: If you get bought out tomorrow, will you go into politics?
igg44705: @georgehotz how much weed do you do? does it affect you memory
CheeseManUchiha: @georgehotz how many mechanical engs (%) did you work alongside of during the self-driving car project
martinkirilov: @georgehotz You ever wear suits?
TeaLeafi: ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh thank you!
blondephilia: Most lucrative crypto in your opinion?
64pillars: comma.blockchain when
Ayyyy420Lmao: do you own or know about chainlink and sergey nazarov?
MrTriharder: @likespuppies 4Head just be cool
jimmyadaro: Let people enjoy hacking lmao
Mrclutch963: Favorite book?
ImJ4Gu4R: Make me geo, im subscriber.
equipollent_z: how to emulate biology on machines?
jay_al97: @georgehotz how's your church project going?
JdPaulBlart: @georgehotz just from google i made a model with 25 mse for your challenge am i hired
anotherkidnamedaustin: @georgehotz how do you focus for long periods of time. i tap out at 6hrs
TeaLeafi: i love ur george
RunnerMD: @georgehotz what's your opinion on high IQ people. Do you think they will do better job in your team ?
TeaLeafi: <3
ImJ4Gu4R: make me mods
903284hg39408gh23098h093f: anyone at comma have a phd?
nvda9: you were icpc World finalist?
igg44705: @georgehotz comma ai school for the win
theonlymonkas: favorite pair of shoes
zennydmt: do you eventually want to teach at a high school
doctorgenus: school about what?
CoachMeech: what level would your school be?
PiroFloydian: LUL
hastingspb: @georgehotz what is the best music??
Codeoxic: @georgehotz Is it worth to study Computer Science or Computer Engineering, while having a liking in hardware
jimmyadaro: You'd get bored
Tyrant_01: WINDOWS OR MAC ?
bytebacon: Did you ever try programming SEGA? Like this guy from Computerphile: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gNHCxH35wYU
TeaLeafi: SCHOOOOL??????????? UR STARTING SCHOOL???
C0deCane: "Cult"
TeaLeafi: SCHOOOOL??????????? UR STARTING SCHOOL??? ?????
blondephilia: Most lucrative crypto in your opinion?
THX1342: of course it is, it's a sscam LUL
igg44705: @georgehotz did't you try to get a phd once?
TeaLeafi: SCHOOOOL??????????? UR STARTING SCHOOL??? ????
anotherkidnamedaustin: university of a joke but u went to carnigie so...
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
shieeeeeeeeet: do you use any note-taking software to manage your thoughts? @georgehotz
janpoonthong: what time you slepp???
pjayys77: wut stockpiling expoits
williamjennings1: scam lmao
theonlymonkas: favorite album right now
likespuppies: @Codeoxic yeah
benchai18: George is one of those rare people that is brilliant but not to a degree that’s “too much for his own good”
ackxhpaez: Jonathan Blow streams @naysayer88
localcanofdutchgold: Kapp
TeaLeafi: SCHOOOOL??????????? UR STARTING SCHOOL???
deva73: opening a university eh?
Ayyyy420Lmao: do you own or know about chainlink and sergey nazarov??
anotherkidnamedaustin: no make it a cult so u dont pay taxes
solitarynative: can you expand on that
inatreecrown: coding school
equipollent_z: LUL
anotherkidnamedaustin: el ron hubbard
braininavatt: HahaThink
jay_al97: @georgehotz I would signup for your school
Abnico: Special school?
TeaLeafi: SCHOOOOL??????????? UR STARTING SCHOOL??? ?
earthbender: LUL
theonlymonkas: are you in the cloud
bankzed: that's why Trump tried out University first before going into politics
toront0saur: LMAO
Mrclutch963: Favorite book?
christianthefalco: @blondephilia stop it with the crypto bullshit. it's for dummies and parasites
l1ght5p33d: school campus lifeee
voxelfox0125: Do you still do hack the box and HackerRank challenges?
doctorgenus: school about how to use the internet efficiently?!
64pillars: LULW
cellophane11578: university
theonlymonkas: CULT LUL
Hawklite: a bigger effect would be reforming public schools, not creating a university
yungdeli_: what state do you live in
anotherkidnamedaustin: yes! el ron hubbard!
jimmyadaro: lul
igg44705: @georgehotz did't you go to collage to get a phd once?
doctorgenus: or school about hacking?
martinkirilov: @georgehotz You know, it's funny in the UK they pay your Tuition Fees and they even give you Maintenance Loan and it's a very low interest one, maybe come study here, you don't need any money :D
TeaLeafi: A.I religion????n hahahah
benchai18: I’d drink the kool aid with u Jorge
pjayys77: Trump University is a good template
CoachMeech: i throw a leather ball real good. DO i get in?
PiroFloydian: carlson makes legit populist analysis and packages some fashy stuff into it
blondephilia: Most lucrative crypto in your opinion?
cellophane11578: LuL
bytebacon: SEGA Programming GOD https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gNHCxH35wYU
TeaLeafi: A.I religion?
mindfog: Kappa
zennydmt: do any high school kids apply to comma ai
likespuppies: > Dropped out of Uni > Creates his own
TeaLeafi: A.I religion? A.I religion?
anotherkidnamedaustin: George Carnigie College, where you get a scuffed folding protein degree
Nussinov: @georgehotz make sure you never grow your hair below your shoulders because then youll REALLY have a cult
nvda9: I can't afford college what should I do
anotherkidnamedaustin: we kove u goerge
jimmyadaro: 4:13 AM Here
THX1342: gn
inatreecrown: online school?
equipollent_z: what would you want from a coronavirus researcher if you had them in the room?
zeus13i: Will Comma hire me to work on this? ;)
TeaLeafi: A.I religion?
christianthefalco: REACT TO MEME VIDEOS
theonlymonkas: we do donations
903284hg39408gh23098h093f: anyone at comma have a phd?
l1ght5p33d: Fun fun fun till geohot said no more Qn A
blondephilia: I'll love you if you answered this question: Most lucrative crypto in your opinion?
anotherkidnamedaustin: make a carnigie college
TeaLeafi: A.I religion? ?
zwisch: what did you take at Carnegie Mellon?
Saltyballss: ever been in germany?
b2kemann: geo loves Q&A
Ayyyy420Lmao: did you get the SNEED joke from the simpsons?
tybutnowyoudie: are you planning on continuing the coq stuff?
MrTriharder: FeelsBadMan DONT GO GEORGE FeelsBadMan U ARE THE ONLY ENTERTAINMENT I HAVE FeelsBadMan
TeaLeafi: A.I religion?
PiroFloydian: be back tomorrow?
b2kemann: he will pass on this to his kids
voxelfox0125: @nvda9 Learn online for free
benchai18: Last time u said couple more min it went an hour exactly
deva73: should i get a phd ?
TeaLeafi: A.I religion??
doctorgenus: will you hire someone with a high IQ but no coding skills
theonlymonkas: favorite album
o______________________k: how to improve in programming ? @georgehotz
equipollent_z: what do you think about general AI? :D
zennydmt: have u applied information theory to multivariate distributions
likespuppies: @georgehotz Serious: I am 23 and average coder, how do I become great? What do I do?
cortickal: SNEED
Abnico: Are u bisexual?
GoodOlSmokey: @georgehotz what do you consider a good coder?
timi13462: python or java
williamjennings1: do you floss your teeth?
thecoder15: @georgehotz thoughts on Richard Feynman?
Exclamation_mark_CODE: Will you post the stream video somewhere?
benchai18: You still playing with coq???
ahahahaitslit: do you enjoy functional programming
Br4nnon: Java
INTeaRs: @georgehotz What programmers you looking for?
CoachMeech: why is this chat so obsessed with college
Ayyyy420Lmao: @cortickal never gets old
jimmyadaro: How much competitive is AI self-driving cars sector???
C0deCane: When is the announcement for comma bio labs?
blondephilia: Most lucrative crypto in your opinion?
TeaLeafi: i love you
anotherkidnamedaustin: STUPID QUESTION GO STUDY AND PRACTICE
NetAce: Any advice on managing ADHD, if you have that issue?
o______________________k: :(
toront0saur: pen testing jobs?
igg44705: @georgehotz did you read about the iq test for Ai by deepminds?
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LUL
TeaLeafi: i love you george you inspire me <3
anotherkidnamedaustin: i was gone 3hr cuz i had to read..
bytebacon: Do you hire people who only know Python and Javascript?
TeaLeafi: i love you george you inspire me <3 <3
jimmyadaro: How much competitive is AI self-driving cars sector??
solitarynative: git gud
Tyrant_01: GEORGE WHY NOT WINDOWS?
64pillars: 4Head
andydavies11: what do you think of OOP?
xhunter0001: how do you know
Br4nnon: study practice implement
anotherkidnamedaustin: IQ IS A JOKE
Nussinov: how do I make my brain smarter? Kappa
xhunter0001: if you're a good coder ?
igg44705: @georgehotz coffe test?
Abnico: Wait so you are bisexual?
ggtom: lmao
TeaLeafi: i love you george you inspire me <3 <3 <3
doctorgenus: Are we doing part 5 tomorrow?!!!!!!!
xhunter0001: how do you know if you're a good coder ?
pjayys77: in the end, just do it
blondephilia: Most lucrative crypto in your opinion?
Br4nnon: it's possible. wheels, motor, sensor
TeaLeafi: i love you george you inspire me <3 <3
K177: Kappa
equipollent_z: what if that house doesn't have cofffee :D
MrTriharder: KappaPride
solitarynative: keurig test LUL
itsxaos: BOOOOOoo bi master race KappaPride
localcanofdutchgold: KappaPride
TeaLeafi: i love you george you inspire me <3 <3 <3
zennydmt: do you use tensorflow or keras
Ayyyy420Lmao: you ever did ketamine?
equipollent_z: people are coffee ☕️
anotherkidnamedaustin: @georgehotz we should get into sativa
theonlymonkas: favorite song
benchai18: GeOrGe hOw I hAcK mY pEePeE iNtO gIrLs VaGeNE
deva73: BECOME TRUMP MAKE yourSElf great AGAIN
Nussinov: ah okay, so only into dudes KappaPride
birkett0011: An area that could use a big shake up is simulation software @georgehotz
K177: BITCOOONNEEEEECT
ShredderSherlock: does it have to pick the lock to your door?
christianthefalco: Is it okay if the robot kills all the humans first?
b2kemann: dog test: when you dog can drive your car, you win selfdriving cars
anotherkidnamedaustin: bitconnect lmao
cellophane11578: how does it know its coffee beans, and not rat poop?
bytebacon: Etherium
jimmyadaro: How much competitive is AI self-driving cars sector???
CheeseManUchiha: hey hey hey
bankzed: Biiiiiiiitconnnnnnnect
solitarynative: he means amoveo
igg44705: @georgehotz are you a postmodernist?
williamjennings1: how do you sleep if you just had coffee
Bootyclub: Opinions on Rust?
nizero: @georgehotz did u implement that new algorithm that came out of deepmind
xhunter0001: if you're a good coder ?
dyxx_pix: did u learning anything useful at cmu
64pillars: buying tesla stock anytime soon?
vix_dev: @georgehotz do you have a favorite programming language?
likespuppies: @georgehotz Ever done DMT?
4FUN_PLAYER: bitconeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
bytebacon: DMT
voxelfox0125: Can i advertise a great website for learning game hacking?
CoachMeech: dude drugs are bad for you
jimmyadaro: How much competitive is AI self-driving cars sector?
blondephilia: that's a bullshit answer :/
nozoke: do you wanna animal crossing stream?
toront0saur: pen testing at comma????
TeaLeafi: KETAMINE??!?!!
Abnico: KappaPride KappaPride KappaPride lmao is he really bisexual?
Codeoxic: Are hackathons worth doing?
THX1342: 1984 or Brave New World?
GoodOlSmokey: @georgehotz what do you consider a good coder? im trying to figure out what you answered before to that question and it's blurry on clip
903284hg39408gh23098h093f: @georgehotz favorite drug?
anotherkidnamedaustin: commabio where we make custom thc for clients
bravetraveller: what's your take on microdosing psilocybin?
MrTriharder: 5Head
bayarealove: adderalls the best baby
igg44705: @georgehotz would you become batman
ahahahaitslit: do you enjoy functional programming
anotherkidnamedaustin: thc strains
TeaLeafi: weird flex
b2kemann: did you meet the machine elves?
tybutnowyoudie: is there a drug you havent done?
whycopper: Did you go to school?
christianthefalco: @blondephilia why do you think?
ryanm0012: how do you feel about ketamine
CoachMeech: DRUGS ARE BAD
TeaLeafi: why is there a bed in your kitchen?
bytebacon: DO JOE ROGAN!
Nussinov: what is with you people so interested in what drugs he's done LUL
PhantoJah: dmt damn
nvda9: George is that true you were a icpc world finalist?
directrix13: In what language is the Android interface written?
voxelfox0125: Can i advertise a great website for learning game hacking?
hastingspb: !adderall
solitarynative: have you had ego death?
jimmyadaro: How much competitive is AI self-driving cars sector?
TeaLeafi: why is there a bed in your kitchen????
zennydmt: Do you like green tea or coffee?
wholesome_pepe: who are your biggest competitors outside of the US?
cellophane11578: time is a timecube
Br4nnon: php monkaS
zeus13i: Whats your daily caffeine limit? Why?
TeaLeafi: why is there a bed in your kitchen? ???
doctorgenus: do you ask the dumb leetcode questions in your interviews?
ImJ4Gu4R: make me mods?? im subscribe WutFace
likespuppies: @georgehotz You would really like crack, dont do it george
benchai18: Do u eat ass???????
theonlymonkas: do you sleep on the kithchen?
TeaLeafi: why is there a bed in your kitchen??????
blondephilia: @christianthefalco the fact that governments are falling apart proves crypto's worth. Your leaders are incompetent.
itsxaos: can we save politics or do we have to burn it down?
anotherkidnamedaustin: letting go of ur ego is genius 101
0R4NG3: benchai18, asking the real questions
cortickal: Permutation Sea?
cellophane11578: o what a great title for a book
Ayyyy420Lmao: you're an absolute nocoiner? no crypto whatsoever?
TeaLeafi: breaking through??
equipollent_z: not sure if I asked this already
cellophane11578: i gotta check it out
equipollent_z: what's outside of everything?
TeaLeafi: have you broken through?
HalluCinogen151: I achieved ego death from hitting a rock bottom
zennydmt: do you meditate?
LokkimestariN: Any suggestions how to learn low level C?
anotherkidnamedaustin: ego death is sooo genius 101. i want to know the 201 stuff...
theonlymonkas: how are you?
christianthefalco: @blondephilia that's a hopeful connection. You want it to be true more than you think it's actually true
Hawklite: do you think some questions can only be answered under the effect of drugs?
C0deCane: @georgehotz is PCP a possible cure? Check the stats?
synoborg: do you remember everything you read?
jimmyadaro: How much competitive is AI self-driving cars sector???
TeaLeafi: nice
benchai18: George, do u eat ass??????????????????
igg44705: @georgehotz can a neurosciences understand a microprocessor was really good man
RunnerMD: @georgehotz I'm a brain surgeon and I learn Python(ML/DL) to automatize some of our tasks(diagnosis more) or analyze some data. Do you think it is worth it?
bytebacon: DID JOE ROGAN OR JAMIE EVER APPROACH YOU?
TeaLeafi: nicenice
b2kemann: love how you don't like s-vally, but still so much of it is in you
TeaLeafi: george u inspire me??
64pillars: indica or sativa
anotherkidnamedaustin: @georgehotz ever read about collective consciouness? i have a good book for u MetaHuman
PiroFloydian: KEKW
Ayyyy420Lmao: you're an absolute nocoiner? no crypto whatsoever?
TeaLeafi: indica or sativa??
TeaLeafi: indica or sativa????
anotherkidnamedaustin: collective conscious theory
pjayys77: If Elon Musk could be president would you vote for him @georgehotz
Saltyballss: is this ur streaming outfit or are just not changing ur clothes?
zennydmt: do you have a ps4
likespuppies: @georgehotz Is leetcode relevant?
techtim123: name of the book again?
TeaLeafi: indica or sativa?????
nvda9: which school did you go in New Jersey
TheOnlyJoric: hey george hope you're having a good one bro
jimmyadaro: How much competitive is AI self-driving cars sector?
Tyrant_01: are you going to stream more now? i want to subs
toront0saur: BLOW IS THE BEST
b2kemann: are you a GOLD COINER?
igg44705: @georgehotz how can i meet you?
anotherkidnamedaustin: collective conscious theory thoughts?
theonlymonkas: do you sleep on the kithchen?
linkrager: do you think people are inherently "winners" and "losers" in whatever they do
TeaLeafi: indica or sativa????
nitrixen: @georgehotz How do you avoid procrastinating?
ggtom: are you a COOMER?
Ayyyy420Lmao: do you know about chainlink and sergey nazarov?
blondephilia: @christianthefalco They're incompetent and falling apart. You can believe whatever you want. Give it 20 years.
benchai18: Damn. U don’t eat ass????
bytebacon: Quantum computing next stream
TeaLeafi: are uy a coomer?
doctorgenus: is ur interviews a bunch of leetcode questions?
nic0latesla: do you have bitcoin?
TeaLeafi: are u a coomer?
C0deCane: LUL
ggtom: TeaLeafi helo fellow COOMER
anotherkidnamedaustin: thoughts on collective conscious theory??
jimmyadaro: Who doesn't eat ass? I will eat your mother
TeaLeafi: @ggtom hello!
opus_000: how do I make 100k this year
likespuppies: Favorite genre of porn?
nizero: George I tried to talk to at defcon but you didn't want to talk to me
voxelfox0125: Guys if you want to learn game hacking learn here. https://guidedhacking.com/
Ayyyy420Lmao: foot fetish yay or nay?
benchai18: @jimmyadaro Don’t forget my sis
ggtom: lmao
christianthefalco: @blondephilia not very actionable but good luck with your investments. Don't make it a personality trait tho lol
anotherkidnamedaustin: thoughts on collective conscious theory??? we all share the same conscious in my opinion
tybutnowyoudie: what do you think of comma offering affirm as a payment option?
MrTriharder: D:
jimmyadaro: @benchai18 Aight
zennydmt: what was your worst subject in high school
deva73: should i create a twitchj bot to ban all CRYPTO USERS😡
CheeseManUchiha: jailbreaking the simulation is one of my favorite 'talks'
CoachMeech: @georgehotz why san diego?
ahahahaitslit: the way i am
jimmyadaro: @CheeseManUchiha WTF
GoodOlSmokey: but i cant take a shit in the bathroom without
peter35_: his best song imo
blondephilia: @christianthefalco very actionable. People make their living off of marketing this in various ways. Which is why I ask about crypto.
nizero: you were sorta in the zone in CTF competition
Cazaa_: ufff nicee
0R4NG3: PogChamp
jellyjar: damn george got bars
theonlymonkas: boy about to drop some bars
l1ght5p33d: get it
Ayyyy420Lmao: sick rhymes
xSynchronizeD: PogChamp white eminem
Saltyballss: PogChamp no doubletime
plumydev: yo geohot!
localcanofdutchgold: rap god Pog
alameda13: favorite childhood video game @georgehotz
MrTriharder: PogChamp
TeaLeafi: white rappppper lmaooo
braininavatt: TwitchLit TwitchLit TwitchLit
0R4NG3: PogChamp 🔥
benchai18: George. I’m at the side door
TeaLeafi: oooooof
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: new geo track PogChamp
Cazaa_: ufffffff
jimmyadaro: NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp
CheeseManUchiha: SourPls
ackxhpaez: How to judge if a start up is going to be successful?
jimmyadaro: NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp
ad_1337: TriHard
TheLastMrX: wow
braininavatt: CurseLit CurseLit CurseLit
theonlymonkas: LUL BARS
rustduck: TriHard 🔥
cellophane11578: 4Head
benchai18: IN THE AIR
jimmyadaro: NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp
TeaLeafi: oooof
jimmyadaro: dayumn
MrTriharder: NEXT SLIM SHADY PogChamp NEXT SLIM SHADY PogChamp NEXT SLIM SHADY PogChamp NEXT SLIM SHADY PogChamp NEXT SLIM SHADY PogChamp
TeaLeafi: FIRE
anotherkidnamedaustin: id love to know your thoughts on collective conscious theory??? we all share the same conscious in my opinion...
jimmyadaro: fireaf
wholesome_pepe: moms spaghetti
jimmyadaro: NotLikeThis PogChamp
MrTriharder: NEXT SLIM SHADY PogChamp NEXT SLIM SHADY PogChamp NEXT SLIM SHADY PogChamp NEXT SLIM SHADY PogChamp NEXT SLIM SHADY PogChamp NEXT SLIM SHADY PogChamp /
travbicklee: NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp
theonlymonkas: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
THX1342: have you ever tried paragliding?
TeaLeafi: nahhhh he aint
igg44705: @georgehotz so if i see you, i should't say HI?
Cazaa_: NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
Landepbs: Are the trained models for OpenPilot publicly available?
benchai18: IM TIRED
doctorgenus: i came here for the rap, got what i came for
rndmsqnce: What's the last thing that made you angry?
jimmyadaro: NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp
Cazaa_: DAAAMN!!!
TeaLeafi: nahhhhhhhhhhhh
solitarynative: was LUL
deva73: slim shady
andydavies11: Is OOP bullshit?
bytebacon: I was a child in the nineties Take a ride with me, while we all recall Walbo and prank phone calls Bumpers for your bowling ball And we be hittin' em all cause this is New Jersey And stay up late but still wake up early To get to school with your seat belt buckled Pokemon cards taught me how to hustle And kids wrote orgy on their backpacks What did that mean? When my parents left home for the evening Googling, I found a splash screen That asked me
jimmyadaro: NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp NotLikeThis PogChamp
Saltyballss: PogChamp white 50 cent
TeaLeafi: nahhhhhhhhhh
Ayyyy420Lmao: do the one where he writes a letter!!!
voxelfox0125: Browse around this website for 5min https://guidedhacking.com/
techtim123: Transcendence in our lifetime??
benchai18: CUZ I AM
TeaLeafi: moms spaghetti rip
theonlymonkas: baaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaars
ggtom: throwback to geohot raps
anotherkidnamedaustin: tomcr00se
TeaLeafi: cooooomer
jimmyadaro: nice
TeaLeafi: cooooooooooomer
Cazaa_: NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
equipollent_z: nexySenpai
64pillars: do u think winners can become losers and vice versa
TeaLeafi: tomcr0000se
TeaLeafi: lmao
TeaLeafi: nah
bytebacon: RAP!
ggtom: TeaLeafi ah imma.. imma coooming
igg44705: @georgehotz so if i see you in the street i should't say HI?
benchai18: All I’ve learned is that George doesn’t eat ass
anotherkidnamedaustin: id love to know your thoughts on collective conscious theory???
jimmyadaro: @64pillars that's life
zwisch: do you use photogrammetry techniques at comm.ai or is it all DNNs?
ryanm0012: ketamine i must
rndmsqnce: What's the last thing that made you angry??
ggtom: lmao winner-loser mobility
nvda9: George you should make more music
T3chHS: Are there better rappers that you at comma.ai?
directrix13: Eminem just sounds like he's whining in all his music.
Ayyyy420Lmao: Eminem - Stan (Long Version) ft. Dido sing this one man
FriscoDeluxe: You been playing around with any 3D programming? like Vulkan or DX12?
theonlymonkas: will tomcr00se come back?
tajpouria: Godzilla
jimmyadaro: ResidentSleeper
nizero: George I tried to shake your hand but you said get away from me freak .. I don't want Corona
C0deCane: LUL who keeps asking these loser winner questions lol were all losers and winners at some point
tybutnowyoudie: do you get recognized a lot in public?
Exclamation_mark_CODE: New plan. Say hi to geo hotz in the street so he starts rapping PogChamp
pjayys77: any philosophy books
jimmyadaro: 4:20 here
braininavatt: if I see you on the street I will ask you for my toaster Kappa
doctorgenus: how do we pick up George Hotz lolol
m0ld_0n3rz: https://clips.twitch.tv/PoisedAmusedTurtleFeelsBadMan
rorhug: You should CALL some people on the stream
Nussinov: I would say "yoooooo" then raise my hand for a high five 4Head
bankzed: the most appropriate level of interaction in the streets is a head nod
Ayyyy420Lmao: foot fetish yay or nay?
nitrixen: @georgehotz How do you avoid procrastinating / stay motivated?
zwisch: do you use photogrammetry techniques at comm.ai or is it all DNNs?
bytebacon: GEORGE PLEASE SING COLD WAR SONG
anotherkidnamedaustin: collective conscious theory
anotherkidnamedaustin: ?
C0deCane: it you find a 5 dollar bill on the ground in my eyes your a fuckin champ
opus_000: fist bump and walk away
jimmyadaro: @braininavatt lmao
benchai18: Lotta dumb questions huh? He’s not ur guru folks. He’s brilliant, he’s fascinating, inspiring.... but he’s not fucking Siddartha
T3chHS: Are there better rappers than you at comma.ai?
64pillars: can you make art
Saltyballss: if your sitting in a bar and i would come over licking your forehead would be inappropriate?
rndmsqnce: What's the last thing that made you angry?
mikey9988: no cmonBruh
julien9877: yes PogChamp
igg44705: @georgehotz do you not like the spot light on you?
CoachMeech: LUL pls
Santiago_LHC: CALLS!
voxelfox0125: Browse around this website for 5min https://guidedhacking.com/
williamjennings1: lol
daxyxy98: new Shkreli PogChamp
Forest_Turner: CALL ELON
Saltyballss: call elon musk
Nussinov: call your viewers LUL
GoodOlSmokey: @georgehotz any suggestions on focus loss while studying?
anotherkidnamedaustin: https://www.instagram.com/georgehotz/
C0deCane: Egirl skype calls about corona virus @georgehotz LUL
equipollent_z: do you miss hacking challenges at all?
theonlymonkas: DO IT
martinkirilov: Say hi as long as you're not invading someone's personal space. Think about someone meeting you on the street and start talking nonsense out of nowhere, no bueno
Santiago_LHC: CALL OBAMA
b2kemann: georg the guru
Ayyyy420Lmao: boobs or ass?
andydavies11: is OOP bullshit?
anotherkidnamedaustin: collective conscious theory..
CoachMeech: stream zoom
jimmyadaro: @andydavies11 how?
solitarynative: @benchai18 hi, its me, siddartha :)
64pillars: do you have any artistic abilities
whycopper: Call ligma!
r0xtehem0x: Do you have a favorite CI system?
nremind: can we get a sub goal for you to voluntarily get covid for the stream?
Tyrant_01: HACKING OR PROGRAMMING ?
anotherkidnamedaustin: NO ANSWER MINE
Br4nnon: OOP Kreygasm
freshsoclean: do you miss WoW?
RunnerMD: @georgehotz for implementing ML/DL in medicine (Diagnosis based on MRI/CT etc) do you think you need to learn specifically Python (almost 0 knowledge) or you can do it in R (which I already know a bit).
pjayys77: you want to do that ... with chat...
igg44705: @georgehotz do you not like to be in the spot light?
TeaLeafi: Will coding be a thing of the past soon? Thank to machine learning? and automatic A.I?
anotherkidnamedaustin: thoughts on collective consciousness
benchai18: @solitarynative Nice tits
NetAce: OOP more like OOPS
doctorgenus: wait you said school is a scam, why are you starting a school?
rndmsqnce: What's the last thing that made you angry?
theonlymonkas: do you have elon musk phone number?
TeaLeafi: Will coding be a thing of the past soon? Thank to machine learning? and automatic A.I??
bytebacon: Is programming a scam?
TeaLeafi: Will coding be a thing of the past soon? Thank to machine learning? and automatic A.I????
anotherkidnamedaustin: GOOGLE IT
directrix13: @georgehotz if you're sitting at a bar and a person has a 30% chance of giving you Coronavirus what is the probability that you will regret your decision of going to a bar?
b2kemann: thoughts on jordan peterson?
jimmyadaro: @TeaLeafi What's "soon" for ya?
martinkirilov: you mean POOP?
THX1342: favorite exploit?
thecoder15: who do you look up to lately @georgehotz
TeaLeafi: Will coding be a thing of the past soon? Thank to machine learning? and automatic A.I? ?????
nvda9: @voxelfox0125 bookmarked. thanks
benchai18: Go watch Lex dude
blondephilia: Theranos LUL
voxelfox0125: Browse around this website for 5min https://guidedhacking.com/
cortickal: Is "Permutation City" the book you mentioned @georgehotz
unnamedtroll: what a time to be alive
TeaLeafi: @jimmyadaro next 5 years
theonlymonkas: favorite album?
Nussinov: this stream is a scam
THX1342: favorite exploit type?
jimmyadaro: @TeaLeafi Nah, we're fine
HalluCinogen151: over 1k per class
T3chHS: Are there better rappers than you at comma.ai?
doctorgenus: gotcha
MrTriharder: Says the guy who was in CMU LUL
l1ght5p33d: This stream is the only not scam
mikey9988: you used to play WoW ? LUL
blondephilia: *Harvard* and *Yale*
toront0saur: PEN TESTING AT COMMA ???
dyxx_pix: is cmu a scam?
anotherkidnamedaustin: lmao google collective conscious. youll like it
HalluCinogen151: Of stuff you can learn online
igg44705: @georgehotz is it because of the cost of harvard?
benchai18: Dumbass questions. Just wanna know if u fucking eat ass bro. I don’t care about hAxing
ahahahaitslit: have you read watchmen
l1ght5p33d: This stream is the least scam of anything
TeaLeafi: @jimmyadaro ooooof
anotherkidnamedaustin: mr meditation
b2kemann: like gucci is a scam
TeaLeafi: RAP BATTLE me!!!
zennydmt: how did you like Operating Systems from CMU?
Bootyclub: Opinions on Rust?
C0deCane: We'd have to get the data first
solitarynative: you should start a pseudo intellectual youtube movie critic channel
equipollent_z: covid RCE?
TeaLeafi: RAP BATTLE ME!!!!!!!!!!
CoachMeech: @georgehotz would you say you generally concur with Thiel on the education system ?
nvda9: George was a member of PPP team
dyxx_pix: was cmu a scam?
Ayyyy420Lmao: you got any original rap song??
MrTriharder: HARVARD AND YALE IS SCAM PogChamp Graduates from Carnegie Mellon LUL
PiroFloydian: RAP BATTLE PogChamp
birkett0011: What you think of simulation software? Anylogic / https://hash.ai/
b2kemann: it's just clothes!!!
realolejka: kendrick is the goat
jimmyadaro: @Ayyyy420Lmao Yep
NetAce: https://adventofcode.com/ - When Geo was asked how he defines if someone is good at coding, he recommended this as a starting point.
cellophane11578: bars sicker than sars
Bombapil0t: corona jailbreaked ?
theonlymonkas: favorite rapper
xxxelent: y pay for knowledge when the internet is a thing, y congregate to share knowledge when wiki literally is the sum of all human knowledge in one place, completely free
Nussinov: @georgehotz do you know anything about twitch or other twitch streamers?
anotherkidnamedaustin: def tomcr00se = goat print(tomcr00se)
zennydmt: Did you like the course Operating Systems from CMU
nizero: George have you heard of nerdcore rappers?
jimmyadaro: gucci gang?
tajpouria: What are u think about deno js
TeaLeafi: feeels
igg44705: @georgehotz do you have a degree?
doctorgenus: but when you hire, would you prefer someone with Harvard CS, over no degree
PiroFloydian: but it looks like a scam @georgehotz
unnamedtroll: taxes are a scam
pjayys77: King of the Doot
benchai18: George u ever had the clap?
b2kemann: gucci is just clothes!!!
anotherkidnamedaustin: Collective consciousness, collective conscience, or collective conscious is the set of shared beliefs, ideas, and moral attitudes which operate as a unifying force within society. In general, it does not refer to the specifically moral conscience, but to a shared understanding of social norms
techtim123: UV air scrubbers? ?
benchai18: I know u get around
jimmyadaro: @anotherkidnamedaustin Bullshit
worrasenule: code jam 2020?
realolejka: savage
Br4nnon: a real HS PogChamp
almonte550: how much do you make in twitch?
bankzed: speaking of scams, best streamer in the topic is kitboga
deva73: cool
cortickal: You might be interested in listening to Peter Thiel on university @georgehotz
CoachMeech: why are you plebs so obsessed with university
blondephilia: That's how you know collective consciousness is real. People still give Harvard credence.
nvda9: You can get into prestigious school donating hell lot of money.
itsxaos: is there any way to reduce the size of governenment/institutions without burning them down?
un3okapi: @georgehotz do you believe in love?
theonlymonkas: opinion on Gennady Korotkevich
anotherkidnamedaustin: @jimmyadaro collective conscious is bullshit?
bytebacon: Richard Dawkins exposes quantum charlatan Deepak Chopra: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jfVIl1UUQns
nitrixen: @georgehotz How do you avoid procrastinating / stay motivated?
solitarynative: read jed mckenna
TeaLeafi: same with Google?
jimmyadaro: @itsxaos Minarchism??
Jehhred: Have you read 'The Fifth Science'??!?!?!?!?
jimmyadaro: @anotherkidnamedaustin Yep, it's
dyxx_pix: does legacy count for cmu admissions
CoachMeech: throwing a big leather ball usually helps as well
zennydmt: do you keep in touch with siraj raval/ He asked you 73 questions right at the party?
nic0latesla: please explain how you hacked sony
Ayyyy420Lmao: have you read stuff by hans herman hoppe?
martinkirilov: @nitrixen Wrong person to ask :D
deva73: knowing people like know who?
cortickal: Richard Dawkins is a charlatan too
equipollent_z: have you seen any good computer architectures?
PiroFloydian: LUL
benchai18: William H Macy can get u a degree
tajpouria: do u believe in god
MrTriharder: Gennedy Korokevik monkaS
nvda9: he worked at Google as a security engineer
igg44705: @georgehotz would you say you love your life?
birkett0011: @georgehotz What you think of simulation field?
almonte550: How much do you make in Twitch?
C0deCane: Hows North Korea doing right now
anotherkidnamedaustin: @jimmyadaro good one
ahahahaitslit: his name is tourist?
pjayys77: wonder if MIT is a scam
anotherkidnamedaustin: what have u read on it? the wiki?
Ayyyy420Lmao: @pjayys77 ask terry davis
jimmyadaro: @anotherkidnamedaustin I've talked enough about that to know it's bs
dyxx_pix: what r the chances that u read my messages
Bombapil0t: Let’s take this out of the courtroom and into the streets
wholesome_pepe: do u get into natural language processing or just visual stuff?
anti_natalist: @anotherkidnamedaustin would a shared set of beliefs and morals just be genetic and environmental rather than some collective immaterial conssciousness?
dyslexicat: banned monkaS
bytebacon: Who is you favourite prof?
techtim123: book suggestions??
theonlymonkas: favorite album
MrTriharder: @georgehotz Comma.ai planning to expand in North Korea?
blondephilia: I care :)
C0deCane: @georgehotz change your nickname to biohots until corona is over
Ayyyy420Lmao: do you know about TempleOS and terry davis?
jimmyadaro: -1000 per month?
Br4nnon: sentient ai
voxelfox0125: something really funny https://guidedhacking.com/forums/wall-of-shame.462/
nvda9: are you single now?
TeaLeafi: what do you do for fun?????????????????????
YoungGuns_: are you still going for your instagram goal? @georgehotz
tajpouria: we care bro
TeaLeafi: are u single?>
Bootyclub: @georgehotz What do you think about Rust?
likespuppies: What's your favorite genre of porn?
igg44705: @georgehotz can you not work and still live the same lifestyle?
zennydmt: what do you think of siraj raval
bytebacon: Do you read books?
theonlymonkas: we care
Saltyballss: i just subscribed for older videos tbh LUL
TheOnlyJoric: this stream is one of the better ones, very interesting and i like a lot of the discussion
Maizlow90: @georgehotz https://www.karger.com/Article/FullText/89211
Ayyyy420Lmao: do you know about TempleOS and terry davis? if not google it srsly
tybutnowyoudie: What do you think of affirm?
realolejka: @jimmyadaro guee it's 100 dollars
YoungGuns_: fuck instagram @georgehotz
Bombapil0t: instagram 2019 DansGame
0R4NG3: lol
theonlymonkas: favorite song
equipollent_z: what's your favorite wargame of all time?
Hawklite: should prostitution be legal
64pillars: fav most recently released song
FriscoDeluxe: You been doing any 3D programming? like Vulkan or DX12?
jimmyadaro: @realolejka Or 10
TeaLeafi: are you single??????????????
rorhug: You have the checkmark!
rorhug: chekc it
efthemess: efthemess subscribed at Tier 1.
b2kemann: you do have a wikipedia though
Nussinov: @georgehotz what are your viewer demographics?
martinkirilov: you don't even post at instagram
C0deCane: @Ayyyy420Lmao he has like videos that are streamed on twitch i have seen them before
TeaLeafi: pay 10k for a check mark!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
bytebacon: Do you have book shelf?
AresRai: why not have a personal checkmarked twitter acc @georgehotz
anotherkidnamedaustin: @anti_natalist so u deeply believe in the we all came from a single cell scam
whycopper: Pls say hi to me hehe
igg44705: @b2kemann true that
doctorgenus: wait, I thought you use linkedin as your dating profile!!!
jimmyadaro: We need more rap @georgehotz
nvda9: lol
TeaLeafi: pay 10k on instagram they will give you blue check mark
theonlymonkas: the checkmark is there lol
likespuppies: @georgehotz How much of what you think and say is original?
Exclamation_mark_CODE: just get a checkmark on StayHomeHUB
AresRai: why not have a personal checkmarked twitter acc ? @georgehotz
anotherkidnamedaustin: @jimmyadaro how is it bullshit
anotherkidnamedaustin: ur answer is vague
andydavies11: Do you like sports?
Ayyyy420Lmao: do you know about TempleOS and terry davis? if not google it srsly
deva73: dude whats a scam and whats not?
martinkirilov: @aresral he has one
anti_natalist: @anotherkidnamedaustin as opposed to what? a divine creator?
dyxx_pix: do u think cmu was a scam?
nizero: @georgehotz do you need any data labeled?
rorhug: You have the public figure checkmark. Look at it
voxelfox0125: something extremely funny https://guidedhacking.com/forums/wall-of-shame.462/ browse normal threads.
TeaLeafi: hoookers!!! they are fun!!!
jimmyadaro: Sports or e-Sports??
igg44705: @georgehotz are you rich? cold war rap was amazing
solitarynative: lamda school good or no
wholesome_pepe: just hack instagram Kappa
CoachMeech: nah
TeaLeafi: hoookers are fun!!!!
jimmyadaro: @solitarynative Nah
PiroFloydian: What if something tells you its a scam @georgehotz ?
braininavatt: PogChamp
blondephilia: nah
TeaLeafi: hookers are fun what you mean????!!
braininavatt: congrats
nvda9: tomcr00se is cool. you should make more George
braininavatt: Kappa
l1ght5p33d: Nah
Br4nnon: lmfao
blondephilia: you have it bro :)
64pillars: lol
Br4nnon: scuffed checkmark
Bombapil0t: You’re fucking with the dude who got the keys to your safe. that was such a beautiful time back then.
theonlymonkas: you can get that checkmark yourself George!
YoungGuns_: budget checkmark
bokeee_: lmao
benchai18: They do. My friends from 90 Day Fiancé have it
Chrimo: Youre a public dude
jimmyadaro: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
localcanofdutchgold: scammed OMEGALUL
THX1342: LUL
AresRai: LUL
evnomics: lmao
b2kemann: looool
CoachMeech: lmao they clowning on your ass bro
dyxx_pix: ahhahahahhahaa
dorkmo: TROLLFACE
itsxaos: LUL
TeaLeafi: SCAMMMED
jimmyadaro: LUL LUL
dyslexicat: not even a checkmark LUL
equipollent_z: LUL
jimmyadaro: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
almonte550: You are half verified!!!!
tybutnowyoudie: 50% check mark
xSynchronizeD: BTEC CHECKMARK LUL
TeaLeafi: SCAMMMMEd
Bombapil0t: scam
jimmyadaro: LUL LUL LUL
dyxx_pix: get scammed
braininavatt: YOU DID IT!!!!! VoHiYo
rndmsqnce: anyone can write public figure
reckful_bald_spot_114: LUL
phrixus_bro: public figure hell yeah playboy
TeaLeafi: SCAMMMMMM
4FUN_PLAYER: scuffed check mark
Ayyyy420Lmao: scammed
ConnorMusarra: that just means you have a business account
TeaLeafi: SCAMMMMMEd
THX1342: "Not Good Enough" SeemsGood
TheLastMrX: LUL LUL
b2kemann: you're not worthy yet
TeaLeafi: SCAMMMMMEd lmaoooooooooooooooo
whycopper: Lmfaoooo
costcospizza: they did u dirty
doctorgenus: close enough
travbicklee: scammed
tajpouria: yeah half check mark
peter35_: we must chimp
williamjennings1: isnt it becuase you have a business account
doctorgenus: it'll impress girls
itsxaos: now THIS is a scam
benchai18: That’s the aspergers check
TeaLeafi: dirty my boy
ConnorMusarra: thats designated by you not instagram
deva73: budget check mark lol
voxelfox0125: something extremely funny https://guidedhacking.com/forums/wall-of-shame.462/ browse normal threads.
CheeseManUchiha: public figure andy
almonte550: You are not worth a full check mark
zennydmt: have u met mark zuckerberg
nvda9: hahaha
roystang: @georgehotz can you even do the fibonacci bro
Saltyballss: so instagram is a scam
THX1342: LUL
theonlymonkas: means you are almost famous
ImJ4Gu4R: how dare facebook dont give geo blue checkmark
TeaLeafi: AHHAHAHAAHAHHAHAHAHA
hastingspb: what is the good music @georgehotz
jellyjar: big surprise
jimmyadaro: LUL LUL LUL LUL
benchai18: Nice pic bro
theonlymonkas: LUL
ImJ4Gu4R: fak em
tybutnowyoudie: surprise
TeaLeafi: 92 male
Exclamation_mark_CODE: consolation checkmark so you stop complaining Kappa
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: squadW
pjayys77: participation trophy
aaaakshat: LUL
doctorgenus: just show girls your wikipedia
techtim123: book suggestions??
christianthefalco: 7% are Trans
mikey9988: LUL
4FUN_PLAYER: LUL
CoachMeech: hahaha
FriscoDeluxe: 5% troll men
igg44705: @georgehotz you need to verify your ID to get the cheak mark
TeaLeafi: 92 male muahhahaha
haircutjimmy: hi George
dyxx_pix: do u like logic, the rapper
TeaLeafi: AHAHAHAHAHAHAHAH
janpoonthong: Apple Or Samsung? And Why?
brownyyyylocks: @doctorgenus nope
solitarynative: I'm trans girl
nvda9: lmao
blondephilia: just like Google huh LUL
jimmyadaro: C.O.D
inciMage: not enough
nremind: you have to suck off zuck to get the checkmark @georgehotz
anotherkidnamedaustin: lol people believe in the single cell origin scam
b2kemann: 8% is alot of fish
ahahahaitslit: i'm surprised it's not 100%
CoachMeech: KILL ALL MEN
TeaLeafi: im a GIRL
birkett0011: @georgehotz Simulation software like this https://www.anylogic.com/ cost like $20,000 per license all java back end and is dumpster to use
equipollent_z: do you still work on Qira?
TeaLeafi: IM A GIRL!!!!
benchai18: George how tall r u
Cazaa_: fuck instagram and fuck society
jimmyadaro: Hey, sports or e-sports? @georgehotz
TeaLeafi: IM A GIRL!!!
dyxx_pix: do u like logic, the rappe
Ayyyy420Lmao: do you know about TempleOS and terry davis? if not google it srsly
nvda9: true
Nussinov: bitches love wikipedia
ConnorMusarra: just apply for verification and send them 3 pieces of recent press about you
christianthefalco: IM A GIRL!!!!
TeaLeafi: IM A GIRL!!......
Jehhred: How much would you pay for a checkmark??!?!?!?!
christianthefalco: IM A GIRL!!!!!
voxelfox0125: something extremely funny https://guidedhacking.com/forums/wall-of-shame.462/ browse normal threads.
TeaLeafi: IM A GIRL!!........
TeaLeafi: IM A GIRL!!...........
almonte550: IM A GIRL!!!!
TeaLeafi: IM A GIRL!!.............
theonlymonkas: favorite rapper
4FUN_PLAYER: IM A GIRL
solitarynative: I have a feminine penis :)
christianthefalco: IM A GIRL!!!!!!
benchai18: I met eBays Chief diversity Officer. SUCH A LAME JOB
Bombapil0t: DansGame
anotherkidnamedaustin: do we exist, or do we think we exist which makes us exist?
nizero: why are Instagram dms the way to get girls these days... seems sorta strange
realolejka: public figure badge isn't even clickable at mobile
LordDankington: IM A GIRL
TeaLeafi: IM A GIRL!!...........
martinkirilov: IM A GIRL
whycopper: My dick big but I’m a girl
itsxaos: TITS OR GTFO
janpoonthong: Apple Or Samsung? And Why?
almonte550: IM A GIRL!!!!!!!!!!
rustduck: HotPokket me
jimmyadaro: "This is my girl penis" like Shameless hahahaa
C0deCane: @georgehotz I heard that people under 5'11'' are more at risk
dyxx_pix: lmfao @whycopper
solitarynative: IM GRIL
roystang: im a girl i rpomise
benchai18: GEORGE WHAT HAPPENED TO ELISA LAM
thecoder15: lolz
bokeee_: girl huh atpDog
vix_dev: GIRL stands for Guy In Real Life
doctorgenus: these girls gold diggers
theonlymonkas: LUL
equipollent_z: :D
Br4nnon: iM aLsO a GiRl
bojosos: Have you ever used Emscripten?
benchai18: @georgehotz seriously. Elisa Lam. Investigate
igg44705: @georgehotz DO YOU LIFT BRUH? or martial arts? or anything physical? sky diving?
pjayys77: there is suddenly a lot of girls in the chat, diversity solved
TeaLeafi: George take me on date <3? i will show you a good time! <3
Saltyballss: im divers
zennydmt: are ur family members into tech like you?
TeaLeafi: George take me on date <3? i will show you a good time! <3!
nvda9: hahaha
whycopper: Lmfaaaooooo
TeaLeafi: George take me on date <3? i will show you a good time! <3!!
toront0saur: TITTS OUT FOR THE BOYS!
benchai18: @georgehotz FOR REAL. CAN U INVESTIGATE MYSTERIES LIKE ELISA LAM. SERIOUSKLY
Cazaa_: you dont need that , you are a fucking god mann wtf
benchai18: ELISA
bytebacon: DO YOU HAVE SIBLINGS
rustduck: monkaS
jimmyadaro: WHAT
Br4nnon: drugs
benchai18: yes
TeaLeafi: George take me on date <3? i will show you a good time! <3!!! <3
GoodOlSmokey: communist retroviruses are worse than non communist ones?
Nussinov: monkaS
K177: Lmao you call yourself a [insert streamer] fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
braininavatt: monkaS
dyxx_pix: geo can u calculate the probability that you will get corona
Lieutenant_51: FeelsBadMan
likespuppies: @georgehotz Favorite meat?
btpisroot: Advent of Code was what was mentioned earlier correct? Never looked at it before, but it seems interesting.
shieeeeeeeeet: @georgehotz do you use any note-taking apps to manage your thoughts/backlog?
anotherkidnamedaustin: i got my college paid 100% for, so i scammed them technically. studied for MCAT and didnt take it
jimmyadaro: @GoodOlSmokey Sure
voxelfox0125: something extremely funny https://guidedhacking.com/forums/wall-of-shame.462/ browse normal threads.
equipollent_z: have you ever studied Complexity Systems Science?
THX1342: is she the chick from the elevator?
TeaLeafi: okay
aaaakshat: you might need to purchase the 1m2020.com domain
benchai18: Watch the video
Ayyyy420Lmao: how many of decimals of pi do you know?
andydavies11: will there ever be a boy born who can swim faster than a shark?
TeaLeafi: hunnnnny
birkett0011: LUL
theonlymonkas: D E E P
CoachMeech: hahahahaha
b2kemann: loool
benchai18: U can
jimmyadaro: @shieeeeeeeeet Markdown files
MrTriharder: @georgehotz Linkedin vs Tinder for dating?
b2kemann: networking
alanantonio1234: ola
pjayys77: the water tank?
TeaLeafi: okayyyyyyyyyy
b2kemann: the right way
benchai18: Watch the video of her in the LA hotel
nvda9: George, are you a wizard?
TeaLeafi: i TAKE IT DADDDY <3
Ayyyy420Lmao: how many decimals of pi do you know?
aaaakshat: we need 1 million followers on insta by 2020
dyxx_pix: can u calculate the probability that u will get covid-19
anotherkidnamedaustin: i took that shit. high school was easy 4.0 clap and got full ride to iowa
TeaLeafi: i TAKE IT DADDDY <3 <3
anotherkidnamedaustin: scammed them
solitarynative: like?
alanantonio1234: soda
jimmyadaro: @MrTriharder Linkedin is not for dating mf
Nussinov: I used to scam people in runescape
TeaLeafi: i TAKE IT DADDDY <3 <3 <3
doctorgenus: what's the take from college?
zennydmt: bumble?
Br4nnon: tinder used to be decent
christianthefalco: START
likespuppies: Computer science degree is being on the take :)
Nussinov: trimming armor Kappa
zennydmt: is bumble any good?
MrTriharder: @jimmyadaro Linkedin is lowkey dating
aaaakshat: you should try grindr
tajpouria: good night
bankzed: it's all about hinge Kappa
jimmyadaro: Sports or e-sports?
b2kemann: but is stem at harvard a scam?
TeaLeafi: GRINDR
jimmyadaro: @MrTriharder Fuck nah
K177: LOL
anotherkidnamedaustin: be a scammer so u dont get scammed. its simple, and turn off the stupid movies and study
Hawklite: comma.dating
evnomics: TRUE
pjayys77: mhmm go on
K177: HotPokket sexist
theonlymonkas: and being on the take can give you some opportunities?
dyslexicat: true LULW
kernelimage: It’s true!!
equipollent_z: comma dating
whycopper: What about pornhub premium?
dyxx_pix: can u calculate the chances that u will get covid-19
braininavatt: they have done it
bojosos: Make CommaDate or OpenDate or something
Ayyyy420Lmao: comma tinder
jimmyadaro: comma.dating !!!! lmao
jimmyadaro: Sports or e-sports?
Jehhred: My Christian Mingle account is lit though
igg44705: @georgehotz what do you think about stoicism?
christianthefalco: Dead On Arrival
MrTriharder: HotPokket EQUALITY
deva73: that genius
kernelimage: Apps disgust me
AresRai: comma.dating
Srule: poor people single forever :-(
ConnorMusarra: Raya is trying
almonte550: dating.comma.ai
aaaakshat: comma.ai/dating
zennydmt: so real life is better than dating apps?
aaaakshat: XDD
bytebacon: Time for Comma.sex?
narkoSays: apart for men who don't wanna pay money 4Head
Saltyballss: comma . onme Kappa
equipollent_z: this joke is going to turn into the largest profit lol
bankzed: SF bars or NYC bars?
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: sqquadW Reverse the roles
rndmsqnce: raya isnt bad
almonte550: comma.onme
Jehhred: 70/30 sounds better
aaaakshat: cum.ai
l1ght5p33d: still 95% men
dyslexicat: Saltyballss Kappa
almonte550: HAHAHAHAHAHA
Lieutenant_51: comma.ai/dating invest now
anotherkidnamedaustin: So being born a male, is a SCAM?
bojosos: And a CommaFold would go a long way
nremind: I thought that's what usually happens except men buy premium or whatever
MrTriharder: @georgehotz whats with this gender discrimination?
THX1342: LUL
jimmyadaro: cum.ai LUL
igg44705: @georgehotz thoughts on stoicism?
tajpouria: how to identify men and women
tybutnowyoudie: that's sexist
whycopper: @georgehotz is phub premium a scam you think?
jimmyadaro: Sports or e-sports?
TeaLeafi: AHAHHAAHAHAHAHAH
TeaLeafi: GRNDRR
toront0saur: BUMBLE
benchai18: @georgehotz If u investigate mysteries the same way u learned bio, you’ll pull 5000 subs easily. Like Death of Elisa Lam.
ShredderSherlock: they could pay women to be on there
christianthefalco: It's effectively that way with premium memberships
bankzed: SF bars are 1% to 99% and NYC is 55% to 45%
Srule: What if my dating app doesn't have enough white people? Should I start charging minorities?
likespuppies: @georgehotz You can only eat one animal for the rest of your life, which one? Not cow
anotherkidnamedaustin: x and y chromosome
GoodOlSmokey: what time is it there?
reckful_bald_spot_114: that would be your typical sex worker website
K177: LOL
PiroFloydian: now youre just skewing wealthier men @georgehotz
TeaLeafi: women are scamms
TeaLeafi: women are scams!!!!
christianthefalco: @ShredderSherlock i'd sign up 100 women profiles
jay_al97: @georgehotz then it will be a place for gold diggers
K177: gachiHYPER
solitarynative: what are you experiences with grindr?
itsxaos: but how do you handle bi
tybutnowyoudie: what if I am trans? I have to pay 50%?
Br4nnon: online dating sux
blondephilia: u get sued
PiroFloydian: Gay people exist?
jimmyadaro: Sports or e-sports?
anotherkidnamedaustin: its 2020 the gender lines are blurred @georgehotz
TeaLeafi: gay people lmaooo
itsxaos: youll have to make a straight only app
AresRai: different business
im_francuzz: when you create they could ask for the identity card @georgehotz
bokeee_: ROFL
zennydmt: so whats the best way to meet people real life?
anotherkidnamedaustin: gotta be specific x and y chromosome
CoachMeech: so easy to get a bj on grinder
TeaLeafi: im a top <3
theonlymonkas: you can get that checkmark yourself!
CheeseManUchiha: KappaPride
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: go on Grindr
Srule: Adultfriendfinder uses your payment strategy
PiroFloydian: nonbinary people exist
K177: but i'm an attack helicopter, which gender do i fit in 🤔
dyslexicat: KappaPride
jimmyadaro: Sports or e-sports??
Ayyyy420Lmao: how many decimals of pi do you know?
0R4NG3: win win KappaPride
PiroFloydian: bi people exist too
voxelfox0125: This will either piss you off or make you laugh. https://guidedhacking.com/forums/wall-of-shame.462/ browse normal threads.
bankzed: there are no such thing gay tops, it's all bottoms KappaPride
pjayys77: seems you put a lot of thought into this
TeaLeafi: imagine being gay lmao
c1tr0n75: @georgehotz do you think you will get to do another hackthebox ? that shit was fun man
dyslexicat: PiroFloydian that's cool and they can use another app to find dates
rndmsqnce: any good dates lately
MrTriharder: Fucking homophobic guy in chat Dansgame
itsxaos: are traps gay?
TeaLeafi: comma.dating
likespuppies: @georgehotz Lamb or steak?
synoborg: do you remember everything you read?
nvda9: Illegal life pro tips: try tinder if you are beside the army campus.
TeaLeafi: comma.bio
joiput: PogChamp
aaaakshat: women were invented by porn companies to make more porn
b2kemann: when are we doing a haskell stream??
64pillars: comma.comma
Gapzyy: whats your take on religion
almonte550: If I beat you at chess can I get hired in comma ai?
bayarealove: My current and last girlfriend I met on bumble, and I've hooked up with a couple girls from tinder
anotherkidnamedaustin: do you believe in coincidences?
jimmyadaro: Comma Pharma
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogChamp
Ayyyy420Lmao: @itsxaos this. are traps gay?
K177: Kappa
Lieutenant_51: cum.ma PogChamp
Nussinov: when are we getting comma.gg for your version of twitch
janpoonthong: Apple or Samsung and why?
MrTriharder: <3
barkazzaz: Kappa
benchai18: @georgehotz if u investigate unsolved mysteries while streaming, you’ll get thousands of subs instantly ‼️ ‼️ ‼️
K177: aha Kappa
christianthefalco: @georgehotz are you actually looking for people with Chemistry/Coding background?
bojosos: Do you know what to 2^31 is?
vix_dev: that's what I need, ML algorithms to pick my next date
jimmyadaro: :clap:
TeaLeafi: at a boy
evnomics: Pogchamp
TeaLeafi: you tell them
igg44705: @georgehotz what are your biggest regrets?
TeaLeafi: <3
realolejka: i identify myself as attack helicopter
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: sounds good
deva73: commaTREES
theonlymonkas: do you sleep on the kitchen?
codsane: comma.xxx
aaaakshat: this stream is the coronvirus equivalent of pillowtalk
MrTriharder: @georgehotz @TeaLeafi BAN THIS GUY DansGame
blondephilia: I'm grabbing the domain
b2kemann: when are we doing a haskell stream?
theonlymonkas: SeemsGood
TeaLeafi: @MrTriharder why?
ab289528: @realolejka LUL
dorkmo: lots of mantinance
solitarynative: HotPokket
nizero: georgehotz did u like ur long vacation in Asian last year
K177: ptsd D:
Scydra_: @georgehotz can you give a quick summary of what your company does?
MrTriharder: HotPokket
ahahahaitslit: rip kobe
TeaLeafi: @georgehotz ban this guy @MrTriharder
dyslexicat: it's a sad life FeelsBadMan
Nussinov: their gunna fill you with gas
likespuppies: @georgehotz Sweat bums on your face
almonte550: I identify as a coronavirus
dyxx_pix: can u calculate the chances that u will get coronavirus
anotherkidnamedaustin: ptsd is a scam
CoachMeech: OCAML IS GOD
K177: PepeHands
jimmyadaro: Sports or e-sports? Come on LUL
yourdailydoseofcocaine: Tolerate everything except intolerance ~ George Holz. I love it!
timi13462: top 5 tv shows
TeaLeafi: @georgehotz ban this guy @MrTriharder his being mean
yevheniiushtyk: Can you play any instrument?
realolejka: pepoCry
Nussinov: pump me full of fuel daddy Kreygasm
64pillars: the real unsung heroes of
K177: melt beams don't melt jet fuel
benchai18: @georgehotz if u investigate unsolved mysteries while streaming, you’ll get thousands of subs. I’m serious. You’re a google rabbit hole wiz
zennydmt: do you play online multiplayer games?
bankzed: or you can be sold to a warring country
rndmsqnce: tell us your worst date story
equipollent_z: what do you think of emergence & self-organization?
likespuppies: helicopter, strong men rubbing you down with grease :)
theonlymonkas: do you sleep on the kitchen?
toront0saur: can i invest in comma.ai ?????
itsxaos: whats your lichess @ georgehotz
pjayys77: warrant officers is the way to go tho
LordHord: More hackerrank?
dyxx_pix: do u like the rapper logic
ahahahaitslit: have you used ocaml
almonte550: I identify as a coronavirus
doctorgenus: on your break, what did you do besides drugs and learn coq?
bytebacon: are you a liberal
timi13462: top 5 tv shows?
TeaLeafi: comma.notascam
whycopper: Let’s play rocket league @georgehotz
jimmyadaro: I cannot tolerate… mosquitoes
tajpouria: How i can buy a comma2 from iran ??
likespuppies: show us your bed PogChamp
yourdailydoseofcocaine: I identify as a hoooman
TeaLeafi: comma.notascam lmao
Scydra_: @georgehotz can you give a quick summary of what your company does?
K177: LUL
TeaLeafi: comma.notascam
b2kemann: haskell stream soon?
MrTriharder: @georgehotz One game of twitch tic tac tr
nozoke: Question for your opinion - Why are most billionaire startups started from individuals that attend prestigious universities regardless of finishing or not? @georgehotz
shieeeeeeeeet: how's backspace.ai doing?
nitrixen: You're obviously smart. How do you stay motivated?
nvda9: George have a look at that ThePersonDoesNotExist.com
equipollent_z: Rule 34 COVID-19?
anotherkidnamedaustin: @georgehotz do you think the past and future are illusions?
rndmsqnce: tell us a bad date story
bojosos: Have you ever been scammed?
voxelfox0125: This will either piss you off or make you laugh. https://guidedhacking.com/forums/wall-of-shame.462/ browse normal threads.
K177: D:
Jehhred: Comma 2 to Australia?!?!!?!?1
zeus13i: lol 'no'
TeaLeafi: comma.notascam <3
igg44705: @georgehotz can i use comma 2 in india?
benchai18: if u investigate unsolved mysteries while streaming, you’ll get thousands of subs so fast
solitarynative: quick rundown>
rndmsqnce: or a good date story
jimmyadaro: "So why comma.ai? Because you want to do something with your life. You want to see progress being made. You want to change the way the narrative will play out. You are bored, and want the world to be less boring. And at the end of the day, you want to win."
l1ght5p33d: lol 'no'
timi13462: top 5 tv shows??
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: $$$$$
zwisch: do you use photogrammetry at comma?
Bootyclub: Any plans to support more Subaru models for the Comma 2?
ahahahaitslit: have you used OCAML
theonlymonkas: have you ever been scammed?
christianthefalco: they were smarter?
janpoonthong: you look like Gordon Ramsay
toront0saur: CAN INVEST IN COMMA ???
AresRai: @christianthefalco LUL
anotherkidnamedaustin: what came first, time or the universe? like the planck era times
CoachMeech: OCAML IS GOD
bytebacon: Who is smarter? Elon Musk or Mike Tyson
PiroFloydian: lol
opus_000: solve oak island
nvda9: https://www.thispersondoesnotexist.com/
zennydmt: who is the most intelligent person you look up to
THX1342: comma.spy
jimmyadaro: Are computer programmers the last job to be replaced?? @georgehotz
doctorgenus: so the take from university is connections for VC funding?!!
CheeseManUchiha: hotz decodes the pyramids
deva73: did the college education help them in what they do at work
peter35_: clintHard
anotherkidnamedaustin: what came first, time or the universe? like the planck era times..?
lightofhel1: Scooby Doo Hotz
igg44705: @georgehotz does the comma 2 work in india?
TeaLeafi: ima INVEST!!!!
K177: PogU
cybergenik: !discord
TeaLeafi: IMA INVEST!!!!!!!
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogChamp
Br4nnon: discord linkkkk
AresRai: !discord
TeaLeafi: discord link!
cybergenik: whats the discrod?
benchai18: What’s the discord link
TeaLeafi: !discord
jimmyadaro: !discord
jimmyadaro: Are computer programmers the last job to be replaced?? @georgehotz
benchai18: !discord
CoachMeech: y'all some plebs
MrTriharder: FeelsBadMan
yourdailydoseofcocaine: This is my first time on this stream but I’ve watched a lot of your videos before. Thank you it’s great so far! Shit talking and not doing anything but also doing a lot! Only on George’s stream
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: !discord
martinkirilov: Because most of them have more capital from their relations and links
gobk0: !time
itsxaos: https://discord.comma.ai/
limpid_kzonix: how your researching in theorems proving is going?)
itsxaos: https://discord.comma.ai/ boys
anotherkidnamedaustin: what came first, time or the universe? like the planck era times?
YoungGuns_: @georgehotz do you like scooby doo or nah
Ayyyy420Lmao: u live in SF?
benchai18: @itsxaos Legend
bytebacon: Why did you name it Comma?
nic0latesla: Do you like Bug bounty program?
igg44705: @georgehotz would comma 2 work in india?
toront0saur: PERFECT. WHAT IS THE DISCORD ?
TheLastMrX: @georgehotz why you just dont make a bot to answer this simple questions ?
TeaLeafi: !discord link???
TeaLeafi: whgats the discord??????????
MrTriharder: @georgehotz Why SF of all cities?
codsane: https://discord.comma.ai/ fellas
nozoke: Ty for answering :)
MrTriharder: @georgehotz Why SD* of all cities?
TeaLeafi: thaml ypu
ahahahaitslit: have you used ocaml
jimmyadaro: Are computer programmers the last job to be replaced?? @georgehotz
dima_lanski: Which trajectory?
brownyyyylocks: legend KappaRoss
THX1342: too much bs in the vc world..
b2kemann: humans making everything into a soscial game
Br4nnon: monkaS
dyxx_pix: what do u think abt graph networks
peter35_: is anime degenerate?
techtim123: Book suggestions??
MrTriharder: monkah
itsxaos: LUL
theonlymonkas: favorite album
brownyyyylocks: keep at it we'll support comma!!
TeaLeafi: nah nah we will never
K177: l0l
nvda9: this is ai powered web, generates pictures of people who doesn't exist
tybutnowyoudie: monkaS
TeaLeafi: monkaS
anotherkidnamedaustin: how can the universe have an age if time is relative? these are the things i want to talk about
nvda9: https://www.thispersondoesnotexist.com/
mikey9988: monkaS
SofiaLouise: there is ~50% male female on tinder in Norway. US women are more sexually conservative i suppose
anotherkidnamedaustin: society is the biggest scam on earth dude
K177: cmonBruh
madscnt: !discord
martinkirilov: @georgehotz That's what happens when youre more driven by the project itself than its profitability on the short term
bytebacon: Stream gameplay
TeaLeafi: george ur awesome
blondephilia: Libertarianism ResidentSleeper
theonlymonkas: there will be stream tomorrow?
Ayyyy420Lmao: what book?
thecoder15: atlas shrugged yo best book ever
brownyyyylocks: oh no ayn rand
anti_natalist: marx quote?
nvda9: what book
Ayyyy420Lmao: what book he talking bout?
b2kemann: lool
thecoder15: atlas shrugged @Ayyyy420Lmao
bytebacon: Ayn Rand was one cold old lady
PiroFloydian: why?
jimmyadaro: Are computer programmers the last job to be replaced?? @georgehotz
solitarynative: don't tell hasan that LUL
b2kemann: *soviet anthem playing*
Ayyyy420Lmao: that's one boring book
jimmyadaro: Fuck Marx
narkoSays: @georgehotz If I'm looking for a coding mentor, do you have an idea where best to post? EU btw.
almonte550: So I can't talk about the optimizations of covid-19 we talked about here to make it worst than HIV and cancer combined?
anotherkidnamedaustin: duh big scam
MrTriharder: KKomrade
Ayyyy420Lmao: you better read some hoppe or rothbard
likespuppies: if you take the cynical viewpoint ye
PiroFloydian: i dont buy that at all @georgehotz
shieeeeeeeeet: how's backspace.ai doing? @georgehotz
jimmyadaro: "Equality or freedom"
aaaakshat: i leave the chat for 5 mins and now geohot is is karl marx?
anotherkidnamedaustin: a little scammy
yourdailydoseofcocaine: Now this is OUR stream
dyxx_pix: im gonna create an ai that perfectly times my message so that u read it based on where ur eyes r looking
doctorgenus: how much does your rent cost?
yevheniiushtyk: Why not make a discord related to this twitch community? Where people could dicuss and share stuff relates to the stream
Siandemm: Why?
murgmasallam: Did the Chinese really contain the virus?
Br4nnon: you have a point
christianthefalco: Try an Ayn Rand novel LMAO
jimmyadaro: Are computer programmers the last job to be replaced?? @georgehotz
equipollent_z: have you read "Complexity: A Guided Tour" ?
Scydra_: but isnt the author counting on only a few ppl following this and not all
THX1342: have you ever read brave new world?
Ayyyy420Lmao: are you familiar with hans herman hoppe?
SofiaLouise: How fast do you read?
brownyyyylocks: is it 1am yet?
solitarynative: @georgehotz make a community discord for us please
K177: ccp really does miracles
l1ght5p33d: Wellfare can be graphed.. reward as a curve it is an inverse quadratic
Br4nnon: good to see other viewpoints
Alexthematey: @georgehotz are u a libertarian?
Nussinov: no no george - the idea is that the government has complete and utter power over the people, so the people never even KNOW how resources are distributed Kappa
l1ght5p33d: some is good then the reward drops off
b2kemann: the chinese contained it's people.. lol
Bombapil0t: we need a corona rap hots
CoachMeech: melanie mitchell is a very smart person
forkdb: Hey
birkett0011: You read "When Atlas Shrugged"? @georgehotz
jimmyadaro: Are computer programmers the last job to be replaced?? @georgehotz
zoogaezee: is there a possibility China is lying about their Corona-virus numbers? In order to save reputation points'
almonte550: If I beat you in chess can I get hired in comma ai?
Ayyyy420Lmao: are you familiar with hans herman hoppe?
C0deCane: LUL that was great
jimmyadaro: @birkett0011 Amazing book
forkdb: I see Indian emblem
Exclamation_mark_CODE: I know a guy who knows a guy who has chicken permits
cybergenik: wait so why do you think that P = BQP? can you explain?
CoachMeech: She is very intelligent
brownyyyylocks: Chuck Rhodes slick
toront0saur: DISCORD LINK????
anotherkidnamedaustin: dude people are dumb. were told we started as a single cell with mutations LMFAO theres a better chance tomcr00se wins best album of the year next 1000 years
forkdb: Good...great
deva73: ya. communism leads to this underground market of favours
theonlymonkas: have you read the hitchhiker's guide to the galaxy?
jimmyadaro: Are computer programmers the last job to be replaced?? @georgehotz
K177: what do you think of a fully automated luxury communism
PiroFloydian: anarchosyndicalism is the way
haircutjimmy: more c programming!
anotherkidnamedaustin: dude people are dumb. we are told we started as a single cell with mutations LMFAO theres a better chance tomcr00se wins best album of the year next 1000 years
bojosos: Have you read 1984?
apollobelvedere: squad4
bankzed: why do I keep getting dudes from thispersondoesnotexist.com? I wanna take a face from there and deepfake it onto some porn so I can jack it to a person that doesn't exist. Kappa
jimmyadaro: @K177 Luxury or communism, can't have both
nvda9: George, ever counted your wpm?
bokeee_: @jimmyadaro spamming atpLaw atpCop
equipollent_z: I love this complexity book, introducing complexity theory
LordHord: Why vim
apollobelvedere: dude 1984 lmao xD society xDddd
anotherkidnamedaustin: metahuman
georgehotz: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Metamorphosis_of_Prime_Intellect
narkoSays: @georgehotz If I'm looking for a coding mentor, do you have an idea where best to post/search?
l1ght5p33d: C suite will get undercut by tech department it is the way of nature
jimmyadaro: @bokeee_ I'm trying to solve that question lmao
zoogaezee: is there a possibility China is lying about their Corona-virus numbers? In order to save reputation points'
Br4nnon: graphic is my middle name
qlutoo: have you read flowers for algernon
TeaLeafi: MAKE A BOOK LIST WE SHOULD READ!!!! please!!!
TeaLeafi: MAKE A BOOK LIST WE SHOULD READ!!!! please!!! !!!
equipollent_z: cliche thing to mention, but... Godel Escher Bach?
georgehotz: http://localroger.com/casodycs.html
anotherkidnamedaustin: RWU
CheeseManUchiha: cicadas monkaS
jimmyadaro: BOOK LIST ON GITHUB?!??!
apollobelvedere: reading both younger than 100 years old knutR
brownyyyylocks: why read it?
Bombapil0t: "k3yb04rd" Your message wasn't posted due to conflicts with the channel's moderation settings. DansGame
theonlymonkas: book list!
Ayyyy420Lmao: are you familiar with hans herman hoppe (libertarian author)?
jimmyadaro: BOOK LIST ON GITHUB?!??
apollobelvedere: books squad4
K177: @jimmyadaro yeah true, now that I think about it if robots replaced the need for jobs, and communism kicked in, it would become the norm and no longer a luxury LUL
itsxaos: thanks
Atlas03: spoiler it rooREE
cybergenik: @georgehotz wait so why do you think that P = BQP? can you explain?
Alexthematey: @georgehotz are u a libertarian?
CoachMeech: science fiction is for nerds
admirablelive: @georgehotz do you have a god complex?
igg44705: @georgehotz do you relate to House from house md?
likespuppies: ROGER WILLIAMS PogChamp
rndmsqnce: same as the first job?
equipollent_z: Thanks for the book links!
rndmsqnce: oldest profession
narkoSays: @georgehotz If I'm looking for a coding mentor, do you have an idea where best to post/search?
MrTriharder: @georgehotz Is there a movie for this book? too lazy to read
b2kemann: geohot book club
64pillars: wheres the goodnotes link
blondephilia: what was the second book @chat?
jimmyadaro: @cybergenik BQP= BQP^BQP
anotherkidnamedaustin: if time is relative, why do we age
TeaLeafi: MAKE A BOOK LIST WE SHOULD READ!!!! please!!!!
T3chHS: How valuable do you think reading is?
zoogaezee: is there a possibility China is lying about their Corona-virus numbers? In order to save reputation points'??
benchai18: What are you most proud of? Something Ur comfortable mentioning publicly.... obv
bojosos: Have you read 1984?
apollobelvedere: read uni bomber manifesto and that's it squad4
cortickal: Familiar with Mencius Moldbug?
igg44705: @georgehotz does the comma 2 work in india?
thecoder15: @georgehotz have you read the unibomber manifesto
jimmyadaro: BOOK LIST ON GITHUB PLEASE
yevheniiushtyk: Writing? LUL
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: monkaW
costcospizza: he was right
dyxx_pix: why hasnt air transportation replaced cars?
theonlymonkas: book list
blondephilia: FBI not lying LUL
aman_v2k: lmao @jimmyadaro
anotherkidnamedaustin: fbi scam
TeaLeafi: BOOK LIST ON GITHUB PLEASE!!!
pjayys77: are you a fan of Noam Chomsky @georgehotz
vix_dev: sean carrol's something deeply hidden was really good
TeaLeafi: BOOK LIST ON GITHUB PLEASE!!!!!!
apollobelvedere: read nothing and play video games instead squad4
TeaLeafi: @apollobelvedere true
brownyyyylocks: how did you find metamorphosis
blondephilia: Yes, Marx describes problems well. Incorrect prescription.
jimmyadaro: It invents problems
jimmyadaro: Marx sucks, Engels too
murgmasallam: Will this pandemic change political systems across nations?
narkoSays: @georgehotz If I'm looking for a coding mentor, do you have an idea where best to post/search?
Hawklite: you have to get your message heard somehow
bokeee_: Making manifestos about problems but not giving proper solutions is a bitch move
T3chHS: How much do you value reading?
apollobelvedere: read nothing, dont play video games and breathe manually instead squad4
TeaLeafi: BOOK LIST ON GITHUB PLEASE!!!
theonlymonkas: could you do a book list
anotherkidnamedaustin: usa is a democracy? but when coronavirus hits people complaining they need 2trillion buyouts
voxelfox0125: React to these posts about bad ways to learn programming. https://guidedhacking.com/forums/wall-of-shame.462/ (browse normal threads.)
anotherkidnamedaustin: pepelaugh
deva73: means of production should reside with the state : worst point according to me
Ayyyy420Lmao: well the unabomber claims that industrial society cant be fixed because psychological issues it causes
realolejka: @bokeee_ is a communist move
admirablelive: @georgehotz do you have a god complex?
zwisch: also mailing pipe bombs is a huge overreaction
benchai18: @zoogaezee Is there a possibility China is lying about some shit to push us into acting a certain way or taking certain actions.
PiroFloydian: have you read kropotkin/bakunin?
TeaLeafi: BOOK LIST ON GITHUB PLEASE!!!?
likespuppies: the solution was to blow everything up :pepega:
anotherkidnamedaustin: production does reside with state? 2TRILLION BUYOUT LMFAO
igg44705: what do you think about stoicism?
b2kemann: that beard
TeaLeafi: that beard
TeaLeafi: BEARD:3
jimmyadaro: Have you read Atlas Shrugged? @georgehotz
dr_set: the solution according to him was to send bombs in the mail to get attention and to write a manifesto
blondephilia: defection
jmv_chin: Do you use a mechanical ⌨️
d0ubletruth: that's because they dont think people will have a *reason* to
Ayyyy420Lmao: essentially stop working and they still have to provide for you
theonlymonkas: BAN
anotherkidnamedaustin: how is a 2trillion dollar buyout to specific government chosen companies not socialism? pepelaugh
dyxx_pix: what do u think will be the effect of the 2 tril stimulus pkg on the economy
jimmyadaro: @jmv_chin Yep
itsxaos: Can we ever bring the size of governments/institutions back down WITHOUT burning them down completely?
solitarynative: debate destiny and get some clout
thecoder15: have you read Richard Feynmans work on simulations via quantum computers @georgehotz
equipollent_z: another book question: have you read "Order of Time" by Carlo Rovelli? That changed my perspective on time completely.
deva73: lure em with ferrarti
ahahahaitslit: do you read scott aaronson
blondephilia: You have to breed that tendency out of the populace.
Abnico: @georgehotz https://twitter.com/breaking911/status/1242712281760358401?s=21
jimmyadaro: Have you read Atlas Shrugged? @georgehotz
jimmyadaro: @itsxaos Yep, minarchism
T3chHS: How much do you value reading?
anotherkidnamedaustin: government chooses who to buyout and who not too. but we are a democracy
apollobelvedere: here we go on politics chat TriHard
theonlymonkas: do you like interstellar
nvda9: religion is a scam
solitarynative: cmonBruh
PiroFloydian: @jimmyadaro he literally mentioned that like 3 mins ago
equipollent_z: the bio book on Feynman is pretty good too
Abnico: Politics are for noobs
b2kemann: feynman was the last american hero
TeaLeafi: politics is a scam
jimmyadaro: @PiroFloydian I was making coffee
apollobelvedere: here comes the interstellar fan TriHard
PiroFloydian: political theory
anotherkidnamedaustin: politics defined in one sentence. People Scam
ahahahaitslit: have you read scott aaronson's book
jimmyadaro: It's 4:47 AM here LUL
benchai18: Fuck fed government. Protect us and unify us, but besides that F off. Local government should be far more important. Even affecting change on a local level is difficult, but at least possible. People in proximity to us should have a say in our laws, not some twats across the country t
dima_lanski: @georgehotz But wouldn't you say the same about the current US system?
blondephilia: Hierarchy everywhere in everything.
igg44705: OPEN SOURCE THE LAW
Abnico: Politics is a gay tv show
equipollent_z: rain
Ayyyy420Lmao: anyway really recomend you reading some hans herman hoppe, he's one of the few libertarian who takes it logically to the extreme
toront0saur: What is the commas DISCORD LINK ??!!!
murgmasallam: @Abnico whatever you shared is no longer there
solitarynative: crypto will replace government unironically
cortickal: Ted Kaczynski spends more time in addressing the "solution" in his new book Anti-Tech Revolution
blondephilia: Pan-integralism or nothing.
nitrixen: "Great minds discuss ideas; average minds discuss events; small minds discuss people."
doctorgenus: Life question: how do you get rich if you are dumb?
anotherkidnamedaustin: 2trillion bailout
b2kemann: goverment should be limited
itsxaos: @jimmyadaro where has that ever happened? its a nice label to say we want minimal government but the point is that it just doesnt seem to work
MrTriharder: @georgehotz that sounds like some buzzfeed shit
apollobelvedere: yea
anotherkidnamedaustin: 2trillion
deva73: what about SOCIALISM?
Ayyyy420Lmao: lmao 2016
anti_natalist: its a loan you know that right
apollobelvedere: Ted is literally the guy who escaped the cave of Plato
jimmyadaro: @itsxaos Maybe not now, the world is not ready yet, they need "papi Estado" like we say in Argentina
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Wut
Siandemm: USSR socialism is all about the top 0.01 rule the country and have any goods they needed but others eat shit
phrixus_bro: banned
codephobia: book must be a real killer
likespuppies: @georgehotz Thoughts on the dangers of collective wisdom, e.g. wikipedia?
nvda9: https://discord.comma.ai
anotherkidnamedaustin: @Siandemm hows that different than us
Abnico: Ban him
jimmyadaro: @Siandemm Yeah, slaving people
rndmsqnce: brave new world
anotherkidnamedaustin: @jimmyadaro same as usa
jimmyadaro: Anti-Tech? That's plain stupid
Ayyyy420Lmao: @anotherkidnamedaustin lol no?
itsxaos: @jimmyadaro so thats my fear, the only way governments get smaller is if they burn
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: PogChamp PogChamp
jimmyadaro: @anotherkidnamedaustin Slaves???? Where???
anotherkidnamedaustin: @jimmyadaro um corporations
jimmyadaro: @itsxaos Maybe it's the right way
anotherkidnamedaustin: um schools?
Abnico: quadratic funding is a good tunnel
solitarynative: is chainlink a scam?
C0deCane: boomers LUL
apollobelvedere: wooow
localcanofdutchgold: ez
jimmyadaro: @anotherkidnamedaustin How is that slaving? Are you stupid or something?
Ayyyy420Lmao: @solitarynative that's what i wanted to know he didnt answer
itsxaos: LIVE PIRACY PogChamp
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: EZ
mikey9988: EZ
GeekTryingToGeek: KEKW
0R4NG3: EZ
equipollent_z: do you think bio is the future of computation?
Bombapil0t: :D
narkoSays: 4Head
jimmyadaro: EZ
Br4nnon: lmao
TeaLeafi: live piracy kekw
toront0saur: Thanks @nvda9
TeaLeafi: EZ
blondephilia: lel
solitarynative: @Ayyyy420Lmao I'm testing him LUL
ad_1337: anti tech LUL
apollobelvedere: very interesting stream, straight to the subject squadHmm
Bombapil0t: e-book version gg
Exclamation_mark_CODE: yoink
benchai18: But dude... that “who cares” attitude is because we know we have zero influence over our federal govt. Zero. People are rightfully disillusioned. I don’t mean angry, I mean resigned and disinterested because of how inaccessible our federal government is. I don’t care what Pelosi’s pubes are shaped like. I don’t want Pelosi to influence laws that affect California.
bankzed: read us a bed time story, Kappa
anti_natalist: @georgehotz what principles of libertarian are compelling?
Abnico: Libgen.is
jimmyadaro: "Anti-tech" pirated lmao
anotherkidnamedaustin: ur taught to get up when the bell rings, sit down and shut up and listen to the teachers who gets a yearly madate from u guessed it the goverment. but yeah ur free @jimmyadaro
TheLastMrX: that was... FAST
theonlymonkas: LUL
Abnico: @georgehotz libgen.is
jimmyadaro: @anotherkidnamedaustin Sounds like a 15 years-old "rebel" argument lmao
icanthitthose: how did you get the pdf
apollobelvedere: thought he wrote this to get bitches squad4
blondephilia: @benchai18 people shouldn't need to care about their government. a child shouldn't need to care about the competency of his parents.
anotherkidnamedaustin: then go work 9-5 and get scammed @jimmyadaro lol while the pay gap gets wider and wider and the peons make less and less
Bombapil0t: this is our jailbreak guy from the past!
solitarynative: deep
Ayyyy420Lmao: @anotherkidnamedaustin wtf u talking about im 32 and have never worked
jimmyadaro: @anotherkidnamedaustin lmao I have my own business, I'm CEO, what the fuck boy hahahaha
anotherkidnamedaustin: @jimmyadaro im 23 suma cum laude from iowa trading biotech options on stock market.
murgmasallam: Didn't the use of invasive facial recognition help China in containing the virus?
sebastianh_777: How does the lane detection find the lanes on roads without any lane lines? (like through an intersection)
doctorgenus: if you have milk in those grocery bags, it's probably GG
ahahahaitslit: have you read scott aaronson's book
cybergenik: Wait can you explain why P = BQP?
likespuppies: human condition used to be much more base
equipollent_z: fan of Douglas Hofstadter?
anti_natalist: @georgehotz what principles of libertarianism are compelling?
rndmsqnce: gotta get that real ego death then you'll get what he means
nremind: most people were very bored in the past
jimmyadaro: @anotherkidnamedaustin I'm 22, and i have market experience since my 18 so…
admirablelive: @georgehotz why mac over windows?
thecoder15: @georgehotz http://www.wisdom.weizmann.ac.il/~naor/COURSE/feynman-simulating.pdf
apollobelvedere: @jimmyadaro where do I apply to be your bitch?
benchai18: @blondephilia I think you’re misunderstanding me. I’m just saying that local government should govern us way more than federal does
jimmyadaro: BQP = BQP^ BQP
CoachMeech: i can think, i can fast, i can wait
blondephilia: everything Ted describes can be derived from careful study and analysis of zoology and animal behavior.
jimmyadaro: @apollobelvedere Search me on Linkedin
apollobelvedere: @jimmyadaro yes daddy
apollobelvedere: squadHmm
jimmyadaro: @apollobelvedere lmao
hastingspb: Q = 1/P
anotherkidnamedaustin: @jimmyadaro so? im not comparing dick sizes. im just saying go to school, go work for a corporation in bed with the government, and stay poor forever is basically slavery
solitarynative: TRUE LU
solitarynative: LUL
passingremarks: everytime i talk to a libertarian
jimmyadaro: @anotherkidnamedaustin That's stupid, so…
PiroFloydian: libertarian socialism is fantastic ideologically @georgehotz
passingremarks: about anything
Ayyyy420Lmao: hans herman hoppe has the most autistic approach to libertarianism the dude's philosophy is impenetrable
ahahahaitslit: have you read antifragile by taleb
admirablelive: @georgehotz why mac over windows?
igg44705: @georgehotz what do you think about stoicism?
zwisch: hemlock
thecoder15: oops that wasn't what i was trying share
passingremarks: they seem to not understand simple cause and effect
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: they got his ass
mikey9988: clapped some boy cheeks KEKW
jimmyadaro: @passingremarks Why?
PiroFloydian: like from an analysis perspective
b2kemann: socrates went out as a champ
equipollent_z: Hofstadter was Melanie Mitchel's doctoral advisor, they worked on an AI program called "Copycat" to form analogies on machines
anti_natalist: @georgehotz ask a simple question about arbitration and libertarianism falls apart
apollobelvedere: Socrates was a hologram, he never existed squad4
jimmyadaro: Socialism sucks lol
blondephilia: @benchai18 irrelevant. no one cares about policy in day to day life. they care about things that pertain to their lives.
Nussinov: most people are two questions away from complete existential disaster
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: Creating an UTOPIA good luck with that chat LULW
PiroFloydian: libertarian socialism is a thing @georgehotz
voxelfox0125: React to these posts about bad ways to learn programming. https://guidedhacking.com/forums/wall-of-shame.462/ (browse normal threads.)
MrTriharder: @jimmyadaro PHP DansGame I lost respect NotLikeThis
itsxaos: @georgehotz do you have a lichess account?
Ayyyy420Lmao: what's a good defense of a socialist position? never hears one
cybergenik: Do you know who Destiny is?
bojosos: How would you describe a "perfect" sciety
thecoder15: @georgehotz you can have a socialist system under a libertarian rule but you cant have the opposite
anotherkidnamedaustin: amazon is the utopia
doctorgenus: are you working from home tomorrow?
bankzed: Socrates got a medal of freedom? Kappa
ahahahaitslit: you will like antifragile by taleb
benchai18: @b2kemann Socrates was a bigot and transphobic. Jk. Just imitating SJWs for the lulz
Nussinov: @cybergenik LUL
Tyrant_01: WHY MAC OVER WINDOWS
peter35_: thoughts on the damore google memo thing?
anti_natalist: why cant we have it somewhere in the middle i.e. a mixed economy?
equipollent_z: have you started watching "Devs" on hulu? :D
localcanofdutchgold: @cybergenik lul
blondephilia: Libertarians can't answer how profits aren't put above the people.
apollobelvedere: @cybergenik please keep Destiny in the trash can
itsxaos: Density LUL
iambdp22: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC2750777/
TeaLeafi: ur like DESTINY!
admirablelive: @georgehotz why mac over windows?
cybergenik: lol
evnomics: You should talk to Destiny
solitarynative: debate destiny LUL
tybutnowyoudie: do you know reckful?
igg44705: what do you think about stoicism??
evnomics: you would get along
jimmyadaro: @MrTriharder lmao how is that important ?
TeaLeafi: Destiny!
MrNavfal1: I am not living, I'm just surviving
anti_natalist: talk to destiny Pog he talks to anyone
bokeee_: Good call LUL
cortickal: Destiny's a narcissist
localcanofdutchgold: @TeaLeafi this guy actually does stuff
christianthefalco: Destiny is for people that unironically think Joe Rogan is smart
AresRai: dont, its toxic
CoachMeech: you and destiny woukd actually be hilarious hahahahaahahah
MrTriharder: @jimmyadaro DansGame just LUL
benchai18: @blondephilia Mate that’s EXACTLY what I’m saying.
roystang: destiny really sucks
apollobelvedere: Destiny fan boys in chat knutR
Ayyyy420Lmao: @blondephilia profits are the people, profits are made by providing for people...
l1ght5p33d: the quality of this chat has really deteriorated
Scydra_: @georgehotz have you played dota 2 ever?
likespuppies: @christianthefalco you think joe rogan is not smart? lol
MrTriharder: @Scydra_ admiralW
cybergenik: Destiny is like the final raid boss of anyone who wants to debate in politics.
jimmyadaro: @MrTriharder OhMyDog
anotherkidnamedaustin: its a paper on targeted protein vaccine
Srule: This guys is destiny 2.0
AresRai: @l1ght5p33d its the spike in viewership recently :/
admirablelive: !PC
christianthefalco: @likespuppies uh oh
equipollent_z: is the outside of the universe the inside of the universe?
b2kemann: @benchai18 i don't care, when you take poision and make that your final lesson, you're a champ
Nussinov: to be fair he hates his subreddit too
peter35_: strims.gg numales in chat
Scydra_: @MrTriharder Of course a wild bulldog sub
roystang: @cybergenik hes really not tho
doctorgenus: how do you train your concentration? you're streaming for HOURS on end :P
blondephilia: @benchai18 not at all. I'm not saying people should have more say in local government.
keewon: regards from spain! How is the qurantine going ?
cybergenik: Hes super solid
MrTriharder: @Scydra_ admiralF1 admiralF2
admirablelive: @georgehotz What computer do you have?
madpyro21: @georgehotz Out of curiosity have you ever looked into ps4 security?
likespuppies: @christianthefalco i'll have you know i was in the navy seals and i could
igg44705: what do you think about stoicism?
ArcherCreatlol: squad1 squad2
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: LULW
Keijo: This chatroom is very intellectual indeed BrokeBack
TeaLeafi: true
jimmyadaro: @doctorgenus lmao
T3chHS: chat, what text editor is that? vim?
Bombapil0t: its a amigo computer @admirablelive
roystang: @cybergenik but hes not tho
pjayys77: can get quite toxic when you're talking about Desinty n Reddit
benchai18: @b2kemann Shit I don’t care even if he was transphobic and bigoted. I was fuckin around.
anotherkidnamedaustin: basically trap the virus and kill it outside of the healthy cells
nvda9: Does he play fps
zeus13i: @T3chHS - vi
anotherkidnamedaustin: pretty interesting actually
cybergenik: @roystang how so?
jimmyadaro: Do you fap? @georgehotz
blondephilia: @Ayyyy420Lmao Untrue. Else people wouldn't be renting as much as they do rather than owning.
Scydra_: @igg44705 good question, i wish to know as well
madscnt: Which IDE do you use?
roystang: @cybergenik dudes a weirdo
T3chHS: @zeus13i thank you!
b2kemann: @benchai18 I know, i just wanted to call him a champ one more time
solitarynative: is futa gay?
Atlas03: rooSmug
anti_natalist: destiny is pretty good faith as long as you dont ad hom, like most people
apollobelvedere: anyone here eating cheerios honey NUTS? squad4
boengels: your "tab" game knows no bounds...
MrTriharder: Time to get the key board question out chat LUL
roystang: @cybergenik hes the harvey weinstein of twitch
cybergenik: @roystang thats not a reasonable arguement, if you took any time to actually listen to what he says its solid
passingremarks: @jimmyadaro libertarians make assumptions about free markets and personal liberties that don't take into consideration bad actors that abuse those systems... which is why i say they don't understand cause and effect
roystang: @cybergenik but its not tho
toront0saur: cant wait to invest in comma!!!!!!!!!!
doctorgenus: so what's the take away from today's stream? buy dna test kits?
Ayyyy420Lmao: @blondephilia woah that's quite the non sequitur
yourdailydoseofcocaine: @admirablelive you should ask about his k e y b o a r d
itsxaos: What is it about reddit that makes it so awful?
Abnico: and I get bleach on my tshirt imma feel like an asshole
anotherkidnamedaustin: Because the S protein of SARS-CoV is involved in receptor recognition, as well as virus attachment and entry, it represents one of the most important targets for the development of SARS vaccines and therapeutics.
solitarynative: thoughts on vr porn?
MrTriharder: Chat ask about his key board Jebaited
yourdailydoseofcocaine: @itsxaos too many fking people.
PiroFloydian: Liberalism
jimmyadaro: @passingremarks I'd like to talk further about this but not now, i'm really sorry, i'm tired, it's almost 5 am here
ArcherCreatlol: squadR yo george what's up squadR
PiroFloydian: Liberalism is shit
igg44705: what do you think about stoicism?
cybergenik: @roystang Ok now your just being an idiot, calling him the Harvey Weinstein of Twitch. I mean just take like 20 minutes to actually look through some of his shit...
Bombapil0t: big business @solitarynative
Atlas03: anyone tried this new site egirl gg
jimmyadaro: @PiroFloydian Awesome argument
evnomics: They would be the extreme ends of our modern system
blondephilia: @Ayyyy420Lmao you said that profits are made by providing for people. Sure, but they aren't necessarily positive provisions.
jmv_chin: What mouse do you use
b2kemann: when are we going to meet your mom georg?
PiroFloydian: i mean neoliberalism
roystang: @cybergenik i used to, when i was in high school, not anymore
solitarynative: @Bombapil0t yes yes
blondephilia: Exploiting != providing in my book.
Ayyyy420Lmao: @blondephilia how is renting bad? providing a home is bad?
ahahahaitslit: what the fuck is destiny? the game?
l1ght5p33d: Guillotine liberalism
c1tr0n75: totalitarianism is the most coherent Kappa Kappa Kappa
anotherkidnamedaustin: https://www.jbc.org/content/264/18/10542.full.pdf
THX1342: do you think fascism is still a global risk?
equipollent_z: any favorite theories that came out of CERN?
igg44705: @blondephilia yeah you can give people meth and still get rich
Ayyyy420Lmao: @georgehotz whats a good defense of socialism acording to you?
doctorgenus: before we go to bed, can we see what you got in your grocery bags
jimmyadaro: Liberalism is not socialism wtf they've stolen that from libertarians
anotherkidnamedaustin: cross link s protein
evnomics: no its the international community working together lol
reckful_bald_spot_114: ahahahaitslit twitch streamer
igg44705: did any one see the new epsoid of better call saul today?
cybergenik: @roystang Ok, well if your gonna say some dumb shit it better be backed up. Or else don't say it
CoachMeech: neoliberlaism is just lib with free markets
equipollent_z: widdFaded
narkoSays: ppl tossing around definitions in chat which they probably aren't even aware of that they don't fully understand :P
blondephilia: @Ayyyy420Lmao people should be owning. renting shelter has caused enormous problems, namely mental health and destruction of birthrates. Trash it.
anotherkidnamedaustin: crosslinking the s protein is what u are looking for @georgehotz
jimmyadaro: @CoachMeech No one is "neoliberal", there's no "new liberty"
PiroFloydian: neoliberalism is both the dem and repub party establishments. started w/ regan and thatcher in the 80s. that whole thing @georgehotz
roystang: @cybergenik dudes a goober and his debates suck
solitarynative: dicatorship is the best depending on the dictator
evnomics: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Neoliberalism
itsxaos: do you think corporatism is a good/useful word?
bankzed: They halted the filming of the new Matrix movie so we will never know what Neo liberalism is... KappaHD
CoachMeech: aight buddy chill
PiroFloydian: renting is a scam yeah
Ayyyy420Lmao: @blondephilia lol what? not at all, owning comes with risks renting allows for more flexibility, if people choose to rent is because it has its benefits
narkoSays: ppl tossing around terms in chat which they probably aren't even aware of that they don't fully understand
C0deCane: @georgehotz what happened to the Uyghur muslims in China, kinda odd this all happens after that shit
toront0saur: DEF CON 28 still happening in the summer ??!!!!!
yourdailydoseofcocaine: @bankzed just wow. Kappa
Nussinov: completely irrelevant
Srule: Would you recommend a 60% key board for browsing pornhub?
cybergenik: @roystang ok cool, well now I know that everything your saying is vacuous...
reckful_bald_spot_114: narkoSays nice contribution to chat SeemsGood
anotherkidnamedaustin: its a example of how you can cross link and isolate the s protein in rona
anotherkidnamedaustin: and kill it off
ArcherCreatlol: LUL
MrTriharder: LUL
bojosos: Do you Fold@home
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: NOOOOOOOOO
PiroFloydian: shit
b2kemann: lool
blondephilia: @Ayyyy420Lmao people rent because they can't afford to own, not to escape risk.
phrixus_bro: thanks!!
Atlas03: rooCry
TeaLeafi: huhuuhuh
localcanofdutchgold: wtf
anotherkidnamedaustin: seriously comma.bio
mikey9988: LUL
Exclamation_mark_CODE: LUL
MrTriharder: fuck
Bombapil0t: BibleThump
equipollent_z: LUL
itsxaos: very fun stream <3
jimmyadaro: @narkoSays So what's your contribution?
TeaLeafi: NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO
dorkmo: choo chooooo
jimmyadaro: NOOO
THX1342: goodnight
MrTriharder: LUL chat
TeaLeafi: noooooooooooo
jimmyadaro: :(
ideology_sniffing_raccoon: <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3
THX1342: thanks for the stream
igg44705: @georgehotz what if a guys rings your frount door?
dr_set: bye <3
archer723: good night
nvda9: George, why don't I see you on DEFCON, you don't attend there anymore?
doctorgenus: noooooo
TeaLeafi: <3
anotherkidnamedaustin: comma.,bio ill sent my resume
roystang: @cybergenik take his 3 cm weiner out of ur mouth bro
MrTriharder: <3
toront0saur: LMAO
equipollent_z: didn't read stream description
BurntOut157: bye George
PiroFloydian: this was fun
ArcherCreatlol: u don't have anything to do else
TeaLeafi: <3 love uuuuuu
reckful_bald_spot_114: you fucked up chat
yourdailydoseofcocaine: @srule I’d rather recommend a 69% one kappa
TeaLeafi: love u so much <33333
solitarynative: tomorrow?
rndmsqnce: <3
bankzed: nn
uduver: Good night! <3
anotherkidnamedaustin: where do i send comma bio resume
TeaLeafi: <3
equipollent_z: widdPeace
Ayyyy420Lmao: @blondephilia so if you cant afford something you dont have it duh
likespuppies: @georgehotz Dream about meat
doctorgenus: good nite bud
jimmyadaro: Love ya
itsxaos: good night everyone, including the crazies :)
jimmyadaro: before we go to bed, can we see what you got in your grocery bags
localcanofdutchgold: <3
64pillars: lol
doctorgenus: :)
archer723: See you tommorrow? can we?
MrTriharder: <3 <3 <3
bokeee_: thanks for streamign george <3
toront0saur: NOO GEORG HAHAHA
TeaLeafi: LOVEUUUUu
igg44705: love you man
localcanofdutchgold: OMEGALUL
Keijo: George uses the newest Asus Predator mechanical anti-ghosting gaming key board, check link in bio for amazon
TeaLeafi: LOVE UUU
uduver: <3 <3 <3
pjayys77: lol wut
jimmyadaro: before we go to bed, can we see what you got in your grocery bags!
yourdailydoseofcocaine: Nighty night
ad_1337: see ya
Atlas03: rooLove
jimmyadaro: before we go to bed, can we see what you got in your grocery bags??
solitarynative: TRUE LUL
TeaLeafi: L:OVEEE U GEORGIE
iambdp22: https://www.embopress.org/doi/10.1038/sj.emboj.7600640
c1tr0n75: Geoorge getting all romantic on us
zwisch: hanlon's razor
MrTriharder: @georgehotz tomorrow again please
Cazaa_: LOVEE UU GEORGEEE
equipollent_z: widdHorn widdHorn widdHorn widdHorn
PiroFloydian: true
TeaLeafi: GEORGIE I LOVES UUUUUU
cybergenik: @georgehotz GN dude, BibleThump
benchai18: Night bruv
4FUN_PLAYER: gn <3
madpyro21: @georgehotz out of curiosity have you ever looked into ps4 security?
igg44705: people are just idots
Cazaa_: <3 <3 <3 <3 <3
murgmasallam: Woaahh DEEEEEEPP
toront0saur: @georgehotz ahahah
Saltyballss: fulltime streamer now PogChamp
jimmyadaro: before we go to bed, can we see what you got in your grocery bags?
Bombapil0t: ur the man <3
PiroFloydian: for the most part
archer723: Plz continue stream tommorrow!
benchai18: I’m an idiot and malicious
pjayys77: you said the K word
TeaLeafi: wowoowooowowow
Abnico: Noice
almonte550: Wait why are we finishing the stream
TeaLeafi: im sad
0R4NG3: HeyGuys byee